<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Sid Meier's Civilization 4 -->
<!-- Copyright Firaxis Games 2005 -->
<!-- -->
<!-- Game Text - New -->
<Civ4GameText xmlns="http://www.firaxis.com" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.firaxis.com ../../../../../Xml/Schema/Civ4Gametext.xsd">
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_UNIT_STEAM_TANK</Tag>
		<English>Steam Tank</English>
		<French>Tank à Vapeur</French>
		<German>Steamtank</German>
		<Italian>Carro armato a vapore</Italian>
		<Spanish>Steamtank</Spanish>
		<Polish>Czołg Parowy</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_UNIT_STEAM_TANK_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>The [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Steam Tank[COLOR_REVERT] is a tank powered by steam and steampunk technology. It destroys cavalry in combat and can attack from water effectively.</English>
		<Italian>Il [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]carro armato a vapore[COLOR_REVERT] è un carro con propulsione a vapore. In combattimento è devastante contro la cavalleria, ed è efficace anche negli attacchi anfibi.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_UNIT_STEAM_TANK_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Steam Tanks are war machines used by steampunk armies. The thick steel armor plating of a Steam Tank makes it all but immune to lesser weapons such as arrows and crossbow bolts. The best way of disabling or destroying a Steam Tank is by cannon fire, although the Steam Tank has been known to shrug off even such damage.</English>
		<Italian>Il carro armato a vapore è simile a un Carro blindato.</Italian>
		<Polish>Czołgi Parowe to potworne, dymiące machiny wojenne, które suną w kierunku wroga strzelając w niego śmiertelnie niebezpiecznymi kulami z karabinów parowych, by zmiszczyć wszystkich ośmielających przeciwstawić się Imperium Człowieka. Zostały zaprojektowane przez sławnego wynalazcę Leonardo z Miragliano, który dostosował parę wykorzystywaną przez krasnoludy do poruszania tłoków i kół zębatych, które napędzają koła Czołgu Parowego. W czasie wojny Szkoła Inżynierów</Polish>
	</TEXT>
</Civ4GameText>