<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Civ4GameText xmlns="http://www.firaxis.com" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.firaxis.com ../../../../../Xml/Schema/Civ4Gametext.xsd">
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZEPHYR</Tag>
		<English>Zephyr</English>
		<Italian>Zefiro</Italian>
		<Polish>Zefir</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZEPHYR_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Airships are popular forms of transport in clockpunk stories. Varieties of airships vary widely. One of the main types of airship is known as non-rigid, but such airships are commonly called Zephyrs. They are uncommon in steampunk stories, wherein the preference is for a more industrial and mechanical aesthetic. Semi-rigid airships are slightly more common and are slightly larger than non-rigid types. They also contain an internal support structure known as a keel.</English>
		<Italian>Unità da combattimento aereo Clockpunk</Italian>
		<Polish>W 1851 roku Henri Jules Giffard zgłosił patent na zastosowanie maszyny parowej do napędu statków powietrznych. Opracował pierwowzór sterowca - balon wyposażony w śmigło napędzane maszyną parową o mocy 2,2 kW. 24 września 1852 wzniósł się z hipodromu w Paryżu na wysokość 1800 m i pokonał 27-kilometrową trasę do Elancourt koło Trappes z prędkością około 8 km/h. 9 sierpnia 1884 r. w Chalais-Meudon kpt. Charles Renard (1847-1905) i kpt. Arthur Krebs (1850-1935) pokonali 7,6-kilometrową trasę sterowcem La France z prędkością niemal 20 km/h (5,5 m/s). Sterowiec o wydłużonym kształcie miał podwieszoną gondolę, na końcu której był zamocowany silnik elektryczny o mocy 6,6 kW ze śmigłem. Statkiem kierowano za pomocą steru.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_UNIT_ZEPHYR_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>The [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Zephyr[COLOR_REVERT] is an alt-timeline Da Vinci/Clockpunk unit. It was sort of concieved as a wooden sailing ship held up by a balloon.</English>
		<Italian>Lo zefiro è un'unità in stile Clockpunk. Era ideato come una nave di legno sospesa in aria da una mongolfiera.</Italian>
		<Polish>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Zefir[COLOR_REVERT] to renesansowy sterowiec z czasów Leonarda Da Vinci.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
</Civ4GameText>