<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSPY v2004 rel. 2 U (http://www.xmlspy.com) by XMLSPY 2004 Professional Ed. Release 2, Installed Multi + SMP for 3 users (Firaxis Games) -->
<!-- Sid Meier's Civilization 4 -->
<!-- Copyright Firaxis Games 2005 -->
<!-- -->
<!-- Game Text - New -->
<Civ4GameText xmlns="http://www.firaxis.com" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.firaxis.com ../../../Xml/Schema/Civ4Gametext.xsd">
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ABBASID_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Abbasid)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ABBASID_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Abbasid) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ABBASID_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Abbasid Caliphate was the third of the Islamic caliphates to succeed the Islamic prophet Muhammad. The Abbasid dynasty descended from Muhammad's youngest uncle, Abbas ibn Abd al-Muttalib (566-653 CE), from whom the dynasty takes its name. They ruled as caliphs, for most of their period from their capital in Baghdad in modern-day Iraq, after assuming authority over the Muslim empire from the Umayyads in 750 CE (132 AH).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADENA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Adena)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADENA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Adena) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADENA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Adena culture was a Pre-Columbian Native American culture that existed from 1000 to 200 BC, in a time known as the Early Woodland period. The Adena culture refers to what were probably a number of related Native American societies sharing a burial complex and ceremonial system. The Adena lived in an area including parts of present-day Ohio, Indiana, West Virginia, Kentucky, New York, Pennsylvania and Maryland. Lasting traces of Adena culture are still seen in their substantial earthworks. Once Adena mounds numbered in the hundreds, but only a small number of Adena earthen monuments still survive today. These mounds generally ranged in size from 20 feet (6.1 m) to 300 feet (91 m) in diameter and served as burial structures, ceremonial sites, historical markers and possibly gathering places. These mounds were built using hundreds of thousands of baskets full of specially selected and graded earth. According to archaeological investigations, Adena mounds were usually built as part of burial ritual, in which the earth of the mound was piled immediately atop a burned mortuary building. These mortuary buildings were intended to keep and maintain the dead until their final burial was performed. Before the construction of the mounds, some utilitarian and grave goods would be placed on the floor of the structure, which was burned with the goods and honored dead within. The mound would then be constructed, and often a new mortuary structure would be placed atop the new mound.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AFGHANISTAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Afghanistan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AFGHANISTAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Afghanistan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AFGHANISTAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Afghanistan is a landlocked country located within South Asia and Central Asia. It has a population of approximately 32 million, making it the 42nd most populous country in the world. It is bordered by Pakistan in the south and east; Iran in the west; Turkmenistan, Uzbekistan, and Tajikistan in the north; and China in the far northeast. Its territory covers 652,000 km2 (252,000 sq mi), making it the 41st largest country in the world. Human habitation in Afghanistan dates back to the Middle Paleolithic Era, and the country's strategic location along the Silk Road connected it to the cultures of the Middle East and other parts of Asia. Through the ages the land has been home to various peoples and witnessed numerous military campaigns; notably by Alexander the Great, Muslim Arabs, Mongols, British, Soviet Russians, and in the modern-era by Western powers. The land also served as the source from which the Kushans, Hephthalites, Samanids, Saffarids, Ghaznavids, Ghorids, Khiljis, Mughals, Hotaks, Durranis, and others have risen to form major empires.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AKSUMITE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Aksumite)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AKSUMITE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Aksumite) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AKSUMITE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Kingdom of Aksum or Axum, also known as the Aksumite Empire, was a trading nation in the area of Eritrea and Northern Ethiopia. It existed from approximately 100-940 AD. It grew from the proto-Aksumite Iron Age period c. 4th century BC to achieve prominence by the 1st century AD, and was a major player in the commercial route between the Roman Empire and Ancient India. The Aksumite rulers facilitated trade by minting their own Aksumite currency, the state established its hegemony over the declining Kingdom of Kush and regularly entered the politics of the kingdoms on the Arabian Peninsula, eventually extending its rule over the region with the conquest of the Himyarite Kingdom.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALACALUFE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Alacalufe)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALACALUFE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Alacalufe) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALACALUFE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Kawésqar or Kaweskar, also called Alacaluf or Halakwulup (meaning "mussel eater" in Yaghan), are a South American people who live in the Chilean Patagonia, specifically in the Brunswick Peninsula, and Wellington, Santa Inés, and Desolación islands of the western area of Tierra del Fuego. Their traditional language is known as Kawésqar; it is endangered as few native speakers survive. Like the Yahgan in southern Chile and Argentina, the Kawésqar were a nomadic seafaring people, called canoe-people by some anthropologists. They made canoes that were eight to nine meters long and one meter wide, which would hold a family and its dog. They continued this fishing, nomadic practice until the twentieth century, when they were moved into settlements on land. Because of their maritime culture, the Kawésqar have never farmed the land.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALBANIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Albanian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALBANIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Albanian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALBANIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The modern-day territory of Albania was at various points in history part of the Roman provinces of Dalmatia (southern Illyricum), Macedonia (particularly Epirus Nova), and Moesia Superior. The modern Republic became independent after the collapse of the Ottoman Empire in Europe following the Balkan Wars. Albania declared independence in 1912 and was recognized the following year. It then became a Principality, Republic, and Kingdom until being invaded by Italy in 1939, which formed Greater Albania. The latter eventually turned into a Nazi German protectorate in 1943. The following year, a socialist People's Republic was established under the leadership of Enver Hoxha and the Party of Labour. Albania experienced widespread social and political transformations during the communist era, as well as isolationism from much of the international community. In 1991, the Socialist Republic was dissolved and the Republic of Albania was established.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALEMANNI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Alemanni)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALEMANNI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Alemanni) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALEMANNI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Alemanni were a confederation of Germanic tribes on the upper Rhine river. First mentioned by Cassius Dio in the context of the campaign of Caracalla of 213, the Alemanni captured the Agri Decumates in 260, and later expanded into present-day Alsace, and northern Switzerland, leading to the establishment of the Old High German language in those regions. In 496, the Alemanni were conquered by Frankish leader Clovis and incorporated into his dominions. Mentioned as still pagan allies of the Christian Franks, the Alemanni were gradually Christianized during the 7th century. The Pactus Alamannorum is a record of their customary law during this period. Until the 8th century, Frankish suzerainty over Alemannia was mostly nominal. But after an uprising by Theudebald, Duke of Alamannia, Carloman executed the Alamannic nobility and installed Frankish dukes. During the later and weaker years of the Carolingian Empire the Alemannic counts became almost independent, and a struggle for supremacy took place between them and the Bishopric of Constance. The chief family in Alamannia was that of the counts of Raetia Curiensis, who were sometimes called margraves, and one of whom, Burchard II, established the Duchy of Swabia, which was recognized by Henry the Fowler in 919 and became a stem duchy of the Holy Roman Empire.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALGIER_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Algier)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALGIER_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Algier) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALGIER_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Algeria is a sovereign state in North Africa on the Mediterranean coast. Its capital and most populous city is Algiers, located in the country's far north. With an area of 2,381,741 square kilometres (919,595 sq mi), Algeria is the tenth-largest country in the world, and the largest in Africa and the Arab world. Algeria is bordered to the northeast by Tunisia, to the east by Libya, to the west by Morocco, to the southwest by Western Sahara, Mauritania, and Mali, to the southeast by Niger, and to the north by the Mediterranean Sea. The country is a semi-presidential republic consisting of 48 provinces and 1,541 communes. Abdelaziz Bouteflika has been President since 1999. Ancient Algeria has known many empires and dynasties, including ancient Numidians, Phoenicians, Carthaginians, Romans, Vandals, Byzantines, Umayyads, Abbasids, Idrisid, Aghlabid, Rustamid, Fatimids, Zirid, Hammadids, Almoravids, Almohads, Ottomans and the French colonial empire. Berbers are generally considered to be the indigenous inhabitants of Algeria. Following the Arab conquest of North Africa, most indigenous inhabitants were Arabised; thus, although most Algerians are Berber in origin, most identify with Arab culture. En masse, Algerians are a mix of Berbers, Arabs, Turks and Syrians.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMIS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Amis)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMIS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Amis) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AMIS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Amis are an indigenous people of Taiwan. They speak Amis, an Austronesian language, and are one of the sixteen officially recognized peoples of Taiwanese aborigines. The traditional territory of the Amis includes the long, narrow valley between the Central Mountains and the Coastal Mountains (Huatung Valley), the Pacific coastal plain eastern to the Coastal Mountains and the Hengchun Peninsula. Family affairs including finance of the family are decided by the female householder, in the Ami tradition. Not many people may have seen the Ami, but many people may have heard the Ami. The musical project Enigma used an Ami chant in their song "Return to Innocence" in their second album, The Cross of Changes. This song was the theme song of the 1996 Atlanta Olympics. The main chorus of it was sung by Difang (Chinese name Kuo Ying-nan) and his wife, Igay (Chinese name Kuo Hsiu-chu), part of a Taiwanese aboriginal cultural performance group. Maison des Cultures du Monde recorded their singing while they were on tour and released a CD, which was subsequently used by Enigma (without mentioning the ethnic origin of the song and the singers). The case was later settled out of court. Ami singing is known for its complex contrapuntal polyphony.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANDAMANESE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Andamanese)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANDAMANESE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Andamanese) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANDAMANESE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Andamanese people are the various aboriginal inhabitants of the Andaman Islands, a district of India located in the southeastern part of the Bay of Bengal. The Andamanese resemble other Negrito groups in Southeast Asia. They are pygmies, and are the only modern people outside of certain parts of Sub-Saharan Africa with steatopygia. They lead a hunter-gatherer lifestyle, and appear to have lived in substantial isolation for thousands of years. The Andamanese are believed to be descended from the migrations which, about 70,000 years ago, brought the first modern humans out of Africa to the Andaman Islands.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANGOLAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Angolan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANGOLAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Angolan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANGOLAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Angola is a country in Southern Africa. It is the seventh-largest country in Africa, and is bordered by Namibia to the south, the Democratic Republic of the Congo to the north, Zambia to the east, and the Atlantic Ocean to west. The exclave province of Cabinda has borders with the Republic of the Congo and the Democratic Republic of the Congo. The capital and largest city is Luanda. Although its territory has been inhabited since the Paleolithic Era, modern Angola originates in Portuguese colonization, which began with, and was for centuries limited to, coastal settlements and trading posts established from the 16th century onwards. In the 19th century, European settlers slowly and hesitantly began to establish themselves in the interior. As a Portuguese colony, Angola did not encompass its present borders until the early 20th century, following resistance by groups such as the Cuamato, the Kwanyama and the Mbunda. Independence was achieved in 1975 after the protracted liberation war. That same year, Angola descended into an intense civil war that lasted until 2002. It has since become a relatively stable unitary presidential republic.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARAGON_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Aragon)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARAGON_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Aragon) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARAGON_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Aragon is an autonomous community in Spain, coextensive with the medieval Kingdom of Aragon. Located in northeastern Spain, the Aragonese autonomous community comprises three provinces (from north to south): Huesca, Zaragoza, and Teruel. Its capital is Zaragoza (also called Saragossa in English). The current Statute of Autonomy declares Aragon a nationality of Spain. Before Aragon came into being as a self-proclaimed kingdom in 1035, the northern counties of Jaca, Sobrarbe and Ribagorza were all counties and appanages suzerain to the Kingdom of Navarre. King Sancho set out on his will the primacy of Pamplona over all appanages (domains for the personal management of his offspring) including Castile, but his younger children set off on separate paths instead, establishing their own kingdoms. Ramiro I was for the first time named king of Aragon in 1035. Later, after his brother Gonzalo's death, he was also named king of Sobrarbe and Ribagorza in 1044. The new kingdom grew quickly, conquering territories from the Moorish kingdoms to the south.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AVARS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Avars)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AVARS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Avars) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AVARS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Avar Khaganate was a khanate established in the Pannonian Basin region in 567 by the Avars, a nomadic people of uncertain origins and ethno-linguistic affiliation. As the Göktürk Empire expanded westwards, the Khagan Bayan I led a group of Avars and Bulgars out of their reach, eventually settling around 568 in what used to be the Roman province of Pannonia. Seeking rich pastoral lands, the Avars initially demanded land south of the Danube River in present-day Bulgaria, but the Byzantines refused, using their contacts with the Göktürks as a threat against Avar aggression. The Avars turned their attention to the Carpathian Plain and to the natural defenses it afforded. However, the Carpathian basin was then occupied by the Gepids. In 567 the Avars formed an alliance with the Lombards-enemies of the Gepids-and together they destroyed much of the Gepid Kingdom. The Avars then persuaded the Lombards to move into northern Italy, an invasion that marked the last Germanic mass-movement in the Migration Period.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AVERNI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Averni)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AVERNI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Averni) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AVERNI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Arverni were a Celtic tribe. The tribe was located in what is today the French Auvergne region, which derives its name from the Arverni. One of the most powerful tribes in ancient Gaul, the Arverni opposed the Romans on several occasions. Their most important stronghold was Gergovia, near the present-day commune of Clermont-Ferrand. The Arverni are known to have had the most powerful tribal hegemony in Gaul during the 3rd and 2nd centuries BC under their kings, Luernios, and his son Bituitus. Their power was based on strong metallurgic technologies and weapons, elaborated and rich agriculture and catering, mining, trade and military dominance over their neighbours with tributes paid to them. But when Arvern king Bituitus was defeated by the Romans of Quintus and Gnaeus Ahenobarbus in 121 BC, their ascendancy passed to the Aedui and Sequani. Unlike the Allobroges, who were brought under direct Roman rule as a result of the Celtic wars of the 120s, the Arverni negotiated a treaty that preserved their independence, though their territory was diminished. No further Arvernian kings are mentioned in the historical record between 121 BC and 52 BC, and they may have adopted a constitutional oligarchy at this time. However, there were at least two later attempts to re-establish rulership by Celtillos and Vercingetorix. The defeat of the Arverni led directly to the establishment of Gallia Narbonensis as a Roman province, referred to simply as the Provincia so often that a part of the ancient region is today known as Provence.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZANDE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Azande)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZANDE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Azande) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AZANDE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Azande (plural of "Zande" in the Zande language) are an ethnic group of North Central Africa. They live primarily in the northeastern part of the Democratic Republic of the Congo, in South-central and Southwestern part of South Sudan, and in southeastern Central African Republic. The Congolese Azande live in Orientale Province, specifically along the Uele River; Isiro, Dungu, Kisangani and Dorima. The Central African Azande live in the districts of Rafaï, Bangasu and Obo. The Azande of South Sudan live in Central and Western Equatoria State, Yei, Maridi, Yambio and Tombura.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BAHRAIN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Bahrain)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BAHRAIN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Bahrain) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BAHRAIN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Bahrain is the site of the ancient Dilmun civilisation. It has been famed since antiquity for its pearl fisheries, which were considered the best in the world into the 19th century. Bahrain was one of the earliest areas to convert to Islam (AD 628). Following a period of Arab rule, Bahrain was occupied by the Portuguese in 1521, who in turn were expelled in 1602 by Shah Abbas I of the Safavid dynasty under the Persian Empire. In 1783, the Bani Utbah clan captured Bahrain from Nasr Al-Madhkur and it has since been ruled by the Al Khalifa royal family, with Ahmed al Fateh as Bahrain's first hakim. In the late 1800s, following successive treaties with the British, Bahrain became a protectorate of the United Kingdom. In 1971, Bahrain declared independence. Formerly a state, Bahrain was declared a Kingdom in 2002. Since early 2011, the country has experienced sustained protests and unrest inspired by the regional Arab Spring, particularly by the majority Shia population.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BACTRIC_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Bactric)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BACTRIC_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Bactric) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BACTRIC_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Greco-Bactrian Kingdom was - along with the Indo-Greek Kingdom - the easternmost part of the Hellenistic world, covering Bactria and Sogdiana in Central Asia from 250 to 125 BC. It was centered around the north of present-day Afghanistan. The expansion of the Greco-Bactrians into present-day northern India and Pakistan from 180 BC established the Indo-Greek Kingdom, which was to last until around 10 AD.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BANGLADESH_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Bangladesh)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BANGLADESH_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Bangladesh) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BANGLADESH_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Bangladesh is a country in South Asia, bordered by India and Myanmar, at the apex of the Bay of Bengal. It is separated from Nepal and Bhutan by the narrow Siliguri Corridor. It is the world's eighth most populous country and the ninety-second largest country by area, making it one of the most densely populated nations on Earth. The majority of the population are Muslims, followed by Hindus, with diverse Buddhist and Christian communities. The official language is Bengali, which is also spoken in the neighboring Indian states of West Bengal and Tripura. Dominated by the fertile Bengal delta, Bangladesh is rich in biodiversity and is home to the world's largest mangrove forest, a mountainous east and a 600 km (370 mi) coastline that has one of the world's longest beaches. The region was known to the ancient Greeks and Romans as Gangaridai. The mighty Ganges and Brahmaputra rivers connected Bengal to India and China, making the region a central entrepot of the historic Silk Road. During the Pala and Sena periods, the people of the land developed their own language, script, literature, music, art and architecture. Islam was established in the second millennium CE under the Delhi Sultanate, the Bengal Sultanate and the Mughal Empire. Annexed by the British East India Company in 1765, the region was a part of British-ruled India until the creation of Pakistan in 1947.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASHKIR_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Bashkir)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASHKIR_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Bashkir) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASHKIR_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Bashkirs are a Turkic people indigenous to Bashkortostan, extending on both sides of the Ural Mountains, on the place where Eastern Europe meets North Asia. Groups of Bashkirs also live in the Republic of Tatarstan, Perm Krai, Chelyabinsk, Orenburg, Tyumen, Sverdlovsk, Kurgan, Samara and Saratov Oblasts of Russia, as well as in Kazakhstan, Ukraine, Uzbekistan and other countries. Early records on the Bashkirs are found in medieval works by Sallam Tardzheman (9th century) and Ibn-Fadlan (10th century). Al-Balkhi (10th century) described Bashkirs as a people divided into two groups, one inhabiting the Southern Urals, the second group living on the Danube plain near the boundaries of Byzantium--therefore - given the geography and date - referring to either Danube Bulgars or Magyars. Ibn Rustah, a contemporary of Al Balkhi, observed that Bashkirs were an independent people occupying territories on both sides of the Ural mountain ridge between Volga, Kama, and Tobol Rivers and upstream of the Yaik river.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BATAVI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Batavi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BATAVI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Batavi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BATAVI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Batavi were an ancient Germanic tribe that lived around the modern Dutch Rhine delta in the area that the Romans called Batavia, from the second half of the first century BC to the third century AD. The name is also applied to several military units employed by the Romans that were originally raised among the Batavi. The tribal name, probably a derivation from batawjo ("good island", from Germanic bat- "good, excellent," which is also in the English "better," and awjo "island, land near water"), refers to the region's fertility, today known as the fruitbasket of the Netherlands (the Betuwe).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BATEK_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Batek)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BATEK_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Batek) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BATEK_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Batek (or Bateq) are an indigenous people (currently numbering about 1,516) who live in the rainforest of peninsular Malaysia. As a result of encroachment, they now primarily inhabit the Taman Negara National Park. They are nomadic hunters and gatherers, so the exact location of their settlements change within the general confines of the area that they inhabit. The common phrase used to refer to them, 'orang asli', signifies a diverse group of which the Batek tribe is a part. It means 'original people' in Malay and was probably first used to identify these people by Austronesian-speaking settlers who arrived by boat from the islands of Southeast Asia. The Batek people were first documented by Europeans in 1878, when explorer-naturalist Nicholai Miklukho-Maklai of Russia wrote about them.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BAVARIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Bavarian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BAVARIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Bavarian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BAVARIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Bavarians are an ethnographic group of Germans of the Bavaria region, a state within Germany. The group's dialect or speech is known as the Bavarian language, native to Altbayern ("Old Bavaria"), roughly the territory of the Electorate of Bavaria in the 17th century. Like the neighboring Swabians and Austrians, Bavarians are traditionally Catholic. In much of Altbayern, membership in the Catholic church remains above 70%, and the center-right Christian Social Union in Bavaria (successor of the Bavarian People's Party of 1919-1933) has traditionally been the strongest party in the Landtag, and also the party of all Ministers-President of Bavaria since 1946, with the single exception of Wilhelm Hoegner, 1954-1957.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEDOUIN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Bedouin)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEDOUIN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Bedouin) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEDOUIN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Bedouin are an Arab seminomadic group, descended from nomads who have historically inhabited the Arabian and Syrian deserts. Their name means "desert dwellers" in Arabic language. Their territory stretches from the vast deserts of North Africa to the rocky sands of the Middle East. They are traditionally divided into tribes, or clans)and share a common culture of herding camels and goats. While many Bedouins have abandoned their nomadic and tribal traditions for modern urban lifestyle, they retain traditional Bedouin culture with concepts of belonging to traditional music, poetry, dances (like Saas), and many other cultural practices. Urbanised Bedouins also organise cultural festivals, usually held several times a year, in which they gather with other Bedouins to partake in, and learn about, various Bedouin traditions - from poetry recitation and traditional sword dances, to classes teaching traditional tent knitting and playing traditional Bedouin musical instruments. Traditions like camel riding and camping in the deserts are also popular leisure activities for urbanised Bedouins who live within close proximity to deserts or other wilderness areas.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BELIZE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Belize)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BELIZE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Belize) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BELIZE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Belize is a country on the eastern coast of Central America. It is the only country in Central America whose official language is English, though Belizean Creole (Kriol) and Spanish are also commonly spoken. Belize is bordered on the north by Mexico, on the south and west by Guatemala, and on the east by the Caribbean Sea. Its mainland is about 290 km (180 mi) long and 110 km (68 mi) wide. In the early 19th century, the British sought greater control over the settlers, threatening to suspend the Public Meeting unless it observed the government's instructions to eliminate slavery outright. Slavery was abolished in the British Empire in 1833, but this did little to change working conditions for labourers in the Belize settlement.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BOLIVIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Bolivian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BOLIVIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Bolivian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BOLIVIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Bolivia is a landlocked country located in western-central South America. It is bordered to the north and east by Brazil, to the southeast by Paraguay, to the south by Argentina, to the southwest by Chile, and to the northwest by Peru. One-third of the country is the Andean mountain range, with its largest city and principal economic centers located in the Altiplano. Before Spanish colonization, the Andean region of Bolivia was part of the Inca Empire, while the northern and eastern lowlands were inhabited by independent tribes. Spanish conquistadors arriving from Cuzco and Asunción took control of the region in the 16th century. During most of the Spanish colonial period, Bolivia was known as Upper Peru and administered by the Royal Court of Charcas. Spain built its empire in great part upon the silver that was extracted from Bolivia's mines.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRETON_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Breton)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRETON_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Breton) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRETON_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Bretons are an ethnic group located in the region of Brittany in France. They trace much of their heritage to groups of Brittonic speakers who emigrated from southwestern Great Britain including Cornwall to avoid invading Germanic tribes. They also descend from the Gauls and in some parts from Vikings. They migrated in waves from the 3rd to 9th century (most heavily from 450 to 600) into the Armorican peninsula, which was subsequently named Brittany after them. A strong historical emigration has created a Breton diaspora within the French borders and in the overseas departments and territories of France; it is mainly established in the Paris area, where more than 1 million people claim Breton heritage. Many Breton families have also emigrated to the Americas, predominantly to Canada (mostly Québec and Atlantic Canada) and the United States. People from the region of Brittany were among the first white settlers to permanently settle the French West Indies, i.e. Guadeloupe and Martinique, where remnants of their culture can still be seen to this day. The only places outside of Brittany that still retain significant Breton customs are in Ile-de-France (mainly Le Quartier du Montparnasse in Paris), Le Havre and in Îles des Saintes, where a group of Breton families settled in the mid-17th century.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRITON_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Briton)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRITON_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Briton) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BRITON_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Britons were an ancient Celtic people who lived in Great Britain from the Iron Age through the Roman and Sub-Roman periods. They spoke a language that is now known as Common Brittonic. The earliest evidence of the existence of the Britons and their language in historical sources dates to the Iron Age. After the Roman conquest of Britain in the 1st century, a Romano-British culture emerged, and Latin and British Vulgar Latin coexisted with Brittonic. During and after the Roman era, the Britons lived throughout Britain south of the Firth of Forth. Their relationship with the Picts, who lived north of the Firth of Forth, has been the subject of much discussion, though most scholars accept that the Pictish language was related to Common Brittonic.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BURGUNDI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Burgundi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BURGUNDI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Burgundi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BURGUNDI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Burgundians were a large East Germanic or Vandal tribe, or group of tribes, who lived in the area of modern Poland in the time of the Roman empire. In the late Roman period, as the empire came under pressure from many such "barbarian" peoples, a powerful group of Burgundians and other Vandalic tribes moved westwards towards the Roman frontiers along the Rhine Valley, making them neighbors of the Franks, forming their kingdoms to the north, and the Suebic Alemanni who were settling to their south, also near the Rhine. They established themselves in Worms, but with Roman cooperation their descendants eventually established the Kingdom of the Burgundians much further south, and within the empire, in the western Alps region where modern Switzerland, France and Italy meet. This later became a component of the Frankish empire. The name of this Kingdom survives in the regional appellation, Burgundy, which is a region in modern France, representing only a part of that kingdom.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CAMBEBA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Cambeba)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CAMBEBA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Cambeba) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CAMBEBA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Cambeba people (also known as the Omagua, Umana, and Kambeba) are an indigenous people in Brazil's Amazon Basin, with territory extending into Peru. They speak the Omagua language. The Cambeba exist today in small numbers, but they were a populous, organized society in the late Pre-Columbian era. Their population suffered steep decline, mostly from infectious diseases, in the early years of the Columbian Exchange. The name Cambeba seems to have been applied by other neighboring tribes and refers to the Omagua custom of flattening their children's heads by binding a piece of wood to the forehead soon after birth. Omagua women would jeer at the women from other tribes, saying that their heads were "round like those of forest savages." In the 18th century, the Omaguas would point out to travelers that their flattened foreheads were a sign of cultural superiority over their neighbors, and for a long time they resisted abandoning this custom, even under missionary pressure.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CANARI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Canari)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CANARI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Canari) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CANARI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Canari are an indigenous ethnic group traditionally inhabiting the territory of the modern provinces of Azuay and Cañar in Ecuador. They are descended from the independent pre-Columbian tribal confederation of the same name. The historic people are particularly noted for their resistance against the Inca Empire. Eventually conquered by the Inca in the early 16th century shortly before the arrival of the Spanish, the Cañari later allied with the Spanish against the Inca. Today, the population of the Cañari, who include many mestizos, numbers in the thousands.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CAPAYAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Capayan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CAPAYAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Capayan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CAPAYAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Capayanes were an indigenous people nowadays extinct that lived in Argentine territory. They knew the technology of the thread, and spun the wool of guanaco and llamas. Also they knew the metallurgy of copper and gold. They constructed channels and irrigation ditches to water their farmlands. Their cultivars were maize, zapallo, potato and quínoa. They widely used ceramics, principally in the production of funeral urns, decorated geometrically with the colors black, red and white, known as Sanagasta style or Angualasto style.Their houses were of mud and adobe and were sometimes built at the foot of a great tree used as a roof. This technology of construction, still lasts in the Riojan zone of Vinchina.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARAL_SUPE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Caral_Supe)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARAL_SUPE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Caral-Supe) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARAL_SUPE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Norte Chico civilization (also Caral or Caral-Supe civilization) was a complex pre-Columbian society around 3500BC-1800BC that included as many as 30 major population centers in what is now the Norte Chico region of north-central coastal Peru. Since the early 21st century, it has been established as the oldest known civilization in the Americas. In archaeological nomenclature, Norte Chico is a pre-ceramic culture of the pre-Columbian Late Archaic; it completely lacked ceramics and apparently had almost no visual art. The most impressive achievement of the civilization was its monumental architecture, including large earthwork platform mounds and sunken circular plazas. Archaeological evidence suggests use of textile technology and, possibly, the worship of common god symbols, both of which recur in pre-Columbian Andean cultures. Sophisticated government is assumed to have been required to manage the ancient Norte Chico. Questions remain over its organization, particularly the influence of food resources on politics. Some scholars have suggested that Norte Chico was founded on seafood and maritime resources, rather than development of an agricultural cereal and crop surpluses, as has been considered essential to the rise of other ancient civilizations.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CATALONIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Catalonian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CATALONIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Catalonian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CATALONIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Catalans (Catalan, French and Occitan: catalans; Italian: catalani; Spanish: catalanes) are a Romance ethnic group formed by the people from, or with origins in, Catalonia, who form a nationality in northern Spain. The inhabitants of the adjacent portion of southern France (known in Catalonia proper as Catalunya Nord and in France as the Pays Catalan) are included in this definition. Also, Catalan is sometimes used to define people from Catalan Countries, which include other areas where the Catalan language is spoken. The area that now is known primarily as Catalonia was, as the rest of the Iberian Peninsula, invaded in 1500 BCE by Proto-Celtic Urnfield people who brought the rite of burning the dead. These Indo-European people were absorbed by the Iberians beginning in 600 BCE in a process that would not be complete until the fourth century BCE. These groups came under the rule of various invading groups starting with the Phoenicians and Carthaginians, who set up colonies along the coast, including Barcino (present-day Barcelona) itself. Following the Punic Wars, the Romans replaced the Carthaginians as the dominant power in the Iberian eastern coast, including parts of Catalonia, by 206 BCE. Rome established Latin as the official language and imparted a distinctly Roman culture upon the local population, which merged with Roman colonists from the Italian peninsula. An early precursor to the Catalan language began to develop from a local form of popular Latin before and during the collapse of the Roman Empire. Various Germanic tribes arrived following nearly six centuries of Roman rule, which had completely transformed the area into the Roman province of Tarraconensis. The Visigoths established themselves in the fifth century and would rule the area until 718 when Muslim Arabs and Berbers conquered the region and held it for close to a century. The Franks held back small Muslim raiding parties, which had penetrated virtually unchallenged as far as central France; Frankish suzerainty extended over much of present-day Catalonia. Larger wars with the Muslims began with the Spanish March which led to the beginnings of the Reconquista (Reconquest) by Catalan forces over most of Catalonia by the year 801. Barcelona became an important center for Christian forces in the Iberian Peninsula.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CELTIBERIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Celtiberian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CELTIBERIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Celtiberian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CELTIBERIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Celtiberians were Celtic-speaking people of the Iberian Peninsula in the final centuries BC. These tribes spoke the Celtiberian language. Extant tribal names include the Arevaci, Belli, Titti, Lusones, and Berones. Cassius Dio appears to imply that the Ebro river forms a demarcation between Celtiberians and other tribes. Archaeologically, the Celtiberians participated in the Hallstatt culture in what is now north-central Spain. The term Celtiberi appears in accounts by Diodorus Siculus, Appian and Martial who recognized intermarriage between Celts and Iberians after a period of continuous warfare, though Barry Cunliffe says "this has the ring of guesswork about it." Strabo just saw the Celtiberians as a branch of the Celti. Pliny the Elder thought that the original home of the Celts in Iberia was the territory of the Celtici in the south-west, on the grounds of an identity of sacred rites, language, and the names of cities.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHACHAPOYA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Chachapoya)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHACHAPOYA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Chachapoya) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHACHAPOYA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Chachapoyas, also called the Warriors of the Clouds, was a culture of Andean people living in the cloud forests of the Amazonas Region of present-day Peru. The Incas conquered their civilization shortly before the arrival of the Spanish in Peru. When the Spanish arrived in Peru in the 16th century, the Chachapoyas were one of the many nations ruled by the Inca Empire. Their incorporation into the Inca Empire had not been easy, due to their constant resistance to the Inca troops. Since the Incas and the Spanish conquistadors were the principal sources of information on the Chachapoyas, there is little first-hand or contrasting knowledge of the Chachapoyas. Writings by the major chroniclers of the time, such as El Inca Garcilaso de la Vega, were based on fragmentary second-hand accounts. Much of what we do know about the Chachapoyas culture is based on archaeological evidence from ruins, pottery, tombs and other artifacts. Spanish chronicler Pedro Cieza de León noted that, after their annexation to the Inca Empire, they adopted customs imposed by the Cuzco-based Inca.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHAVIN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Chavin)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHAVIN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Chavin) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHAVIN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Chavín culture is an extinct, prehistoric civilization, named for Chavín de Huantar, the principal archaeological site at which its artifacts have been found. The culture developed in the northern Andean highlands of Peru from 900 BC to 200 BC. It extended its influence to other civilizations along the coast. The Chavín people (whose name for themselves is unknown) were located in the Mosna Valley where the Mosna and Huachecsa rivers merge. This area is 3150 meters above sea level and encompasses the quechua, jalca, and puna life zones.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHECHENIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Chechenian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHECHENIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Chechenian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHECHENIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Chechens are a Caucasian ethnic group of the Nakh peoples originating in the North Caucasus region of Western Asia. They refer to themselves as Vainakhs (which means "our people" in Chechen) or Nokhchiy. Chechen and Ingush peoples are collectively known as the Vainakh. The majority of Chechens today live in the Chechen Republic, a subdivision of the Russian Federation. The isolated terrain of the Caucasus mountains and the strategic value outsiders have placed on the areas settled by Chechens has contributed much to the Chechen community ethos and helped shape its fiercely independent national character. Chechen society has traditionally been egalitarian and organized around many autonomous local clans, called teips.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHILEAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Chilean)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHILEAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Chilean) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHILEAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Chile is a South American country occupying a long, narrow strip of land between the Andes to the east and the Pacific Ocean to the west. It borders Peru to the north, Bolivia to the northeast, Argentina to the east, and the Drake Passage in the far south. Chilean territory includes the Pacific islands of Juan Fernandez, Salas y Gómez, Desventuradas, and Easter Island in Oceania. In 1520, while attempting to circumnavigate the globe, Ferdinand Magellan discovered the southern passage now named after him, the Strait of Magellan, thus becoming the first European to set foot on what is now Chile. The next Europeans to reach Chile were Diego de Almagro and his band of Spanish conquistadors, who came from Peru in 1535 seeking gold. The Spanish encountered various cultures that supported themselves principally through slash-and-burn agriculture and hunting. Cut off to the north by desert, to the south by the Mapuche, to the east by the Andes Mountains, and to the west by the ocean, Chile became one of the most centralized, homogeneous colonies in Spanish America. Serving as a sort of frontier garrison, the colony found itself with the mission of forestalling encroachment by both the Mapuche and Spain's European enemies, especially the British and the Dutch. Buccaneers and English adventurers menaced the colony in addition to the Mapuche, as was shown by Sir Francis Drake's 1578 raid on Valparaíso, the colony's principal port. Chile hosted one of the largest standing armies in the Americas, making it one of the most militarized of the Spanish possessions, as well as a drain on the treasury of the Viceroyalty of Peru.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHIMU_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Chimu)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHIMU_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Chimu) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHIMU_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Chimú were the residents of Chimor, with its capital at the city of Chan Chan, a large adobe city in the Moche Valley of present-day Trujillo city. The culture arose about 900 AD. The Inca ruler Tupac Inca Yupanqui led a campaign which conquered the Chimú around 1470 AD. This was just fifty years before the arrival of the Spanish in the region. Consequently, Spanish chroniclers were able to record accounts of Chimú culture from individuals who had lived before the Inca conquest. Similarly, archaeological evidence suggest Chimor grew out of the remnants of Moche culture; early Chimú pottery had some resemblance to that of the Moche. Their ceramics are all black, and their work in precious metals is very detailed and intricate.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHORESM_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Choresm)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHORESM_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Choresm) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHORESM_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>An East Iranian language, known as Khwarezmian language, was spoken in Khwarezm proper (i.e., the lower Amu Darya region) until soon after the Mongol invasion, when it was replaced by Turkic languages. It was closely related to Sogdian. Other than the astronomical terms used by the native Iranian Chorasmian speaker Al-Biruni, our other sources of Khwarezmian include Zamakhshari's Arabic-Persian-Khwarezmian dictionary and several legal texts that use Khwarezmian terms to explain certain legal concepts. The area of Khwarezm was under Afrighid and then Samanid control until the 10th century before it was conquered by the Ghaznavids. The Iranian Chorasmian language and culture felt the pressure of Turkic infiltration from northern Khwarezm southwards, leading to the disappearance of the original Iranian character of the province and its complete Turkicisation today, but Khwarezmian speech probably lasted in upper Khwarezm, the region round Hazarasp, till the end of the 8th/14th century.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CZECH_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Czech)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CZECH_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Czech) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CZECH_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Czech Republic is a landlocked country in Central Europe bordered by Germany to the west, Austria to the south, Slovakia to the southeast and Poland to the northeast. The capital and largest city, Prague, has over 1.2 million residents. The Czech Republic includes the historical territories of Bohemia, Moravia, and Czech Silesia. The Czech state was formed in the late 9th century as the Duchy of Bohemia under the Great Moravian Empire. After the fall of the Empire in 907, the centre of power transferred from Moravia to Bohemia under the Premyslids. In 1004, the duchy was formally recognized as part of the Holy Roman Empire, becoming the Kingdom of Bohemia in 1212, and reaching its greatest territorial extent in the 14th century. The King of Bohemia ruled not only Bohemia itself, but also other lands, which together formed the so-called Crown of Bohemia, and he had a vote in the election of the Holy Roman Emperor. In the Hussite wars of the 15th century driven by the Bohemian Reformation, the kingdom faced economic embargoes and defeated five crusades proclaimed by the leaders of the Roman Catholic Church and organized mainly by the emperor and princes of the Holy Roman Empire.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DACIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Dacian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DACIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Dacian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DACIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Dacians were an Indo-European people, part of or related to the Thracians. Dacians were the ancient inhabitants of Dacia, located in the area in and around the Carpathian Mountains and west of the Black Sea. This area includes the present-day countries of Romania and Moldova, as well as parts of Ukraine, Eastern Serbia, Northern Bulgaria, Slovakia, Hungary and Southern Poland. The Dacians spoke the Dacian language, believed to have been closely related to Thracian, but were somewhat culturally influenced by the neighbouring Scythians and by the Celtic invaders of the 4th century BC.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DAYAK_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Dayak)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DAYAK_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Dayak) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DAYAK_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Dayak or Dyak or Dayuh are the native people of Borneo. It is a loose term for over 200 riverine and hill-dwelling ethnic subgroups, located principally in the interior of Borneo, each with its own dialect, customs, laws, territory and culture, although common distinguishing traits are readily identifiable. Dayak languages are categorised as part of the Austronesian languages in Asia. The Dayak were animist in belief; however many converted to Islam and since the 19th century, mass conversion to Christianity. The Dayak people of Borneo possess an indigenous account of their history, mostly in oral literature, partly in writing in papan turai (wooden records), and partly in common cultural customary practices. Among prominent accounts of the origin of the Dayak people includes the mythical oral epic of "Tetek Tahtum" by the Ngaju Dayak of Central Kalimantan, it narrates the ancestors of the all Dayak people descended from the heavens before dispensing from the inland to the downstream shores of Borneo.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DRAVIDIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Dravidian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DRAVIDIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Dravidian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DRAVIDIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Historically the Sanskrit word "dravia" is used to denote geographical region of South India. And was devoid of any ethnic or linguistic identity. While in Prakrit, words such as "Damela", "Dameda", "Dhamila" and "Damila" which later evolved into "Tamila" could have been used to denote an ethnic identity. The largest-Dravidian ethnic groups are the Tamil People from Tamil Nadu, Puducherry Sri Lanka, Malaysia, Singapore and Indonesia, Kannada people from Karnataka, the Telugu people from Andhra Pradesh and Telangana, and the Malayalam people from Kerala and Tulu people from Karnataka. Ancient Dravidians were noted for their martial, religious and mercantile activities. Urbanisation and mercantile activity along the western and eastern coast of what is today Tamil Nadu and Kerala led to the development of four large political states Chola dynasty, Pandyan dynasty, Chera Dynasty and a number of smaller states warring amongst themselves for hegonomy and dominance over the region. Some of the greatest Dynasties in Indian history were established by partly the Dravidian people under the Satavahana dynasty, Rashtrakuta dynasty, Western Chalukya Empire and fully Vijayanagara Empire and kingdoms like Pandya. Among languages spoken today, Tamil is the oldest known Dravidian language with unbroken literary tradition since the 3rd century BC.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ECUADORIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Ecuadorian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ECUADORIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Ecuadorian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ECUADORIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Ecuador is a representative democratic republic in northwestern South America, bordered by Colombia on the north, Peru on the east and south, and the Pacific Ocean to the west. Ecuador also includes the Galapagos Islands in the Pacific, about 1,000 kilometres (620 mi) west of the mainland. What is now Ecuador was home to a variety of Amerindian groups that were gradually incorporated into the Inca Empire during the fifteenth century. The territory was colonized by Spain during the sixteenth century, achieving independence in 1820 as part of Gran Colombia, from which it emerged as its own sovereign state in 1830. The legacy of both empires is reflected in Ecuador's ethnically diverse population, with most of its 15.2 million people being mestizos, followed by large minorities of European, Amerindian, and African descendants.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ESTONIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Estonian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ESTONIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Estonian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ESTONIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Estonia is a country in the Baltic region of Northern Europe. It is bordered to the north by the Gulf of Finland, to the west by the Baltic Sea, to the south by Latvia (343 km), and to the east by Lake Peipus and Russia (338.6 km). Across the Baltic Sea lies Sweden in the west and Finland in the north. The territory of Estonia consists of a mainland and 2,222 islands and islets in the Baltic Sea, covering 45,339 km2 (17,505 sq mi) of land, and is influenced by a humid continental climate. Estonia is a democratic parliamentary republic divided into fifteen counties, with its capital and largest city being Tallinn. With a population of 1.3 million, it is one of the least-populous member states of the European Union, Eurozone, the North Atlantic Treaty Organisation, the OECD and the Schengen Area. Ethnic Estonians are Finnic people, and the official language, Estonian, is a Finno-Ugric language closely related to Finnish and the Sami languages, and distantly to Hungarian. A developed country with an advanced, high-income economy and high living standards, Estonia ranks very high in the Human Development Index, and performs favourably in measurements of economic freedom, civil liberties, education, and press freedom (third in the world in 2012). Estonia is often described as one of the most wired countries in Europe.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETRUSCAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Etruscan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETRUSCAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Etruscan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETRUSCAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Culture that is identifiably Etruscan developed in Italy after about 800 BC approximately over the range of the preceding Iron Age Villanovan culture. The latter gave way in the 7th century to a culture that was influenced by Hellenic, Magna Graecian, and Phoenician contacts. After 500 BC, the political destiny of Italy passed out of Etruscan hands. The latest mitochondrial DNA study (2013) shows that Etruscans appear to fall very close to a Neolithic population from Central Europe and to other Tuscan populations.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FATIMID_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Fatimid)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FATIMID_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Fatimid) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FATIMID_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Fatimid Caliphate was an Ismaili Shia Islamic caliphate that spanned a large area of North Africa, from the Red Sea in the east to the Atlantic Ocean in the west. The dynasty ruled across the Mediterranean coast of Africa and ultimately made Egypt the centre of the caliphate. At its height the caliphate included in addition to Egypt varying areas of the Maghreb, Sudan, Sicily, the Levant, and Hijaz. The Fatimids claimed descent from Fatima bint Muhammad, the daughter of Islamic prophet Muhammad. The Fatimids conquered North Africa and their Fatimid state took shape among the Kutama, in the West of the North African littoral, particularly Algeria, in 909 conquering Raqqada, the Aghlabid capital. In 921 the Fatimids established the Tunisian city of Mahdia as their new capital. In 948 they shifted their capital to Al-Mansuriya, near Kairouan in Tunisia. In 969 they conquered Egypt and established Cairo as the capital of their caliphate - Egypt became the political, cultural, and religious centre of their empire.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FLEMISH_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Flemish)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FLEMISH_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Flemish) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FLEMISH_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Flanders today normally refers to the Dutch-speaking northern portion of Belgium. It is one of the communities, regions and language areas of Belgium. The demonym associated with Flanders is Fleming, while the corresponding adjective is Flemish. The official capital of Flanders is Brussels, although Brussels itself has an independent regional government, and the government of Flanders only oversees some cultural aspects of Brussels life. Historically, the name referred to the County of Flanders (Flandria), which around 1000 CE stretched from the Strait of Dover to the Scheldt estuary. The only parts of historical Flanders situated within modern-day Flanders are the provinces West Flanders and East Flanders. Nevertheless, during the 19th and 20th centuries it became increasingly commonplace to use the term "Flanders" to refer to the entire Dutch-speaking part of Belgium, stretching all the way to the River Maas. In accordance with late 20th century Belgian state reforms the area was made into two political entities: the "Flemish Community" (Dutch: Vlaamse Gemeenschap) and the "Flemish Region" (Dutch: Vlaams Gewest). These entities were merged, although geographically the Flemish Community, which has a broader cultural mandate, covers Brussels, whereas the Flemish Region does not.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FUEGIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Fuegian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FUEGIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Fuegian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FUEGIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Fuegians are one of the three tribes of indigenous inhabitants of Tierra del Fuego, at the southern tip of South America. In English, the term originally referred to the Yaghan people of Tierra del Fuego. In Spanish, the term fueguino can refer to any person from the archipelago. The indigenous Fuegians belonged to several tribes including the Ona (Selk'nam), Haush (Manek'enk), Yaghan (Yamana), and Alacaluf (Kawésqar). All of these tribes except the Selk'nam lived exclusively in coastal areas. The Yaghans and the Alacaluf traveled by birchbark canoes around the islands of the archipelago, while the coast dwelling Haush did not. The Selk'nam lived in the interior of Isla Grande de Tierra del Fuego and lived mainly by hunting guanacos. The Ona were exclusively terrestrial hunter gathers that hunted terrestrial game such as guanacos, foxes, tuco-tucos and upland nesting birds as well as littoral fish and shellfish. The Fuegian peoples spoke several distinct languages: both the Kawésqar language and the Yaghan language are considered language isolates, while the Selk'nams spoke a Chon language like the Tehuelches on the mainland.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FURAWI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Furawi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FURAWI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Furawi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FURAWI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Fur are an ethnic group from western Sudan, principally inhabiting the region of Darfur where they are the largest tribe. They are a Western Sudanese people who practice sedentary herding and agriculture, mainly the cultivation of millet. Their society is a traditional one governed by village elders. They speak Fur, a Nilo-Saharan language, and are Muslims, having adopted the religion following the region's conquest by the Kanem-Bornu Empire during the Middle Ages. Some of them have come to speak Arabic in recent years. The name of Darfur comes from the name of this tribe and means "the home of the Fur". Most of the well known governors of Darfur such as Deriage and Tegani Seisei are members of the Fur. The Fur established the historical Sultanate of Darfur which governed Darfur until 1916 (see History of Darfur).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GALATIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Galatian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GALATIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Galatian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GALATIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Galatians were a Celtic people that dwelt mainly in the north central regions of Asia Minor or Anatolia, in what was known as Galatia, in today's Turkey. In their origin they were a part of the great Celtic migration which invaded Macedon, led by Brennus. The original Celts who settled in Galatia came through Thrace under the leadership of Leotarios and Leonnorios c. 278 BC. These Celts consisted mainly of three tribes, the Tectosages, the Trocmii, and the Tolistobogii, but they were also other minor tribes. They spoke a Celtic language, the Galatian language, which is sparsely attested. In the 1st century AD, many of them were Christianized by Paul the Apostle's missionary action. One of the Epistles of Paul the Apostle in the Bible (New Testament) is addressed to Galatian Christian communities (Epistle to the Galatians).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GAUCHO_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Gaucho)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GAUCHO_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Gaucho) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GAUCHO_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Gaucho is a word with several meanings. In its historical sense a gaucho was "A mestizo who, in the 18th and 19th centuries, inhabited Argentina, Uruguay and Rio Grande do Sul in Brazil". Today, in Argentina and Uruguay, a gaucho is simply "A country person, experienced in traditional cattle ranching work". Because historical gauchos were reputed to be brave, if unruly, the word is also applied metaphorically to mean "Noble, brave and generous", but also "One who is skilful in subtle tricks, crafty". In Portuguese the word gaúcho (note the accent) means "An inhabitant of the plains of Rio Grande do Sul or the pampas of Argentina descended from European man and [Amer]Indian woman who devotes himself to lassoing and raising cattle and horses".</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEORGIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Georgian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEORGIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Georgian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEORGIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Georgia is a country in Eurasia, located on the crossroads of Eastern Europe and West Asia. Nestled between the Greater Caucasus and Lesser Caucasus mountain ranges, it is bounded to the west by the Black Sea, to the north and northeast by Russia, to the south by Turkey and Armenia, and to the southeast by Azerbaijan. The capital and largest city is Tbilisi. During classical antiquity, several independent kingdoms became established in what is now Georgia. The kingdoms of Colchis and Iberia adopted Christianity as their state religion in the early 4th century, leading to the decline and elimination of previously dominant paganism, Zoroastrianism, and Mithraism. A unified Kingdom of Georgia reached the peak of its political and economic strength during the reign of King David IV and Queen Tamar from the late 11th to the early 13th centuries. Thereafter and throughout the early modern period Georgia became fractured and fell into decline due to the onslaught of various hostile empires, including the Mongols, the Ottoman Empire, and successive dynasties of Iran. In 1783, the eastern Georgian kingdom of Kartli-Kakheti forged an alliance with the Russian Empire, which led to the gradual annexation of Georgia by Russia starting in 1801. After a brief period of independence following the Russian Revolution of 1917, the first Georgian Republic was occupied by Soviet Russia in 1921, and absorbed into the Soviet Union as the Georgian Soviet Socialist Republic in 1922. After restoring its independence in 1991, post-communist Georgia suffered from civil unrest and an economic crisis for most of the 1990s. Following a peaceful change of power in the Rose Revolution of 2003, Georgia pursued a strongly pro-Western foreign policy, introducing a series of political and economic reforms.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GHURID_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Ghurid)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GHURID_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Ghurid) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GHURID_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Ghurids or Ghorids were a dynasty of Eastern Iranian descent (presumably Tajik, but the exact ethnic origin is uncertain), from the Ghor region of present-day central Afghanistan. The dynasty converted to Sunni Islam from Buddhism, after the conquest of Ghor by the Ghaznavid emperor Mahmud of Ghazni in 1011. Abu Ali ibn Muhammad (reigned 1011-1035) was the first Muslim king of the Ghurid dynasty to construct mosques and Islamic schools in Ghor. The dynasty overthrew the Ghaznavid Empire in 1186, when Sultan Mu'izz ad-Din Muhammad of Ghor conquered the last Ghaznavid capital of Lahore. At their zenith, the Ghurid empire encompassed Khorasan in the west and reached northern India as far as Bengal in the east. Their first capital was Firozkoh in Mandesh, Ghor, which was later replaced by Herat, while Ghazni and Lahore were used as additional capitals, especially during winters. The Ghurids were patrons of Persian culture and heritage.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GOKTURK_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Gokturk)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GOKTURK_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Gokturk) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GOKTURK_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Kok Turks were a nomadic confederation of Turkic peoples in medieval Inner Asia. The Köktürks, under the leadership of Bumin Qaghan (d. 552) and his sons, succeeded the Rouran Khaganate as the main power in the region and established the Turkic Khaganate, one of several nomadic dynasties which would shape the future geolocation, culture, and dominant beliefs of Turkic peoples. The Göktürk rulers originated from the Ashina clan, who were first attested to 439. The Book of Sui reports that in that year, on October 18, the Tuoba ruler Emperor Taiwu of Northern Wei overthrew Juqu Mujian of the Northern Liang in eastern Gansu, whence 500 Ashina families fled northwest to the Rouran Khaganate in the vicinity of Gaochang. Peter Benjamin Golden points out the possibility that the khaghans of the Turkic Khaganate, the Ashina, were themselves originally Indo-Europeans (possibly Iranian peoples) who later adopted the Turkic language but continued to use titles from their earlier Indo-European languages. German Turkologist W.-E. Scharlipp points out that many common terms in Turkic are Iranian in origin.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GOLDEN_HORDE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Golden Horde)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GOLDEN_HORDE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Golden Horde) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GOLDEN_HORDE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Golden Horde was a Mongol and later Turkicized khanate established in the 13th century and originating as the northwestern sector of the Mongol Empire. With the fragmentation of the Mongol Empire after 1259 it became a functionally separate khanate. It is also known as the Kipchak Khanate or as the Ulus of Jochi. After the death of Batu Khan (the founder of the Golden Horde) in 1255, his dynasty flourished for a full century, until 1359, though the intrigues of Nogai did instigate a partial civil war in the late 1290s. The Horde's military power peaked during the reign of Uzbeg (1312-1341), who adopted Islam. The territory of the Golden Horde at its peak included most of Eastern Europe from the Urals to the Danube River, and extended east deep into Siberia. In the south, the Golden Horde's lands bordered on the Black Sea, the Caucasus Mountains, and the territories of the Mongol dynasty known as the Ilkhanate.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUAM_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Guam)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUAM_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Guam) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUAM_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The original inhabitants of Guam and the Northern Mariana Islands are believed to be descendants of Austronesian people originating from Southeast Asia as early as 2000 BC.:16 They evolved into the Chamorro people. The ancient-Chamorro society had four classes: chamorri (chiefs), matua (upper class), achaot (middle class), and mana'chang (lower class).:20-21 The matua were located in the coastal villages, which meant they had the best access to fishing grounds, whereas the mana'chang were located in the interior of the island. Matua and mana'chang rarely communicated with each other, and matua often used achaot as intermediaries. There were also "makåhna" (similar to shamans), skilled in healing and medicine. Belief in spirits of ancient Chamorros called "Taotao mo'na" still persists as a remnant of pre-European culture. Their society was organized along matrilineal clans.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUANCHES_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Guanches)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUANCHES_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Guanches) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUANCHES_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Guanches (also: Guanchis or Guanchetos) were the Berber aboriginal inhabitants of the Canary Islands. It is believed that they migrated to the archipelago around 1000 BC or perhaps earlier. While it is generally considered that the Guanches no longer exist as a distinct ethnicity, traces of their culture can still be found intermixed within Canarian customs and traditions, such as Silbo, the whistled language of La Gomera Island. The Guanches were the only native people known to have lived in the Macaronesian region before the arrival of Europeans, as there is no evidence that the Azores, Cape Verde, Madeira and the Savage Islands were inhabited before that time. After the Spanish conquest of the Canaries, they were ethnically and culturally absorbed by Spanish settlers, although elements of their culture survive to this day.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUARANI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Guarani)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUARANI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Guarani) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUARANI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Guarani are a group of culturally related indigenous peoples of South America. They are distinguished from the related Tupí by their use of the Guaraní language. The traditional range of the Guaraní people is in what is now Paraguay between the Uruguay River and lower Paraguay River, the Misiones Province of Argentina, southern Brazil once as far as north as Rio de Janeiro, and parts of Uruguay and Bolivia. Although their demographic dominance of the region has been reduced by European colonisation and the commensurate rise of mestizos, there are contemporary Guaraní populations in these areas. Most notably, the Guarani language, still widely spoken across traditional Guaraní homelands, is one of the two official languages in Paraguay, the other one being Spanish. The language was once looked down upon by the upper and middle classes, but it is now often regarded with pride and serves as a symbol of national distinctiveness. The Paraguayan population learns Guaraní both informally from social interaction and formally in public schools. In modern Spanish Guaraní is also applied to refer to any Paraguayan national in the same way that the French are sometimes called Gauls.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUATEMALA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Guatemala)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUATEMALA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Guatemala) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUATEMALA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Guatemala is a country in Central America bordered by Mexico to the north and west, the Pacific Ocean to the southwest, Belize to the northeast, the Caribbean to the east, Honduras to the east and El Salvador to the southeast. With an estimated population of around 15.8 million, it is the most populous state in Central America. The territory of modern Guatemala once formed the core of the Mayan civilization, which extended across Mesoamerica. Most of the country was conquered by the Spanish in the 16th century, becoming part of the viceroyalty of New Spain. Guatemala attained independence in 1821 as part of the Federal Republic of Central America, which dissolved in 1841. From the mid to late 19th century, Guatemala experienced chronic instability and civil strife. Beginning in the early 20th century, it was ruled by a series of dictators backed by the United Fruit Company and the United States government. In 1944, authoritarian leader Jorge Ubico was overthrown by a pro-democratic military coup, initiating a decade-long revolution that led to sweeping social and economic reforms. A U.S.-backed military coup in 1954 ended the revolution and installed a dictatorship. From 1960 to 1996, Guatemala endured a bloody civil war fought between the U.S.-backed government and leftist rebels, which included massacres of the Mayan population perpetrated by the military. Since a United Nations-negotiated peace accord, Guatemala has witnessed both economic growth and successful democratic elections, though it continues to struggle with high rates of poverty, crime, drug trade, and instability.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUYANA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Guyana)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUYANA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Guyana) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUYANA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Guyana is a sovereign state on the northern mainland of South America. It is bordered by the Atlantic Ocean to the north, Brazil to the south and southwest, Suriname to the east and Venezuela to the west. With 215,000 square kilometres (83,000 sq mi), Guyana is the fourth-smallest country on mainland South America after Uruguay and Suriname and French Guiana. The region known as "Guyana" comprised the large shield landmass north of the Amazon River and east of the Orinoco River known as the "Land of many waters". Originally inhabited by several indigenous groups, Guyana was settled by the Dutch before coming under British control in the late 18th century. It was governed as the plantation economy of British Guiana until independence in 1966, and officially became a republic within the British Commonwealth of Nations in 1970. The legacy of British rule is reflected in the country's diverse population, which includes Indian, African, Amerindian, and multiracial groups.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HELVETII_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Helvetii)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HELVETII_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Helvetii) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HELVETII_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Helvetiii were a Gallic tribe or tribal confederation occupying most of the Swiss plateau at the time of their contact with the Roman Republic in the 1st century BC. According to Julius Caesar, the Helvetiians were divided into four subgroups or pagi. Of these Caesar only names the Verbigeni and the Tigurini, while Posidonius mentions the Tigurini and the Tougeni. They feature prominently in the Commentaries on the Gallic War, with their failed migration attempt to southwestern Gaul (58 BC) serving as a catalyst for Caesar's conquest of Gaul.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HEMUDU_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Hemudu)</English>
		<German>
			<Text>Kultur Hemudu:Kultur Hemudu:Kultur Hemudu:Kultur Hemudu</Text>
			<Gender>Female</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HEMUDU_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Hemudu) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>		
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HEMUDU_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Hemudu culture (5500 BC to 3300 BC) was a Neolithic culture that flourished just south of the Hangzhou Bay in Jiangnan in modern Yuyao, Zhejiang, China. The culture may be divided into an early and late phases, before and after 4000 BC respectively. The site at Hemudu, 22 km north-west of Ningbo, was discovered in 1973. Hemudu sites were also discovered on the islands of Zhoushan. Hemudu are said to have differed physically from inhabitants of the Yellow River sites to the north. Scholars view the Hemudu Culture as a source of the proto-Austronesian cultures.</English>
		<German>Die [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Hemudu[COLOR_REVERT]-Kultur hatte ihre Blütezeit von etwa 5000 bis 3300 v.Chr. Sie ist nach dem Dorf Hemudu benannt, in dem 1973 eine Vielzahl an Relikten entdeckt wurden. Diese bestätigten die Vermutung, dass sich die chinesische Zivilisation aus den neolithischen Kulturen im Unterlauf des Jangtsekiang entwickelt hat. Belegt ist, dass die Hemudu bereits Nassreis anbauten, Seidenraupen züchteten und Lack gewinnen und verarbeiten konnten. Die Hemudu stellten Gegenstände aus Knochen und Keramik her und lebten in Holzhäusern. Man vermutet, dass sie später durch Überschwemmung, die Versalzung des Bodens oder durch die Änderung des Flussbetts des Yaojiang gezwungen waren, ihre angestammten Gebiete zu verlassen.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HIMYARITE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Himyarite)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HIMYARITE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Himyarite) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HIMYARITE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Himyarite Kingdom or Himyar (Flourished 110 BCE-520s CE), historically referred to as the Homerite Kingdom by the Greeks and the Romans, was a kingdom in ancient Yemen. Established in 110 BCE, it took as its capital the modern-day city of Sana'a after the ancient city of Zafar. The Kingdom conquered neighbouring Saba' (Sheba) in c. 25 BCE (for the first time), Qataban in c. 200 CE, and Haramaut c. 300 CE. Its political fortunes relative to Saba' changed frequently until it finally conquered the Sabaean Kingdom around 280 CE. Himyar then endured until it finally fell to Christian invaders in 525 CE.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HONGKONG_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Hong Kong)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HONGKONG_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Hong Kong) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HONGKONG_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Hong Kong is an autonomous territory on the southern coast of China at the Pearl River Estuary and the South China Sea. Hong Kong is known for its skyline and deep natural harbour. It has a land area of 1104 km2 and shares its northern border with Guangdong Province of Mainland China. With around 7.2 million inhabitants of various nationalities,[note 1] Hong Kong is one of the world's most densely populated metropolises. After the First Opium War (1839-42), Hong Kong became a British colony with the perpetual cession of Hong Kong Island, followed by Kowloon Peninsula in 1860 and a 99-year lease of the New Territories from 1898. Hong Kong remained under British control for about a century until the Second World War, when Japan occupied the colony from December 1941 to August 1945. After the Surrender of Japan, the British resumed control. In the 1980s, negotiations between the United Kingdom and China resulted in the 1984 Sino-British Joint Declaration, which provided for the transfer of sovereignty of Hong Kong on 30 June 1997. The territory became a special administrative region of China with a high degree of autonomy on 1 July 1997 under the principle of one country, two systems. Disputes over the perceived misapplication of this principle have contributed to popular protests, including the 2014 Umbrella Revolution.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOPEWELL_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Hopewell)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOPEWELL_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Hopewell) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOPEWELL_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Hopewell tradition (also called the Hopewell culture) describes the common aspects of the Native American culture that flourished along rivers in the northeastern and midwestern United States from 200 BC to 500 AD, in the Middle Woodland period. The Hopewell tradition was not a single culture or society, but a widely dispersed set of related populations. They were connected by a common network of trade routes, known as the Hopewell Exchange System. At its greatest extent, the Hopewell exchange system ran from the Southeastern United States as far south as the Crystal River Indian Mounds into the southeastern Canadian shores of Lake Ontario up north. Within this area societies participated in a high degree of exchange with the highest amount of activity along waterways. The Hopewell exchange system received materials from all over what is now the United States. Most of the items traded were exotic materials and were received by people living in the major trading and manufacturing areas. These people then converted the materials into products and exported them through local and regional exchange networks. The objects created by the Hopewell exchange system spread far and wide and have been seen in many burials outside the Midwest.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HURRIANS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Hurrians)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HURRIANS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Hurrians) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HURRIANS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Hurrians also called Hari, Khurrites, Hourri, Churri, Hurri or Hurriter, were a people of the Bronze Age Near East. They spoke a Hurro-Urartian language called Hurrian, and lived in Anatolia and Northern Mesopotamia. The largest and most influential Hurrian nation was the multi-ethnic kingdom of Mitanni, the Mitanni perhaps being Indo-European speakers who formed a ruling class over the Hurrians. The population of the Indo-European-speaking Hittite Empire in Anatolia included a large population of Hurrians, and there is significant Hurrian influence in Hittite mythology. By the Early Iron Age, the Hurrians had been assimilated with other peoples, except perhaps in the kingdom of Urartu. According to a hypothesis by I.M. Diakonoff and S. Starostin, the Hurrian and Urartian languages are related to the Northeast Caucasian languages while present day Armenians are an amalgam of both Hurrians and Urartians.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HYKSOSI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Hyksosi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HYKSOSI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Hyksosi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HYKSOSI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Hyksos ere a people of mixed origins from Western Asia, who settled in the eastern Nile Delta, some time before 1650 BCE. The arrival of the Hyksos led to the end of the Thirteenth Dynasty of Egypt and initiated the Second Intermediate Period. In the context of Ancient Egypt, the term "Asiatic" - which is often used of the Hyksos - may refer to any people native to areas east of Egypt. Immigration by Canaanite populations preceded the Hyksos. Canaanites first appeared in Egypt towards the end of the 12th Dynasty c. 1800 BC, and either around that time or c. 1720 BC, established an independent realm in the eastern Nile Delta. The Canaanite rulers of the Delta, regrouped in the 14th Dynasty, coexisted with the Egyptian 13th Dynasty, based in Itjtawy. The power of the 13th and 14th Dynasties progressively waned, perhaps due to famine and plague,</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ILLYRIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Illyrian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ILLYRIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Illyrian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ILLYRIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>In classical antiquity, Illyria (Latin: Illyria, see also Illyricum) was a region in the western part of the Balkan Peninsula inhabited by the Illyrians. The prehistory of Illyria and the Illyrians is known from archaeological evidence. The Romans conquered the region in 168 BC in the aftermath of the Illyrian Wars. The Roman term Illyris (distinct from Illyria) was sometimes used to define an area north of the Aous valley, most notably Illyris proper. The earliest recorded Illyrian kingdom was that of the Enchele in the 8th century BC. The era in which we observe other Illyrian kingdoms begins approximately at 400 BC and ends at 167 BC. The Autariatae under Pleurias (337 BC) were considered to have been a kingdom. The Kingdom of the Ardiaei began at 230 BC and ended at 167 BC. The most notable Illyrian kingdoms and dynasties were those of Bardyllis of the Dardani and of Agron of the Ardiaei who created the last and best-known Illyrian kingdom. Agron ruled over the Ardiaei and had extended his rule to other tribes as well. As for the Dardanians, they always had separate domains from the rest of the Illyrians.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ILOCANO_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Ilocano)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ILOCANO_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Ilocano) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ILOCANO_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Ilokanos (Ilocano: Tattao a Iloko) or Iloko people are the third largest Filipino ethnolinguistic group. There are over 40 dialects of the Ilokano language and their speakers reside within the Ilocos region in the Philippines. Ilocandia is the term given to the traditional homeland of the Ilokano people. From the original western strip of Northern Luzon, Ilocandia has spread throughout the Cordillera Administrative Region, Cagayan Valley and some parts of Central Luzon.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Indus)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Indus) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The 'Indus Valley Civilization (IVC) was a Bronze Age civilisation (3300-1300 BCE; mature period 2600-1900 BCE) extending from what today is northeast Afghanistan to Pakistan and northwest India (see map). Along with Ancient Egypt and Mesopotamia it was one of three early civilisations of the Old World, and of the three the most widespread. It flourished in the basins of the Indus River, one of the major rivers of Asia, and along a system of perennial, mostly monsoon-fed, rivers that once coursed in the vicinity of the seasonal Ghaggar-Hakra river in northwest India and eastern Pakistan. Aridification of this region during the 3rd millennium BCE may have been the initial spur for the urbanisation associated with the civilisation, but eventually also reduced the water supply enough to cause the civilisation's demise, and to scatter its population eastward.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRANIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Iranian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRANIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Iranian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRANIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Iran is a sovereign state in Western Asia. It is bordered to the northwest by Armenia, the de facto Nagorno-Karabakh Republic, and Azerbaijan; to the north by Kazakhstan and Russia across the Caspian Sea; to the northeast by Turkmenistan; to the east by Afghanistan and Pakistan; to the south by the Persian Gulf and the Gulf of Oman; and to the west by Turkey and Iraq. Comprising a land area of 1,648,195 km2 (636,372 sq mi), it is the second-largest country in the Middle East and the 18th-largest in the world. With 78.4 million inhabitants, Iran is the world's 17th-most-populous country. It is the only country that has both a Caspian Sea and an Indian Ocean coastline. Iran has long been of geostrategic importance because of its central location in Eurasia and Western Asia, and its proximity to the Strait of Hormuz. Iran is home to one of the world's oldest civilizations, beginning with the formation of the Proto-Elamite and Elamite kingdoms in 3200-2800 BC. The Iranian Medes unified the area into the first of many empires in 625 BC, after which it became the dominant cultural and political power in the region. Iran reached the pinnacle of its power during the Achaemenid Empire founded by Cyrus the Great in 550 BC, which at its greatest extent comprised major portions of the ancient world, stretching from parts of the Balkans (Thrace-Macedonia, Bulgaria-Paeonia) and Eastern Europe proper in the west, to the Indus Valley in the east, making it the largest empire the world had yet seen. The empire collapsed in 330 BC following the conquests of Alexander the Great. The Parthian Empire emerged from the ashes and was succeeded by the Sassanid Dynasty in 224 AD, under which Iran again became one of the leading powers in the world, along with the Roman-Byzantine Empire, for a period of more than four centuries.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRAQUI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Iraqui)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRAQUI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Iraqui) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRAQUI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Iraq is a country in Western Asia. The country borders Turkey to the north, Iran to the east, Kuwait to the southeast, Saudi Arabia to the south, Jordan to the southwest, and Syria to the west. The southern part of Iraq is within the Arabian Peninsula. The capital, Baghdad, is in the centre of the country and its largest city. The largest ethnic groups in Iraq are Arabs and Kurds. Other ethnic groups include Assyrians, Turkmen, Shabakis, Yazidis, Armenians, Mandeans, Circassians, and Kawliya. Around 95% of the country's 36 million citizens are Shia or Sunni Muslims, with Christianity, Yarsan, Yezidism, and Mandeanism also present. Iraq has a narrow section of coastline measuring 58 km (36 miles) on the northern Persian Gulf and its territory encompasses the Mesopotamian Alluvial Plain, the northwestern end of the Zagros mountain range, and the eastern part of the Syrian Desert. Two major rivers, the Tigris and Euphrates, run south through the centre of Iraq and flow into the Shatt al-Arab near the Persian Gulf. These rivers provide Iraq with significant amounts of fertile land.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAVANESE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Javanese)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAVANESE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Javanese) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JAVANESE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Javanese are an ethnic group native to the Indonesian island of Java. With approximately 100 million people (as of 2011), they form the largest ethnic group in Indonesia. They are predominantly located in the central to eastern parts of the island. There are also significant numbers of people of Javanese descent in most Provinces of Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, Suriname, South Africa and the Netherlands. The Javanese ethnic group has many sub-groups, such as the Mataram, Cirebonese, Osing, Tenggerese, Boyanese, Samin, Naganese, Banyumasan, etc. A majority of the Javanese people identify themselves as Muslims, with a minority identifying as Christians and Hindus. However, Javanese civilisation has been influenced by more than a millennium of interactions between the native animism Kejawen and the Indian Hindu-Buddhist culture, and this influence is still visible in Javanese history, culture, traditions and art forms.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JUTES_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Jutes)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JUTES_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Jutes) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JUTES_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Jutes were a Germanic people. According to Bede, the Jutes were one of the three most powerful Germanic peoples of their time in the Nordic Iron Age, the other two being the Saxons and the Angles. The Jutes are believed to have originated from the Jutland Peninsula (called Iutum in Latin) and part of the North Frisian coast. In present times the Jutlandic Peninsula consists of the mainland of Denmark and Southern Schleswig in Germany. North Frisia is part of Germany as well. The Jutes invaded and settled in southern Britain in the late 4th century during the Age of Migrations, as part of a larger wave of Germanic settlement in the British Isles.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KENYAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Kenyan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KENYAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Kenyan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KENYAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Kenya is a country in Africa and a founding member of the East African Community (EAC). Its capital and largest city is Nairobi. Kenya's territory lies on the equator and overlies the East African Rift covering a diverse and expansive terrain that extends roughly from Lake Victoria to Lake Turkana (formerly called Lake Rudolf) and further south-east to the Indian Ocean. It is bordered by Tanzania to the south, Uganda to the west, South Sudan to the north-west, Ethiopia to the north and Somalia to the north-east. Kenya covers 581,309 km2 (224,445 sq mi), and had a population of approximately 45 million people in July 2014. The African Great Lakes region, which Kenya is a part of, has been inhabited by humans since the Lower Paleolithic period. By the first millennium AD, the Bantu expansion had reached the area from West-Central Africa. The borders of the modern state consequently comprise the crossroads of the Niger-Congo, Nilo-Saharan and Afroasiatic areas of the continent, representing most major ethnolinguistic groups found in Africa. Bantu and Nilotic populations together constitute around 97% of the nation's residents. European and Arab presence in coastal Mombasa dates to the Early Modern period; European exploration of the interior began in the 19th century. The British Empire established the East Africa Protectorate in 1895, which starting in 1920 gave way to the Kenya Colony. Kenya obtained independence in December 1963. Following a referendum in August 2010 and adoption of a new constitution, Kenya is now divided into 47 semi-autonomous counties, governed by elected governors.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KHAZAK_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Kazakh)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KHAZAK_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Kazakh) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KHAZAK_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Kazakhs are a Turkic people who mainly inhabit the northern parts of Central Asia (largely Kazakhstan, but also found in parts of Uzbekistan, China, Russia and Mongolia). Kazakh identity is of medieval origin and was strongly shaped by the foundation of the Kazakh Khanate between 1456 and 1465, when several tribes under the rule of the sultans Zhanibek and Kerey departed from the Khanate of Abu'l-Khayr Khan. Most modern Kazakhs are either irreligious or nondenominational Muslims. The Kazakhs are descendants of the Turkic and medieval Mongol tribes - Argyns, Dughlats, Naimans, Jalairs, Khazars, Qarluqs; and of the Kipchaks and Cumans, and other tribes such as the Huns, and ancient Iranian nomads like the Sarmatians, Saka and Scythians from East Europe populated the territory between Siberia and the Black Sea and remained in Central Asia and Eastern Europe when the nomadic groups started to invade and conquer the area between the 5th and 13th centuries AD.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KHAZARS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Khazars)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KHAZARS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Khazars) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KHAZARS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Khazars were a semi-nomadic Turkic people, who created what for its duration was the most powerful polity to emerge from the breakup of the western Turkish steppe empire, known as the Khazar Khanate or Khazaria. Astride a major artery of commerce between northern Europe and southwestern Asia, Khazaria became one of the foremost trading emporia of the medieval world, commanding the western marches of the Silk Road and played a key commercial role as a crossroad between China, the Middle East and Kievan Rus'. For some three centuries (c. 650-965) the Khazars dominated the vast area extending from the Volga-Don steppes to the eastern Crimea and the northern Caucasus.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KHITAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Khitan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KHITAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Khitan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KHITAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Khitan people were a nomadic people originally from Mongolia, Manchuria (or Northeast China), and the Russian Far East from the 4th century that spoke a language distantly related to the Mongolic languages. As the Liao dynasty, they dominated a vast area north of and including parts of China, but left few relics that have survived until today. After the fall of the Liao dynasty in 1125 following the Jurchen invasion, many Khitans followed Yelu Dashi's group westward to establish the Qara Khitai or Western Liao dynasty in Central Asia, which lasted several decades before being consumed by the Mongol Empire in 1218.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KILLKE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Killke)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KILLKE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Killke) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KILLKE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Killke culture occupied the South American region around Cusco, Peru from 900 to 1200 AD, prior to the arrival of the Incas in the 13th century. Killke culture flourished in highland Peru in the Late Intermediate Period around what is now Cusco. They built the massive fortress, Saksaywaman, during the 12th century. Later, the fortress was used by the Inca, following their occupation of the region. In 2007, excavations uncovered a temple on the edge of the fortress, indicating religious as well as military use of the facility. New excavations began in June 2007 that will continue to 2012. On March 13, 2008, archaeologists discovered the ruins of another ancient temple, roadway, and irrigation systems at Saksaywaman, overlooking the Inca capital of Cusco. Part of the temple was destroyed by dynamite blasts in the early 20th century, when the site was used as a stone quarry.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KITARA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Kitara)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KITARA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Kitara) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KITARA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>According to oral tradition in the area of the Great Lakes of Africa, the Empire of Kitara (also known as Bachwezi, Bacwezi, or Chwezi empire) was ruled into the 16th century by a dynasty known as the Bachwezi (or Chwezi), successors of the Batembuzi Dynasty. The sphere of influence of this empire would have included what corresponds to modern Uganda, northern Tanzania, eastern Congo (DRC), Rwanda and Burundi. There is no evidence of the historicity of such an empire, and scholarly opinion is sceptical, but the tradition has been important in the political history of the East African Community, especially in the Buganda kingdom of the 19th century, whose kings sought legitimacy by declaring themselves the heirs of the Kitara empire.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOGI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Kogi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOGI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Kogi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOGI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Kogi or Cogui or Kagaba, meaning "jaguar" in the Kogi language, are an indigenous ethnic group that lives in the Sierra Nevada de Santa Marta in Colombia. Their civilization has continued since the Pre-Columbian era. The Kogi are descendants of the Tairona culture, which flourished before the times of the Spanish conquest. The Tairona were an advanced civilization which built many stone structures and pathways in the jungles. They made many gold objects which they would hang from trees and around their necks. They lived not much differently from modern day Kogi. Before the Spanish conquistadors arrived, the Tairona were forced to move into the highlands when the Caribs invaded around 1000 CE. The decision to flee to the mountains proved beneficial and strategic by the time the Spanish entered modern-day Colombia in the 15th century. In 1498, the Spanish arrived in Northern Colombia where they began to enslave indigenous groups. Threatened by dogs and soldiers alike, the Tairona remained in isolation. Regardless, many priests were hanged, women were stolen and raped, and children where forced to accept Spanish education. Later, missionaries came and also began to influence their way of life, building chapels and churches amidst their villages to train and convert the locals. In the years since, the Kogi have remained in their home in the mountains, which allows them to escape the worst effects of colonization and aids them in preserving their traditional way of life </English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KURDISH_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Kurdish)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KURDISH_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Kurdish) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KURDISH_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Kurds are an ethnic group in the Middle East, mostly inhabiting a contiguous area spanning adjacent parts of eastern and southeastern Turkey (Northern Kurdistan), western Iran (Eastern or Iranian Kurdistan), northern Iraq (Southern or Iraqi Kurdistan), and northern Syria (Western Kurdistan or Rojava). The Kurds have ethnically diverse origins. They are culturally and linguistically closely related to the Iranian peoples and, as a result, are often themselves classified as an Iranian people. Kurdish nationalists claim that the Kurds are descended from the Hurrians and the Medes, (the latter being another Iranian people) and the claimed Median descent is reflected in the words of the Kurdish national anthem: "we are the children of the Medes and Kai Khosrow". The Kurdish languages form a subgroup of the Northwestern Iranian languages.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KUSH_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Kush)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KUSH_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Kush) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KUSH_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Kingdom of Kush or Kush was an ancient African kingdom situated on the confluences of the Blue Nile, White Nile and River Atbara in what is now the Republic of Sudan. Established after the Bronze Age collapse and the disintegration of the New Kingdom of Egypt, it was centered at Napata in its early phase. After King Kashta ("the Kushite") invaded Egypt in the 8th century BC, the Kushite kings ruled as pharaohs of the Twenty-fifth dynasty of Egypt for a century, until they were expelled by the Assyrians under the rule of Esarhaddon. During Classical antiquity, the Kushite imperial capital was at Meroe. In early Greek geography, the Meroitic kingdom was known as Ethiopia. The Kushite kingdom with its capital at Meroe persisted until the 4th century AD, when it weakened and disintegrated due to internal rebellion.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KUSHAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Kushan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KUSHAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Kushan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KUSHAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Kushan Empire was a syncretic empire, formed by Yuezhi, in the Bactrian territories in the early 1st century. It spread to encompass much of Afghanistan, and then the northern parts of the Indian subcontinent at least as far as Saketa and Sarnath near Varanasi (Benares), where inscriptions have been found dating to the era of the Kushan emperor Kanishka the Great. Emperor Kanishka was a great patron of Buddhism; however, as Kushans expanded southward, the deities of theirlater coinage came to reflect its new Hindu majority.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KUWAIT_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Kuwait)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KUWAIT_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Kuwait) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KUWAIT_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Kuwait is a country in Western Asia. Situated in the northern edge of Eastern Arabia at the tip of the Persian Gulf, it shares borders with Iraq and Saudi Arabia. As of 2014, Kuwait has a population of 4.2 million people; 1.3 million are Kuwaitis and 2.9 million are expatriates. Oil reserves were discovered in 1938. From 1946 to 1982, the country underwent large-scale modernization. In the 1980s, Kuwait experienced a period of geopolitical instability and an economic crisis following the stock market crash. In 1990, Kuwait was invaded by Iraq. The Iraqi occupation came to an end in 1991 after military intervention by United States-led forces. At the end of the war, there were extensive efforts to revive the economy and rebuild national infrastructure. Kuwait is a constitutional emirate with a high income economy backed by the world's sixth largest oil reserves. The Kuwaiti dinar is the highest valued currency in the world. According to the World Bank, the country has the fourth highest per capita income in the world. The constitution was promulgated in 1962, making Kuwait the most politically progressive country in the region. In recent years, political instability has hindered the country's economic development.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LATVIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Latvian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LATVIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Latvian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LATVIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Latvia is a country in the Baltic region of Northern Europe, one of the three Baltic states. It is bordered by Estonia to the north, Lithuania to the south, Russia to the east, and Belarus to the southeast, as well as a maritime border to the west alongside Sweden. Latvia has 2,070,371 inhabitants and a territory of 64,589 km2 (24,938 sq mi). The country has a temperate seasonal climate. Latvia is a democratic parliamentary republic established in 1918. The capital city is Riga, the European Capital of Culture 2014. Latvian is the official language. Latvia is a unitary state, divided into 118 administrative divisions, of which 109 are municipalities and 9 are cities. Latvians and Livs are the indigenous people of Latvia. Latvian is an Indo-European language; it and Lithuanian are the only two surviving Baltic languages. Despite foreign rule from the 13th to 20th centuries, the Latvian nation maintained its identity throughout the generations via the language and musical traditions. Latvia and Estonia share a long common history. As a consequence of the Soviet occupation, both countries are home to a large number of ethnic Russians (26.9% in Latvia and 25.5% in Estonia), some of whom are non-citizens. Latvia is historically predominantly Protestant Lutheran, except for the Latgale region in the southeast, which has historically been predominantly Roman Catholic.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LA_PLATA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (La Plata)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LA_PLATA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (La Plata) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LA_PLATA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Viceroyalty of the Río de la Plata (Spanish: Virreinato del Río de la Plata) was the last to be organized and the one with the shortest life of the Viceroyalty of the Spanish Empire in the Americas. The Viceroyalty was established in 1776 from several former Viceroyalty of Perú dependencies that mainly extended over the Río de la Plata Basin, roughly the present-day territories of Argentina, Bolivia, Paraguay and Uruguay, extending inland from the Atlantic Coast. Buenos Aires, located on the western shore of the Río de la Plata estuary flowing into the Atlantic Ocean, opposite the Portuguese outpost of Colonia del Sacramento, was chosen as the capital. Usually considered one of the late Bourbon Reforms, the organization of this viceroyalty was motivated on both commercial grounds (Buenos Aires was by then a major spot for illegal trade), as well as on security concerns brought about by the growing interest of competing foreign powers in the area. The Spanish Crown wanted to protect its territory against Great Britain and the Kingdom of Portugal.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LEBANON_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Lebanon)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LEBANON_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Lebanon) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LEBANON_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Lebanon is a sovereign state in Asia. It is bordered by Syria to the north and east and Israel to the south. Lebanon's location at the crossroads of the Mediterranean Basin and the Arabian hinterland facilitated its rich history and shaped a cultural identity of religious and ethnic diversity. The earliest evidence of civilization in Lebanon dates back more than seven thousand years, predating recorded history. Lebanon was the home of the Canaanites/Phoenicians and their kingdom, a maritime culture that flourished for over a thousand years (c. 1550-539 BC). In 64 BC, the region came under the rule of the Roman Empire, and eventually became one of the Empire's leading centers of Christianity. In the Mount Lebanon range a monastic tradition known as the Maronite Church was established. As the Arab Muslims conquered the region, the Maronites held onto their religion and identity. However, a new religious group, the Druze, established themselves in Mount Lebanon as well, generating a religious divide that has lasted for centuries. During the Crusades, the Maronites re-established contact with the Roman Catholic Church and asserted their communion with Rome. The ties they established with the Latins have influenced the region into the modern era.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIBYAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Libyan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIBYAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Libyan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIBYAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Libya has been inhabited by Berbers since the late Bronze Age. The Phoenicians established trading posts in western Libya, and Ancient Greek colonists established city-states in eastern Libya. Libya was variously ruled by Persians, Egyptians and Greeks before becoming a part of the Roman Empire. Libya was an early center of Christianity. After the fall of the Western Roman Empire, the area of Libya was mostly occupied by the Vandals until the 7th century, when invasions brought Islam and Arab colonization. In the sixteenth century, the Spanish Empire and the Knights of St John occupied Tripoli, until Ottoman rule began in 1551. Libya was involved in the Barbary Wars of the 18th and 19th centuries. Ottoman rule continued until the Italian occupation of Libya resulted in the temporary Italian Libya colony from 1911 to 1943. During the Second World War Libya was an important area of warfare in the North African Campaign. The Italian population then went into decline. Libya became an independent kingdom in 1951.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LITHUANIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Lithuanian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LITHUANIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Lithuanian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LITHUANIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>For centuries, the southeastern shores of the Baltic Sea were inhabited by various Baltic tribes. In the 1230s, the Lithuanian lands were united by Mindaugas, the King of Lithuania, and the first unified Lithuanian state, the Kingdom of Lithuania, was created on 6 July 1253. During the 14th century, the Grand Duchy of Lithuania was the largest country in Europe; present-day Lithuania, Belarus, Ukraine, and parts of Poland and Russia were the territories of the Grand Duchy. With the Lublin Union of 1569, Lithuania and Poland formed a voluntary two-state union, the Polish-Lithuanian Commonwealth. The Commonwealth lasted more than two centuries, until neighboring countries systematically dismantled it from 1772-95, with the Russian Empire annexing most of Lithuania's territory.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LONGOBARDI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Longobardi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LONGOBARDI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Longobardi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LONGOBARDI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Lombards or Longobards were a Germanic people who ruled Italy from 568 to 774. The Lombard historian Paul the Deacon wrote in the Historia Langobardrum that the Lombards descended from a small tribe called the Winnili who dwelt in southern Scandinavia (Scadanan) before migrating to seek new lands. In the 1st century AD, they formed part of the Suebi, in northwestern Germany. By the end of the 5th century, they had moved into the area roughly coinciding with modern Austria north of the Danube river, where they subdued the Heruls and later fought frequent wars with the Gepids. The Lombard king Alboin eventually destroyed the Gepids in 567. Following this victory, Alboin decided to lead his people to Italy, which had become severely devastated after the long Gothic War (535-554) between the Byzantine Empire and the Ostrogothic Kingdom there. The Lombards were joined by numerous Saxons, Heruls, Gepids, Bulgars, Thuringians, and Ostrogoths, and their invasion of Italy was almost unopposed. By late 569 they had conquered all north of Italy and the principal cities north of the Po River except Pavia, which fell in 572. At the same time, they occupied areas in central Italy and southern Italy. They established a Lombard Kingdom in north and central Italy, later named Regnum Italicum ("Kingdom of Italy"), which reached its zenith under the 8th-century ruler Liutprand. In 774, the Kingdom was conquered by the Frankish King Charlemagne and integrated into his Empire. However, Lombard nobles continued to rule southern parts of the Italian peninsula, through the Duchy of Benevento, well into the 11th century when they were conquered by the Normans and added to their County of Sicily. Their legacy is also apparent in the regional name, Lombardy (in the north of Italy).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LULE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Lule)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LULE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Lule) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LULE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Lule is an indigenous language of northern Argentina. Lule may be extinct today. Campbell (1997) writes that in 1981 there was an unconfirmed report that Lule is still spoken by 5 families in Resistencia in east-central Chaco Province. It is unclear if it is the same language as Tonocoté. Lule appears to be distantly related to the still-spoken Vilela language, together forming a small Lule-Vilela family. Kaufman (1990) finds this relationship likely and with general agreement among the major classifiers of South American languages. Viegas Barros published additional evidence 1996-2006. Zamponi (2008) and other authors consider Lule and Vilela two linguistic isolates. There were three distinct groups known as Lulé: The nomadic Lule of the plains, who in addition to their own language, spoke Tonocote, the local lingua franca and the language of Spanish catechism. The sedentary Lule of the foothills, who were trilingual in Lule, Tonocote, and Quechua in addition to their original language, Cacan. The Lule-Tonocote, whose language was recorded by Machon.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUNDA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Lunda)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUNDA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Lunda) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUNDA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Kingdom of Lunda (c. 1665-1887), was a pre-colonial African confederation of states in what is now the Democratic Republic of Congo, north-eastern Angola and northwestern Zambia. Its central state was in Katanga. The strength of the kingdom enabled its military and ruling classes to conquer other tribes, especially to the east. In the eighteenth century a number of migrations took place as far as the region to the south of Lake Tanganyika. The Bemba people of Northern Zambia descended from Luba migrants who arrived in Zambia throughout the seventeenth century. At the same time, a Lunda chief and warrior called Mwata Kazembe set up an Eastern Lunda kingdom in the valley of the Luapula River.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUSITANI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Lusitani)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUSITANI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Lusitani) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUSITANI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Lusitanians (or Latin: Lusitani) were an Indo-European people living in the west of the Iberian Peninsula prior to its conquest by the Roman Republic and the subsequent incorporation of the territory into the Roman province of Lusitania (most of modern Portugal, Extremadura and a small part of the province of Salamanca). The Lusitanians were a people formed by several tribes that lived between the rivers Douro and Tagus, in most of today's Beira and Estremadura regions of central Portugal, and some areas of the Extremadura region (Spain). They were a tribal confederation, not a single political entity; each tribe had its own territory and was independent, and formed by smaller clans. However, they had a cultural sense of unity and a common name for the tribes. Each tribe was ruled by its own tribal aristocracy and chief. Many members of the Lusitanian tribal aristocracy were warriors as happened in many other pre-Roman peoples of the Iron Age. Only when an external threat occurred did the different tribes politically unite, as happened at the time of the Roman conquest of their territory when Viriathus became the single leader of the Lusitanian tribes. Kaukainos (or Caucenus) was another important Lusitanian chief before the Roman conquest. He ruled the Lusitanians (before Viriathus) for some time, leading the tribes in the resistance against Carthaginian attempts of conquest, and was successful.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MALAGASY_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Malagasy)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MALAGASY_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Malagasy) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MALAGASY_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Malagasy (French: Malgache) are the ethnic group that forms nearly the entire population of Madagascar. They are divided into two subgroups: the "Highlander" Merina, Sihanaka and Betsileo of the central plateau around Antananarivo, Alaotra (Ambatondrazaka) and Fianarantsoa, and the "coastal dwellers" elsewhere in the country. This division has its roots in historical patterns of settlement. The original Austronesian settlers from Borneo arrived between the third and tenth centuries and established a network of principalities in the Central Highlands region conducive to growing the rice they had carried with them on their outrigger canoes. Sometime later, a large number of settlers arrived from East Africa and established kingdoms along the relatively unpopulated coastlines.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAMELUKS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Mameluks)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAMELUKS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Mameluks) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAMELUKS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Mamluk Sultanate was a medieval realm spanning Egypt, the Levant, and Hejaz. It lasted from the overthrow of the Ayyubid Dynasty until the Ottoman conquest of Egypt in 1517. Historians have traditionally broken the era of Mamluk rule into two periods-one covering 1250-1382, the other, 1382-1517. Western historians call the former the "Bahri" period and the latter the "Burji," because of the political dominance of the regiments known by these names during the respective times. Mamluk state reached its height under the Turkish rule and then fell into a prolonged phase of decline under the Circassians. The sultanate's ruling caste was composed of Mamluks, soldiers of predominantly Cuman-Kipchaks (from Crimea), Circassian, Abkhazian, Oghuz Turks and Georgian slave origin. While Mamluks were purchased, their status was above ordinary slaves, who were not allowed to carry weapons or perform certain tasks. Mamluks were considered to be "true lords", with social status above citizens of Egypt. Though it declined towards the end of its existence, at its height the sultanate represented the zenith of medieval Egyptian and Levantine political, economic, and cultural glory in the Islamic era.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MANI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Mani)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MANI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Mani) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MANI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Maniq are an ethnic group of Thailand. They are the only Negrito group in Thailand and speak Maniq (also called Tonga, Kensiu or Mos), a Mon-Khmer language in the Aslian language group. It is thought they once spoke a language similar to the Andamanese language but then adopted the language of the Mon-Khmer people around them. The Maniq are a hunting and gathering society. They build temporary huts of bamboo with roofs made of banana leaves. They hunt many types of animals and consume many different kinds of vegetables and fruits. They wear simple clothes made of materials such as bamboo leaves. They are familiar with many different species of medicinal herbs.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MEDES_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Medes)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MEDES_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Medes) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MEDES_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Medes were an ancient Iranian people who lived in an area known as Media (Northwestern Iran) and who spoke the Median language. Their arrival to the region is associated with the first wave of migrating Iranic Aryan tribes into Ancient Iran from the late 2nd millennium BCE (circa 1000 BC) (the Bronze Age collapse) through the beginning of the 1st millennium BCE (circa 900 BC). Greek references to "Median" people make no clear distinction between the "Persians" and the "Medians"; in fact for a Greek to become "too closely associated with Iranian culture" was "to become medianized, not persianized". The Median kingdom was a short-lived Iranian state and the textual and archaeological sources of that period are rare and little could be known from the Median culture which nevertheless made a "profound, and lasting, contribution to the greater world of Iranian culture".</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MELANESIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Melanesian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MELANESIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Melanesian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MELANESIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Melanesians are the dominant inhabitants of Melanesia. Most speak one of the many Papuan languages, though a few groups such as Moluccans, the Motu and Fijians speak Austronesian languages. The Melanesians appear to have occupied islands from Eastern Indonesia to as far east as the main islands in the Solomon Islands, including Makira and possibly the smaller islands farther to the east. Early European explorers noted the physical differences among groups of Pacific Islanders. In 1756 Charles de Brosses theorized that there was an 'old black race' in the Pacific who were conquered or defeated by the peoples of what is now called Polynesia, whom he distinguished as having lighter skin.:189-190 By 1825 Jean Baptiste Bory de Saint-Vincent developed a more elaborate, 15-race model of human diversity. He described the inhabitants of modern-day Melanesia as Mélaniens, a distinct racial group from the Australian and Neptunian (i.e. Polynesian) races surrounding them.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MICRONESIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Micronesian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MICRONESIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Micronesian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MICRONESIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The ancestors of the Micronesians settled over four thousand years ago. A decentralized chieftain-based system eventually evolved into a more centralized economic and religious culture centered on Yap. Nan Madol, consisting of a series of small artificial islands linked by a network of canals, is often called the Venice of the Pacific. It is located on the eastern periphery of the island of Pohnpei and used to be the ceremonial and political seat of the Saudeleur dynasty that united Pohnpei's estimated 25,000 people from about AD 500 until 1500, when the centralized system collapsed. European explorers-first the Portuguese in search of the Spice Islands (Indonesia) and then the Spanish-reached the Carolines in the sixteenth century. The Spanish incorporated the archipelago to the Spanish East Indies and in the 19th century established a number of outposts and missions. In 1887, they founded the town of Santiago de la Ascension in what today is Kolonia on the island of Pohnpei. Following defeat in the Spanish-American War, the Spanish sold the archipelago to Germany in 1899 under the German-Spanish Treaty of 1899. Germany incorporated it into German New Guinea. During World War I, it was captured by Japan. Following the war, the League of Nations awarded a mandate for Japan to administer the islands as part of the South Pacific Mandate. During World War II, a significant portion of the Japanese fleet was based in Truk Lagoon. In February 1944, Operation Hailstone, one of the most important naval battles of the war, took place at Truk, in which many Japanese support vessels and aircraft were destroyed.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MING_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Ming)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MING_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Ming) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MING_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Ming dynasty also called the Empire of the Great Ming, was the ruling dynasty of China for 276 years (1368-1644) following the collapse of the Mongol-led Yuan dynasty. The Ming, described by some as "one of the greatest eras of orderly government and social stability in human history," was the last dynasty in China ruled by ethnic Han Chinese. Although the primary capital of Beijing fell in 1644 to a rebellion led by Li Zicheng (who established the Shun dynasty, soon replaced by the Manchu-led Qing dynasty), regimes loyal to the Ming throne - collectively called the Southern Ming - survived until 1662. The Hongwu Emperor (ruled 1368-98) attempted to create a society of self-sufficient rural communities ordered in a rigid, immobile system that would guarantee and support a permanent class of soldiers for his dynasty: the empire's standing army exceeded one million troops and the navy's dockyards in Nanjing were the largest in the world. He also took great care breaking the power of the court eunuchs and unrelated magnates, enfeoffing his many sons throughout China and attempting to guide these princes through the Huang Ming Zu Xun, a set of published dynastic instructions. This failed spectacularly when his teenage successor, the Jianwen Emperor, attempted to curtail his uncles' power, prompting the Jingnan Campaign, an uprising that placed the Prince of Yan upon the throne as the Yongle Emperor in 1402. The Yongle Emperor established Yan as a secondary capital and renamed it Beijing, constructed the Forbidden City, and restored the Grand Canal and the primacy of the imperial examinations in official appointments. He rewarded his eunuch supporters and employed them as a counterweight against the Confucian scholar-bureaucrats. One, Zheng He, led seven enormous voyages of exploration into the Indian Ocean as far as Arabia and the eastern coasts of Africa.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MITTANNI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Mittanni)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MITTANNI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Mittanni) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MITTANNI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Mitanni also called Hanigalbat (Hanigalbat, Khanigalbat cuneiform a-ni-gal-bat) in Assyrian or Naharin in Egyptian texts, was a Hurrian-speaking state in northern Syria and southeast Anatolia from ca. 1500 BC-1300 BC. Founded by an Indo-Aryan ruling class governing a predominantly Hurrian population, Mitanni came to be a regional power after the Hittite destruction of Amorite Babylon and a series of ineffectual Assyrian kings created a power vacuum in Mesopotamia. At the beginning of its history, Mitanni's major rival was Egypt under the Thutmosids. However, with the ascent of the Hittite empire, Mitanni and Egypt made an alliance to protect their mutual interests from the threat of Hittite domination. At the height of its power, during the 14th century BC, Mitanni had outposts centered on its capital, Washukanni, whose location has been determined by archaeologists to be on the headwaters of the Khabur River. Eventually, Mitanni succumbed to Hittite and later Assyrian attacks, and was reduced to the status of a province of the Middle Assyrian Empire.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOCOVI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Mocovi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOCOVI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Mocovi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOCOVI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Mocoví are an indigenous tribe of the Gran Chaco. They live in Chaco Province and Santa Fe Province of Argentina.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOHAWK_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Mohawk)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOHAWK_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Mohawk) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOHAWK_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Mohawk people (who identify as Kanien'keha:ka) are the most easterly tribe of the Iroquois Confederacy, and are also known as the "People of the Flint Place." They are an Iroquoian-speaking indigenous people of North America. They were historically based in the Mohawk Valley in present-day upstate New York west of Albany; their territory ranged to the St. Lawrence River and present-day southern Quebec and eastern Ontario, greater New Jersey, and southward into present-day Pennsylvania, eastward to the Green Mountains of Vermont, and westward to the border with the Oneida Nation's traditional homeland territory. As one of the five original members of the Iroquois League, or Haudenosaunee, the Mohawk were known as the Keepers of the Eastern Door. For hundreds of years, they guarded the Iroquois Confederation against invasion from that direction by tribes from the New England and lower New York areas. Their current major settlements include areas around Lake Ontario and the St Lawrence River in Canada and New York.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOLLO_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Mollo)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOLLO_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Mollo) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOLLO_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Mollo culture existed in Bolivia's altiplano area after the collapse of the Tiwanaku culture during the period of AD 1000 to 1500; it predated the Inca civilization. While the Mollo showed a continuity with Late Tiwanaku culture in both domestic and village architecture, they left no pyramids. Mollo worshiped the jaguar. The Mollo were defined by their ceramics. Shoe pots, grave pots, vases, and dipping vessels have been found and these are either plain or painted black and white on red clay. They created a unique drinking cup with a built-in straw. Some of these ceramics can be found today as far away as the Naprstek Museum in Prague.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUISCA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Muisca)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUISCA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Muisca) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUISCA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Muisca are the Chibcha-speaking people that formed the Muiscan Confederation of the central highlands of present-day Colombia's Eastern Range. They were encountered by the Spanish Empire in 1537, at the time of the conquest. Subgroupings of the Muisca were mostly identified by their allegiances to three great rulers: the Zaque, centered in Chunza, ruling a territory roughly covering modern southern and northeastern Boyaca and southern Santander; the Zipa, centered in Bacata, and encompassing most of modern Cundinamarca, the western Llanos and northeastern Tolima; and the Iraca, ruler of Suamox and modern northeastern Boyaca and southwestern Santander.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MURRI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Murri)</English>
		<German>
			<Text>Kultur Murri:Kultur Murri:Kultur Murri:Kultur Murri</Text>
			<Gender>Female</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MURRI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Murri) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MURRI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Murri are the Indigenous Australians of modern-day Queensland, North West New South Wales. Collections of tribes and extended family groups throughout geographic regions of Australia have different names, such as the Yugarabul, the Jagera peoples from Coorparoo, Kwiambal peoples from Northern New South Wales and the Koori people of parts of New South Wales and Victoria. The term is their preferred term, expressing pride in their heritage and race.</English>
		<German>Bei den [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Murri[COLOR_REVERT] handelt es sich um ein indigenes australisches Volk aus dem Gebiet des heutigen Queensland und dem Nordwesten von New South Wales, das auf eine 40000-jährige Geschichte zurückblicken kann. Über die Murri ist bekannt, dass sie sich häufig im Zentrum ihres Gebietes versammelten, um dort ein riesiges Fest zu feiern. Zu solchen Zeiten befanden sich Tausende Menschen gleichzeitig auf Wanderschaft. Nach der Ankunft der Europäer wurden viele Murri in Missionsstationen zwangumgesiedelt. Dort mussten sie mit Stämmen zusammenleben, die ihnen nicht unbedingt freundlich gesinnt waren. In der ersten Hälfte des 19. Jahrhunderts wurden vielen Murri ihre Mischlingskinder entrissen und zur Adoption an weiße Familien gegeben, um sie zu christianisieren und als Weiße zu erziehen (Gestohlene Generation).</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NABATEANS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Nabateans)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NABATEANS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Nabateans) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NABATEANS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Nabataeans were an Arab people who inhabited northern Arabia and the Southern Levant, and whose settlements, most prominently the assumed capital city of Petra, in AD 37 - c. 100, gave the name of Nabatene to the borderland between Arabia and Syria, from the Euphrates to the Red Sea. Their loosely controlled trading network, which centered on strings of oases that they controlled, where agriculture was intensively practiced in limited areas, and on the routes that linked them, had no securely defined boundaries in the surrounding desert. Trajan conquered the Nabataean kingdom, annexing it to the Roman Empire, where their individual culture, easily identified by their characteristic finely potted painted ceramics, became dispersed in the general Greco-Roman culture and was eventually lost. They were later converted to Christianity. Jane Taylor, a writer, describes them as "one of the most gifted peoples of the ancient world".</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAHUA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Nahua)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAHUA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Nahua) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAHUA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Nahuas are a group of indigenous people of Mexico and El Salvador. Their language of Uto-Aztecan affiliation is called Nahuatl and consists of many more dialects and variants, a number of which are mutually unintelligible. About 1,500,000 Nahua speak Nahuatl and another 1,000,000 speak only Spanish. Less than 1,000 native speakers remain in El Salvador. Evidence suggests the Nahua peoples originated in Aridoamerica, in regions of the present day northwestern Mexico. They split off from the other Uto-Aztecan speaking peoples and migrated into central Mexico around 500 CE. They settled in and around the Basin of Mexico and spread out to become the dominant people in central Mexico.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NIGERIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Nigerian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NIGERIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Nigerian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NIGERIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Nigerian culture was profoundly affected by the British colonial rule. Such as British colonial authorities' denouncements and attacks upon polygamy, trial by ordeal, and certain types of sacrifices. At the same time, British colonial authorities maintained and promoted traditional Nigerian culture that strengthened colonial administration. The British spread Christianity throughout southern Nigeria and Christian missionaries assisted British authorities in establishing a Western-style education system in Nigeria that resulted in the teaching of the English language in Nigeria and its subsequent adoption as Nigeria's main language. The British replaced unpaid household labour with wage labour. Prior to colonization in the twentieth century, Nigeria's tribes usually possessed the land as a community, such that land could not be bought or sold. Colonization brought the notion of individuals owning land and commercialization of land began.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NOONGAR_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Noongar)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NOONGAR_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Noongar) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NOONGAR_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Noongar are an Indigenous Australian people who live in the south-west corner of Western Australia, from Geraldton on the west coast to Esperance on the south coast. Traditionally, they inhabited the region from Jurien Bay to the southern coast of Western Australia, and east to what is now Ravensthorpe and Southern Cross, south west of the circumcision line separating those Aboriginal groups of central Australia that practised male circumcision upon initiation from those who did not. Noongar country, according to Norman Tindale, was occupied by 14 different groups: Amangu, Ballardong, Yued, Kaneang, Koreng, Mineng, Njakinjaki, Njunga, Pibelmen, Binjareb, Wardandi, Whadjuk, Wilman and Wudjari. The Noongar traditionally spoke dialects of the Noongar language, a member of the large Pama-Nyungan language family, but generally today speak Australian Aboriginal English (a dialect of the English language) combined with Noongar words and grammar. Although Noongar today still recognise the existence of these groups, most Noongar today trace their ancestry to more than one of these groups.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NORMAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Norman)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NORMAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Norman) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NORMAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Normans were the people who in the 10th and 11th centuries gave their name to Normandy, a region in France. They were descended from Norse ("Norman" comes from "Norseman") raiders and pirates from Denmark, Iceland and Norway who, under their leader Rollo, agreed to swear fealty to King Charles III of West Francia. Through generations of assimilation and mixing with the native Frankish and Roman-Gaulish populations, their descendants would gradually merge with the Carolingian-based cultures of West Francia. The distinct cultural and ethnic identity of the Normans emerged initially in the first half of the 10th century, and it continued to evolve over the succeeding centuries.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NUMIDIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Numidian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NUMIDIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Numidian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NUMIDIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Numidia (202 BC - 46 BC) was an Ancient Berber kingdom in what is now Algeria and a smaller part of Tunisia, in North Africa. Numidia was originally divided between Massylii in the east and Masaesyli in the west. During the Second Punic War (218-201 BC), Massinissa, king of the Massylii, defeated Syphax of the Masaesyli to unify Numidia into one kingdom. The kingdom began as a sovereign state and later alternated between being a Roman province and a Roman client state. It was bordered by the kingdoms of Mauretania (modern-day Morocco) to the west, the Roman province of Africa (modern-day Tunisia) to the east, the Mediterranean Sea to the north, and the Sahara Desert to the south. It is considered to be the first major state in the history of Algeria and the Berber world.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ODAWA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Odawa)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ODAWA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Odawa) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ODAWA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Odawa (also Ottawa or Odaawaa), said to mean "traders," have long had territory that crossed the current borders of the United States, where they are federally recognized as Native American tribes, and Canada, where there are numerous recognized First Nations bands. They are one of the Anishinaabeg, related to but distinct from the Ojibwe and Potawatomi peoples. After migrating from the East Coast in ancient times, they settled on Manitoulin Island, near the northern shores of Lake Huron, and the Bruce Peninsula in the present-day province of Ontario, Canada. They considered this their original homeland. After the 17th century, they also settled along the Ottawa River, and in the state of Michigan, United States, as well as through the Midwest south of the Great Lakes in the latter country. In the 21st century, there are approximately 15,000 Odawa living in Ontario, and Michigan and Oklahoma (former Indian Territory, United States).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OMAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Oman)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OMAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Oman) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OMAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Oman is an Arab country in the southeastern coast of the Arabian Peninsula. Holding a strategically important position at the mouth of the Persian Gulf, the nation is bordered by the United Arab Emirates to the northwest, Saudi Arabia to the west, and Yemen to the southwest, and shares marine borders with Iran and Pakistan. The coast is formed by the Arabian Sea on the southeast and the Gulf of Oman on the northeast. The Madha and Musandam exclaves are surrounded by the UAE on their land borders, with the Strait of Hormuz (which it shares with Iran) and Gulf of Oman forming Musandam's coastal boundaries. From the late 17th century, the Omani Sultanate was a powerful empire, vying with Portugal and Britain for influence in the Persian Gulf and Indian Ocean. At its peak in the 19th century, Omani influence or control extended across the Strait of Hormuz to modern-day Iran and Pakistan, and as far south as Zanzibar (today part of Tanzania, also former capital). As its power declined in the 20th century, the sultanate came under the influence of the United Kingdom. Historically, Muscat was the principal trading port of the Persian Gulf region. Muscat was also among the most important trading ports of the Indian Ocean. Oman's official religion is Islam.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OPHIR_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Ophir)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OPHIR_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Ophir) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OPHIR_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Ophir is a port or region mentioned in the Bible, famous for its wealth. King Solomon received a cargo of gold, silver, sandalwood, pearls, ivory, apes and peacocks from Ophir, every three years. Biblical scholars, archaeologists and others have tried to determine the exact location of Ophir. Vasco da Gama's companion Tomé Lopes reasoned that Ophir would have been the ancient name for Great Zimbabwe in Zimbabwe, the main center of sub-African trade in gold in the Renaissance period - though the ruins at Great Zimbabwe are now dated to the medieval era, long after Solomon is said to have lived. The identification of Ophir with Sofala in Mozambique was mentioned by Milton in Paradise Lost (11:399-401), among many other works of literature and science.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ORANG_ASLI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Orang Asli)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ORANG_ASLI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Orang Asli) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ORANG_ASLI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Orang Asli (lit. "original people", "natural people" or "aboriginal people" in Malay) are the indigenous people and the oldest inhabitants of Peninsular Malaysia. Orang Asli kept to themselves until the first traders from India arrived in the first millennium AD. Living in the interior they bartered inland products like resins, incense woods and feathers for salt, cloth and iron tools. The rise of the Malay sultanates, coinciding with trade in Orang Asli slaves, forced the group to retreat further inland to avoid contact with outsiders. The arrival of British colonists brought further inroads in the lives of Orang Asli. They were targeted by Christian missionaries and became subjects of anthropological research. Slave raids into Orang Asli settlements were also quite common feature back in the 18th and 19th centuries. These slave-raiders were mainly local Malays and Bataks, who considered the Orang Asli as 'kafirs', 'non-humans', 'savages' and 'jungle-beasts. The modus operandi was basically to swoop down a settlement and then kill off all the adult men. Women and children were captured alive as they are 'easier to tame.' The captives Orang Asli slaves were sold off or given to local rulers and chieftains to gain their favour. Slaves trade soon developed and even continued into the present century despite the official abolition of all forms of slavery in 1884. The derogatory term "Sakai" is used to refer to the Orang Asli until the middle of the 20th century meant slave or dependent. Many of the elders Orang Asli still remember this sad period of their history, and they detest being called "Sakai".</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PAIUTE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Paiute)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PAIUTE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Paiute) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PAIUTE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Northern Paiute traditionally have lived in the Great Basin in eastern California, western Nevada, and southeast Oregon. The Northern Paiute's pre-contact lifestyle was well adapted to the harsh desert environment in which they lived. Each tribe or band occupied a specific territory, generally centered on a lake or wetland that supplied fish and water-fowl. Communal drives, which often involved neighboring bands, would take rabbits and pronghorn from surrounding areas. Individuals and families appear to have moved freely between bands. Pinyon nuts gathered in the mountains in the fall provided critical winter food. Grass seeds and roots were also important parts of their diet. The name of each band came from a characteristic food source. For example, the people at Pyramid Lake were known as the Cui Ui Ticutta (meaning "Cui-ui eaters"), the people of the Lovelock area were known as the Koop Ticutta, meaning "ground-squirrel eaters", and the people of the Carson Sink were known as the Toi Ticutta, meaning "tule eaters". The Kucadikadi of Mono County, California are the "brine fly eaters".</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PALESTINIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Palestinian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PALESTINIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Palestinian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PALESTINIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Palestinian people are an ethnic group comprising the modern descendants of the peoples who have lived in Palestine over the centuries, and who today are largely culturally and linguistically Arab due to Arabization of the region. Despite various wars and exoduses (such as that in 1948), roughly one half of the world's Palestinian population continues to reside in historic Palestine, the area encompassing the West Bank, the Gaza Strip and Israel. In this combined area, as of 2004, Palestinians constituted 49% of all inhabitants, encompassing the entire population of the Gaza Strip (1.6 million), the majority of the population of the West Bank (approximately 2.3 million versus close to 500,000 Jewish Israeli citizens which includes about 200,000 in East Jerusalem), and 16.5% of the population of Israel proper as Arab citizens of Israel. Many are Palestinian refugees or internally displaced Palestinians, including more than a million in the Gaza Strip, three-quarters of a million in the West Bank, and about a quarter of a million in Israel proper. Of the Palestinian population who live abroad, known as the Palestinian diaspora, more than half are stateless lacking citizenship in any country. 3.24 million of the diaspora population live in neighboring Jordan, over 1 million live between Syria and Lebanon, a quarter of a million in Saudi Arabia, with Chile's half a million representing the largest concentration outside the Arab world.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PANAMAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Panaman)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PANAMAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Panaman) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PANAMAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Panama is a country in Central America situated between North and South America. It is bordered by Costa Rica to the west, Colombia to the southeast, the Caribbean to the north and the Pacific Ocean to the south. The capital and largest city is Panama City, whose metropolitan area is home to nearly half of the country's 3.9 million people. Panama was inhabited by several indigenous tribes prior to settlement by the Spanish in the 16th century. Panama broke away from Spain in 1821 and joined a union of Nueva Granada, Ecuador, and Venezuela named the Republic of Gran Colombia. When Gran Colombia dissolved in 1831, Panama and Nueva Granada remained joined, eventually becoming the Republic of Colombia. With the backing of the United States, Panama seceded from Colombia in 1903, allowing the Panama Canal to be built by the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers between 1904 and 1914. In 1977, an agreement was signed for the total transfer of the Canal from the United States to Panama by the end of the 20th century, which culminated on 31 December 1999.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PARAGUAYAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Paraguayan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PARAGUAYAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Paraguayan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PARAGUAYAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Paraguay is a landlocked country in central South America, bordered by Argentina to the south and southwest, Brazil to the east and northeast, and Bolivia to the northwest. Paraguay lies on both banks of the Paraguay River, which runs through the center of the country from north to south. Due to its central location in South America, it is sometimes referred to as Corazón de Sudamérica ("Heart of South America").The indigenous Guaraní had been living in Paraguay for at least a millennium before the Spanish conquered the territory in the 16th century. Spanish settlers and Jesuit missions introduced Christianity and Spanish culture to the region. Paraguay was a peripheral colony of the Spanish Empire, with few urban centers and settlers. Following independence from Spain in 1811, Paraguay was ruled by a series of dictators who generally implemented isolationist and protectionist policies. Following the disastrous Paraguayan War (1864-1870), the country lost 60 to 70 percent of its population through war and disease, and about 140,000 square kilometers (54,054 sq mi) of territory to Argentina and Brazil. Through the 20th century, Paraguay continued to endure a succession of authoritarian governments, culminating in the regime of Alfredo Stroessner, who led South America's longest-lived military dictatorship from 1954 to 1989. He was toppled in an internal military coup, and free multi-party elections were organized and held for the first time in 1993. A year later, Paraguay joined Argentina, Brazil and Uruguay to found Mercosur, a regional economic collaborative.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PASHTUN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Pashtun)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PASHTUN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Pashtun) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PASHTUN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Pashtuns are an ethnic group with populations in Afghanistan and Pakistan. They are generally classified as Eastern Iranian who use Pashto language and follow Pashtunwali, which is a traditional set of Torah ethics guiding individual and communal conduct derived from the Torah. The origin of Pashtuns is Israel but historians have come across references to various ancient peoples called Pakthas (Pactyans) between the 2nd and the 1st millennium BC, who may be their early ancestors. Often characterised as a warrior and martial race, their history is mostly spread amongst various countries of South and Central Asia, centred on their traditional seat of power in medieval Afghanistan.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERUVIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Peruvian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERUVIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Peruvian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERUVIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Peruvian territory was home to ancient cultures spanning from the Norte Chico civilization in Caral, one of the oldest in the world, to the Inca Empire, the largest state in Pre-Columbian America. The Spanish Empire conquered the region in the 16th century and established a Viceroyalty with its capital in Lima, which included most of its South American colonies. Ideas of political autonomy later spread throughout Spanish America and Peru gained its independence, which was formally proclaimed in 1821. After the battle of Ayacucho, three years after proclamation, Peru ensured its independence. After achieving independence, the country remained in recession and kept a low military profile until an economic rise based on the extraction of raw and maritime materials struck the country, which ended shortly before the war of the Pacific. Subsequently, the country has undergone changes in government from oligarchic to democratic systems. Peru has gone through periods of political unrest and internal conflict as well as periods of stability and economic upswing</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PHILIPINO_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Filipino)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PHILIPINO_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Filipino) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PHILIPINO_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Philippines is a sovereign island country in Southeast Asia situated in the western Pacific Ocean. It consists of about 7,641 islands that are categorized broadly under three main geographical divisions: Luzon, Visayas, and Mindanao. The capital city of the Philippines is Manila and the most populous city is Quezon City; both are part of Metro Manila. To the North of the Philippines across the Luzon Strait lies Taiwan; China and the territories of Hong Kong and Macao lie in the Northeast; Vietnam sits West across the South China Sea; Southwest lie Brunei, Indonesia and Malaysia in the island of Borneo; the Celebes Sea separates it from other islands of Indonesia in the South; while to the Southeast it is bounded by the Philippine Sea, Indonesia and the island-nation of Palau; far East lie the United States territories of Guam the Northern Mariana Islands; small islands of Japan are found in the Northeast. Its location on the Pacific Ring of Fire and close to the equator makes the Philippines prone to earthquakes and typhoons, but also endows it with abundant natural resources and some of the world's greatest biodiversity. At approximately 300,000 square kilometers (115,831 sq mi), the Philippines is the 72nd-largest country in the world.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PHILISTINES_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Philistines)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PHILISTINES_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Philistines) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PHILISTINES_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Philistines were a people described in the Bible. The Hebrew term "pelishtim" occurs 286 times in the Masoretic Text of the Hebrew Bible (of which 152 times in 1 Samuel), whereas in the Greek Septuagint version of the Hebrew Bible, the equivalent term phylistiim occurs only 12 times, with the remaining 269 references instead using the term "allophylos" ("of another tribe"). According to the Old Testament, the land of the Philistines was a pentapolis in southwestern Levant comprising the five city-states of Gaza, Ashkelon, Ashdod, Ekron, and Gath, from Wadi Gaza in the south to the Yarqon River in the north. The Bible portrays them at one period of time as among the Kingdom of Israel's most dangerous enemies. Biblical scholars have connected the Philistines to other biblical groups such as Caphtorim and the Cherethites and Pelethites, which have both been identified with Crete, and leading to the tradition of an Aegean origin, although this theory has been disputed.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PILAGA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Pilaga)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PILAGA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Pilaga) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PILAGA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>As many anthropologists have noted, the Chaco groups, including the Pilaga, have been hunter-gatherers. Hunting includes fishing and collection of honey. Hunting is exclusively the domain of men, while gathering of wild fruits, palm hearts, mesquite (prosopis sp.) and firewood is done regularly by women. The major animals hunted are species of deers and armadillos. Among the fish specimens are surubí (Pseudoplatysoma coruscans), pacú (colossoma mitrei) and dorado (salminus maxillosus). The geographical distribution into communities is permeated by pan-Chacoan social organization of people into bands. According to Braunstein (1983), among the Chaco groups several bands constitute a 'tribe', identified by a common name and associated by marriage and exchange. He states that tribes have been preferably endogamous, with uxirolocal postmarital residence. Among the Pilaga, tribes have identified with names of regional animals and these traditional denominations persist in present times.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POVERTY_POINT_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Poverty Point)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POVERTY_POINT_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Poverty Point) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POVERTY_POINT_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Poverty Point culture is an archaeological culture that corresponds to an ancient group of Indigenous peoples who inhabited the area of the lower Mississippi Valley and surrounding Gulf coast from about 2200 BC - 700 BC. Dating of the Watson Brake site in present-day Ouachita Parish, Louisiana, where eleven earthwork mounds were built beginning about 3500 BC, shows it to be the earliest, dated mound complex in the Americas. It was begun well before the construction of the pyramids in Egypt. Next oldest is the Poverty Point Culture, which thrived from 2200 BC- 700 BC, during the late Archaic period in the Americas. Evidence of this mound builder culture has been found at more than 100 sites, including the Jaketown Site near Belzoni, Mississippi. The largest and best-known site is at Poverty Point, which lies on the Macon Ridge near present-day Epps, Louisiana. The Poverty Point culture may have hit its peak around 1500 BC. It is one of the oldest complex cultures, and possibly the first tribal culture in the Mississippi Delta and in the present-day United States. The people occupied villages that extended for nearly 100 miles (160 km) on either side of the Mississippi River. Poverty Point culture was followed by the Tchefuncte and Lake Cormorant cultures of the Tchula period, a local manifestation of the Early Woodland period. These descendant cultures differed from Poverty Point culture in trading over shorter distances, creating less massive public projects, completely adopting ceramics for storage and cooking, and lacking a lapidary (stone-carving) industry.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POYA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Poya)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POYA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Poya) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POYA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Poyas were a subgroup of indigenous Tehuelche people living in the Andes of Llanquihue and Palena Province as well as on the southern shores of Nahuel Huapi Lake in present-day Argentina. The Jesuit priest Nicolas Mascardi divided the Poya language into two linguistically distinct groups the one spoken by the "comarcanos" of Nahuelhuapi and another one spoken further east as far away as to the Atlanctic Ocean.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUELCHE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Puelche)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUELCHE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Puelche) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUELCHE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Puelche (Mapudungun: pwelche, " people of the east") is the name that the Mapuche used to give the ethnic groups who inhabited the lands to the east of the Andes Mountains (in Argentine territory and some valleys of Chile) including the northern Tehuelches and Hets, these last ones were also known as the Pampas or Querandíes. By the end of the 18th century the survivors of the plagues and epidemics that annihilated these ethnic groups were aculturated in a process of Araucanization by Mapuche immigrants, so that in the 19th century the ethnically mixed group formed was basically Het and Tehuelche but Araucanized linguistically and culturally.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUNTIC_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Puntic)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUNTIC_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Puntic) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUNTIC_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Land of Punt, also called Pwenet, or Pwene by the ancient Egyptians, was an old kingdom. A trading partner of Egypt, it was known for producing and exporting gold, aromatic resins, blackwood, ebony, ivory, and wild animals. The region is known from ancient Egyptian records of trade expeditions to it. Some biblical scholars have identified it with the biblical land of Put. At times Punt is referred to as Ta netjer, the "land of the god". The exact location of Punt is still debated by historians. Most scholars today believe Punt was located to the southeast of Egypt, most likely in the coastal region of what is today Somalia, Djibouti, Eritrea, northeast Ethiopia and the Red Sea coast of Sudan. However, some scholars point instead to a range of ancient inscriptions which locate Punt in the Arabian Peninsula. It is also possible that the territory covered both the Horn of Africa and Southern Arabia. Puntland, the Somali administrative region situated at the extremity of the Horn of Africa, is named in reference to the Land of Punt.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QIN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Qin)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QIN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Qin) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QIN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Qin dynasty was the first imperial dynasty of Ancient China, lasting from 221 to 206 BC. Named for its heartland of Qin, in modern-day Gansu and Shaanxi, the dynasty was formed after the conquest of six other states by the Qin state, and its founding emperor named Qin Shi Huang, the First Emperor of Qin. The strength of the Qin state was greatly increased by the Legalist reforms of Shang Yang in the fourth century BC, during the Warring States period. In the mid and late third century BC, the Qin accomplished a series of swift conquests, first ending the powerless Zhou dynasty, and eventually conquering the other six of the Seven Warring States to gain control over the whole of China.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QING_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Qing)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QING_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Qing) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QING_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Qing dynasty was the last imperial dynasty of China, ruling from 1644 to 1912 with a brief, abortive restoration in 1917. It was preceded by the Ming dynasty and succeeded by the Republic of China. The Qing multi-cultural empire lasted almost three centuries and formed the territorial base for the modern Chinese state. The dynasty was founded by the Jurchen Aisin Gioro clan in Manchuria. In the late sixteenth century, Nurhaci, originally a Ming vassal, began organizing Jurchen clans into "Banners", military-social units. Nurhaci formed these clans into a unified entity, the subjects of which became known collectively as the Manchu people. By 1636, his son Hong Taiji began driving Ming forces out of Liaodong and declared a new dynasty, the Qing. In 1644, peasant rebels led by Li Zicheng conquered the Ming capital Beijing. Rather than serve them, Ming general Wu Sangui made an alliance with the Manchus and opened the Shanhai Pass to the Banner Armies led by Prince Dorgon, who defeated the rebels and seized Beijing. The conquest of China proper was not completed until 1683 under the Kangxi Emperor (r. 1661-1722). The Ten Great Campaigns of the Qianlong Emperor from the 1750s to the 1790s extended Qing control into Central Asia. While the early rulers maintained their Manchu ways, and while their official title was Emperor they were known as khans to the Mongols and patronized Tibetan Buddhism, they governed using Confucian styles and institutions of bureaucratic government. They retained the imperial examinations to recruit Han Chinese to work under or in parallel with Manchus. They also adapted the ideals of the tributary system in international relations, and in places such as Taiwan, the Qing so-called internal foreign policy closely resembled colonial policy and control.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QUEBEC_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Quebec)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QUEBEC_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Quebec) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QUEBEC_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Quebec is Canada's second most populous province, after Ontario. Most inhabitants live in urban areas near the Saint Lawrence River between Montreal and Quebec City, the capital. Approximately half of Quebec residents live in the Greater Montreal Area, including the Island of Montreal. English-speaking communities and English-language institutions are concentrated in the west of the island of Montreal but are also significantly present in the Outaouais, Eastern Townships, and Gaspé regions. The Nord-du-Québec region, occupying the northern half of the province, is sparsely populated and inhabited primarily by Aboriginal peoples. The climate around the major cities is four-season continental with cold and snowy winters combined with warm to hot humid summers, but further north long winter seasons dominate and as a result the northern areas of the province are marked by tundra conditions. Even in central Quebec at comparatively southerly latitudes winters are very severe in inland areas.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QUERANDI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Querandi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QUERANDI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Querandi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QUERANDI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Querandí were one of the Het peoples, indigenous South Americans who lived in the Pampas area of Argentina; specifically, they were the eastern Didiuhet. The name Querandí was given by the Guaraní people, as they would consume animal fat in their daily diet. Thus, Querandí means "men with fat". They were also well known as the Pampas prior to the 19th Century. Mapuche (or araucanos) called them Puelche. This is today the present Argentine provinces of La Pampa, most of the province of Buenos Aires, the center and the south of the province of Santa Fe (especially to the south of the Tercero-Carcaraña River), a great part of the province of Cordoba (adapted ecologically to the temperate Pampasia, their northern limits were in the region of the Gran Chaco - around 31° lat. South) and the peneplains of the present provinces of San Luis and Mendoza, although these zones were more difficult to inhabit due to its extreme climate and lack of surface water.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QULLA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Qulla)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QULLA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Qulla) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QULLA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Qulla (Quechua for south, hispanicized and mixed spellings Colla, Kolla) are an indigenous people of Western Bolivia, Chile, and Argentina, living in Jujuy and Salta Provinces. The 2004 Complementary Indigenous Survey reported 53,019 Qulla households living in Argentina. They moved freely between the borders of Argentina and Bolivia. Their lands are part of the yungas or high altitude forests at the edge of the Amazon rainforest. The Qulla have lived in their region for centuries, before the arrival of the Inca Empire in the 15th century. Sillustani is a prehistoric Qulla cemetery in Peru, with elaborate stone chullpas. Several groups made up the Qulla people, including the Zenta, and Gispira. The Qulla came into contact with Spaniards in 1540. They resisted Spanish invasion for 110 years but ultimately lost the Santiago Estate to the Spanish. One particularly famous rebel leader was Ñusta Willaq, a female warrior who fought the Spanish in 1780. With Argentinian independence in 1810, the situation of the Qulla people did not improve and they worked for minimal wages.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RED_OCHER_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Red Ocher)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RED_OCHER_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Red Ocher) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RED_OCHER_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Red Ocher people were an indigenous people of North America. A series of archaeological sites located in the Upper Great Lakes, the Greater Illinois River Valley, and the Ohio River Valley in the American Midwest have been discovered to be a Red Ocher burial complex, dating from 1000 BC to 400 BC, the Terminal Archaic - Early Woodland period. Characterized as shallow burials located in sandy ridges along river valleys, covered in red ochre or hydrated iron oxide (FeH3O), they contain diagnostic artifacts that include caches of flint points, turkey-tails, and various forms of worked copper. Turkey-tails are large flint blades of a distinct type. It is believed that Red Ocher people spoke an ancestral form of the Algonquian languages. Red ochre has a long history of use in North America; as early as the Folsom tradition during the Paleo-Indian period, certain localities in New Mexico and Wyoming were actively being mined for the substance. The people today known as Red Ocher were first identified by the University of Chicago in 1937. During the late 1950s and early 1960s, the Red Ocher Culture was a topic of great interest among archaeologists who were trying to better define the burial culture through various methods of research. Since then intermittent archaeological works have been published dealing with specific sub-topics within the burial culture and supported by more reliable AMS carbon dates. Nevertheless, many important archaeological questions regarding the Red Ocher burial manifestation and cultural phenomenon are still without answers.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SABBATEAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Sabbatean)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SABBATEAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Sabbatean) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SABBATEAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Sabbateans (Sabbatians) is a complex general term that refers to a variety of followers of, disciples and believers in Sabbatai Zevi (1626-1676), a Jewish rabbi who was proclaimed to be the Jewish Messiah in 1665 by Nathan of Gaza. Vast numbers of Jews in the Jewish diaspora accepted his claims, even after he became a Jewish apostate with his conversion to Islam in 1666. Sabbatai Zevi's followers, both during his "Messiahship" and after his conversion to Islam, are known as Sabbateans. They can be grouped into three: "Maaminim" (believers), "Haberim" (associates), and "Ba'ale Milhamah" (warriors).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFAVIDS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Safavids)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFAVIDS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Safavids) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFAVIDS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Safavid dynasty was one of the most significant ruling dynasties of Persia (modern Iran) after the fall of the Sasanian Empire - following the Muslim conquest of Persia in the seventh century A.D., and "is often considered the beginning of modern Persian history". The Safavid shahs ruled over one of the so-called gunpowder empires, and they ruled one of the greatest Persian empires after the Muslim conquest of Persia and established the Twelver school of Shi'a Islam as the official religion of their empire, marking one of the most important turning points in Muslim history. The Safavid dynasty had its origin in the Safaviyya Sufi order, which was established in the city of Ardabil in the Azerbaijan region. It was of mixed ancestry (Kurdish and Azerbaijani, which included intermarriages with Georgian, Circassian, and Pontic Greek dignitaries). From their base in Ardabil, the Safavids established control over parts of Greater Iran and reasserted the Iranian identity of the region, thus becoming the first native dynasty since the Sasanian Empire to establish a unified Iranian state.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFFARID_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Saffarid)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFFARID_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Saffarid) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFFARID_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Saffarid dynasty was a Muslim Persianate dynasty from Sistan that ruled over parts of eastern Iran, with its capital at Zaranj (a city now in southwestern Afghanistan). Khorasan, Afghanistan and Balochistan from 861 to 1003. The dynasty, of Persian origin, was founded by Ya'qub bin Laith as-Saffar, born in 840 in a small town called Karnin (Qarnin), which was located east of Zaranj and west of Bost, in what is now Afghanistan - a native of Sistan and a local ayyar, who worked as a coppersmith (affar) before becoming a warlord. He seized control of the Sistan region and began conquering most of Iran and Afghanistan, as well as parts of Pakistan, Tajikestan and Uzbekistan. The Saffarids used their capital Zaranj as a base for an aggressive expansion eastward and westward. They first invaded the areas south of the Hindu Kush in Afghanistan and then overthrew the Persian Tahirid dynasty, annexing Khorasan in 873. By the time of Ya'qub's death, he had conquered the Kabul Valley, Sindh, Tocharistan, Makran (Balochistan), Kerman, Fars, Khorasan, and nearly reached Baghdad but then suffered a defeat by the Abbasids.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAKA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Saka)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAKA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Saka) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAKA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Saka was the term used in Persian and Sanskrit sources for the Scythians, a large group of Eastern Iranian nomadic tribes on the Eurasian Steppe. "The regions of Tashkent, Fergana, and Kashgar were inhabited by the people known to the Chinese under the name Sse (ancient pronunciation, Ssek)[needs IPA], to the Persians and Indians as Saka, or Shaka, and to the Greeks as Sakai: our Sakas. They were in fact the 'Scythians of Asia.' They formed a branch of the great Scytho-Sarmatian family; that is, they were nomadic Iranians from the northwestern steppes."</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SARMATIANS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Sarmatians)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SARMATIANS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Sarmatians) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SARMATIANS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Sarmatians were a large confederation of Iranian people during classical antiquity, flourishing from about the 5th century BC to the 4th century AD. They spoke Scythian, an Indo-European language from the Eastern Iranian family. Originating in Central Asia, the Sarmatians started their westward migration around the 6th century BC, coming to dominate the closely related Scythians by the 2nd century BC. The Sarmatians differed from the Scythians in their veneration of the god of fire rather than god of nature, and women's prominent role in warfare, which possibly served as the inspiration for the Amazons. At their greatest reported extent, around 1st century AD, these tribes ranged from the Vistula River to the mouth of the Danube and eastward to the Volga, bordering the shores of the Black and Caspian seas as well as the Caucasus to the south. Their territory, which was known as Sarmatia to Greco-Roman ethnographers, corresponded to the western part of greater Scythia (mostly modern Ukraine and Southern Russia, also to a smaller extent north eastern Balkans around Moldova). According to authors Arrowsmith, Fellowes and Graves Hansard in their book A Grammar of Ancient Geography published in 1832, Sarmatia had two parts, Sarmatia Europea  and Sarmatia Asiatica  covering a combined area of 503,000 sq mi or 1,302,764 km2.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SELJUKS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Seljuks)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SELJUKS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Seljuks) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SELJUKS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Seljuk empire was founded by Tughril Beg (1016-63) in 1037. Tughril was raised by his grandfather, Seljuk-Beg, who was in a high position in the Oghuz Yabgu State. Seljuk gave his name to both the Seljuk empire and the Seljuk dynasty. The Seljuks united the fractured political scene of the eastern Islamic world and played a key role in the first and second crusades. Highly Persianized in culture and language, the Seljuks also played an important role in the development of the Turko-Persian tradition, even exporting Persian culture to Anatolia. The settlement of Turkic tribes in the northwestern peripheral parts of the empire, for the strategic military purpose of fending off invasions from neighboring states, led to the progressive Turkicization of those areas.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEMANG_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Semang)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEMANG_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Semang) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEMANG_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Semang are a Negrito ethnic group of the Malay Peninsula. They are found in Perak, Kedah and Pahang of Malaysia. During the colonial British administration, Orang Asli living in the northern Malay Peninsula were classified as Sakai. Lowland Semang tribes are also known as Sakai, although this term is considered to be derogatory by the Semang people. They have been recorded to have lived here since before the 3rd century. They are ethnologically described as nomadic hunter-gatherers. See also Bajaus and Aetas.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SENEGALI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Senegali)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SENEGALI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Senegali) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SENEGALI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Senegal is a country in West Africa. Senegal's economical and political capital is Dakar. It is the westernmost country in the mainland of the Old World, or Eurafrasia, and owes its name to the Sénégal River, which borders it to the east and north. The name "Senegal" comes from the Wolof "Sunuu Gaal," which means "Our Boat." Senegal covers a land area of almost 197,000 square kilometres (76,000 sq mi) and has an estimated population of about 13 million. The climate is Sahelian, but there is a rainy season. The territory of modern Senegal has been inhabited by various ethnic groups since the prehistoric era. Organized kingdoms emerged around the seventh century, and parts of the country were ruled by prominent regional empires such as the Wolof. The present state of Senegal has its roots in European colonialism, which began during the mid-15th century, when various European powers began competing for trade in the area. The establishment of coastal trading posts gradually gave way to control of the mainland, culminating in French rule of the area by the 19th century, albeit amid much local resistance. Senegal peacefully attained independence from France in 1960, and has since been among the more politically stable countries in Africa.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SENNAR_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Sennar)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SENNAR_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Sennar) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SENNAR_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Funj Sultanate of Sennar (sometimes spelled Sinnar), known in Sudanese traditions as the Blue Sultanate was a sultanate in the north of Sudan, named Funj after the ethnic group of its dynasty or Sinnar (or Sennar) after its capital, which ruled a substantial area of northeast Africa between 1504 and 1821. In the 15th century the part of Nubia previously controlled by Makuria was home to a number of small states and subject to frequent incursions by desert nomads. The situation in Alodia is less well known, but it also seems as though that state had collapsed. The area was reunified under Abdallah Jamma, the gatherer, who came from the eastern regions that had grown wealthy and powerful from the trade on the Red Sea. To him is ascribed the capture of Soba, which sank into unimportance: according to Reubeni, in the time of 'Amara Dunqas it was in ruins. 'Abdallah's status as Muslim hero is confirmed by traditions representing him marrying the daughter of a Hijazi holy man called Alshikh Hamd Abou Dunana who was burned in Abu Delaig, and as the eponymous ancestor of the ruling clan, the 'Abdallab. </English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SERBIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Serbian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SERBIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Serbian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SERBIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Following the Slavic migrations to the Balkans from the 6th century onwards, Serbs established several states in the early Middle Ages. The Serbian Kingdom obtained recognition by Rome and Constantinople in 1217; it reached its peak in 1346 as a relatively short-lived Serbian Empire. By the mid-16th century, the entire territory of modern-day Serbia was annexed by the Ottoman Empire, at times interrupted by the Habsburgs. In the early 19th century, the Serbian Revolution established the nation-state as the region's first constitutional monarchy, which subsequently expanded its territory. Following disastrous casualties in World War I, and subsequent unification of Habsburg crownland of Vojvodina with Serbia, the country co-founded Yugoslavia with other South Slavic peoples, which would exist in various political formations until the Yugoslav Wars of the 1990s, which had devastating effects for the region. As a result, Serbia formed a union with Montenegro in 1992, which broke apart in 2006, when Serbia again became an independent country. In 2008 the parliament of Kosovo, Serbia's southern province with an Albanian ethnic majority, declared independence, with mixed responses from the international community.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SICAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Sican)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SICAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Sican) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SICAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Sican culture is the name that archaeologist Izumi Shimada gave to the culture that inhabited what is now the north coast of Peru between about AD 750 and 1375. According to Shimada, Sican means "temple of the moon". The Sican culture is also referred to as Lambayeque culture, after the name of the region in Peru. It succeeded the Moche culture. There is still controversy among archeologists and anthropologists over whether the two are separate cultures. The Sican culture is divided into three major periods based on cultural changes as evidenced in archeological artifacts.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SICILIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Sicilian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SICILIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Sicilian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SICILIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>About 750 BC, the Greeks began to live in Sicily, establishing many important settlements. The most important colony was Syracuse; other significant ones were Akragas, Selinunte, Gela, Himera, and Zancle. The native Sicani and Sicel peoples were absorbed by the Hellenic culture with relative ease, and the area was part of Magna Graecia along with the rest of southern Italy, which the Greeks had also colonised. Sicily was very fertile, and the introduction of olives and grape vines flourished, creating a great deal of profitable trading; a significant part of Greek culture on the island was that of Greek religion, and many temples were built across Sicily, such as the Valley of the Temples at Agrigento. Politics on the island was intertwined with that of Greece; Syracuse became desired by the Athenians, who, during the Peloponnesian War, set out on the Sicilian Expedition. Syracuse gained Sparta and Corinth as allies and, as a result, the Athenian expedition was defeated. The Athenian army and ships were destroyed, with most of the survivors being sold into slavery.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SINTASHTA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Sintashta)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SINTASHTA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Sintashta) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SINTASHTA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Sintashtais an archaeological site in Chelyabinsk Oblast, Russia. It is the remains of a fortified settlement dating to the Bronze Age, c. 2800-1600 BC, and is the type site of the Sintashta culture. The site has been characterised "fortified metallurgical industrial center". Sintashta is situated in the steppe just east of the Ural Mountains. The site is named for the adjacent Sintashta River, a tributary to the Tobol. The shifting course of the river over time has destroyed half of the site, leaving behind thirty one of the approximately fifty or sixty houses in the settlement. The settlement consisted of rectangular houses arranged in a circle 140 m in diameter and surrounded by a timber-reinforced earthen wall with gate towers and a deep ditch on its exterior. The fortifications at Sintashta and similar settlements such as Arkaim were of unprecedented scale for the steppe region. There is evidence of copper and bronze metallurgy taking place in every house excavated at Sintashta, again an unprecedented intensity of metallurgical production for the steppe. Early Abashevo culture ceramic styles strongly influenced Sintashta ceramics. Due to the assimilation of tribes in the region of the Urals, such as the Pit-grave, Catacomb, Poltavka, and northern Abashevo into the Novokumak horizon, it would seem inaccurate to provide Sintashta with a purely Aryan attribution. In the origin of Sintashta, the Abashevo culture would play an important role.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SLOVENIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Slovenian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SLOVENIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Slovenian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SLOVENIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Historically, the current territory of Slovenia was part of many different state formations, including the Roman Empire and the Holy Roman Empire, followed by the Habsburg Monarchy. In October 1918, the Slovenes exercised self-determination for the first time by co-founding the internationally unrecognized State of Slovenes, Croats and Serbs, which merged that December with the Kingdom of Serbia into the Kingdom of Serbs, Croats and Slovenes (renamed Kingdom of Yugoslavia in 1929). During World War II, Slovenia was occupied and annexed by Germany, Italy, and Hungary, with a tiny area transferred to the Independent State of Croatia, a Nazi puppet state. Afterward, it was a founding member of the Federal People's Republic of Yugoslavia, later renamed the Socialist Federal Republic of Yugoslavia, a communist state which was the only country in the Eastern Bloc not part of the Warsaw Pact. In June 1991, after the introduction of multi-party representative democracy, Slovenia split from Yugoslavia and became an independent country. In 2004, it entered NATO and the European Union; in 2007 became the first former Communist country to join the Eurozone; and in 2010 joined the OECD, a global association of high-income developed countries.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUDANESE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Sudanese)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUDANESE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Sudanese) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUDANESE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Sudan was home to numerous ancient civilizations, such as the Kingdom of Kush, Kerma, Nobatia, Alodia, Makuria, Meroë and others, most of which flourished along the Nile. During the pre-dynastic period Nubia and Nagadan Upper Egypt were identical, simultaneously evolved systems of pharaonic kingship by 3300 BC. By virtue of its proximity to Egypt, the Sudan participated in the wider history of the Near East inasmuch as it was Christianized by the 6th century, and Islamized in the 15th. As a result of Christianization, the Old Nubian language stands as the oldest recorded Nilo-Saharan language (earliest records dating to the 9th century). Sudan was the largest country in Africa and the Arab world until 2011, when South Sudan separated into an independent country, following an independence referendum. Sudan is now the third largest country in Africa (after Algeria and the Democratic Republic of the Congo) and also the third largest country in the Arab world (after Algeria and Saudi Arabia).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUNDANESE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Sundanese)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUNDANESE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Sundanese) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUNDANESE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Sundanese are an ethnic group native to the western part of the Indonesian island of Java. They number approximately 40 million, and are the second most populous of all the nation's ethnicities. The Sundanese are predominantly Muslim. In their own language, Sundanese, the group is referred to as Urang Sunda, and Orang Sunda or Suku Sunda in the national language, Indonesian. The Sundanese have traditionally been concentrated in the provinces of West Java, Banten, Jakarta, and the western part of Central Java. Sundanese migrants can also be found in Lampung and South Sumatra. The provinces of Central Java and East Java are home to the Javanese, Indonesia's largest ethnic group. Sundanese culture has a number of similarities with Javanese culture, however it differs by being more overtly Islamic, with less Hindu-Buddhist elements, and has a less rigid system of social hierarchy. The common identity that binds Sundanese together is their language and culture.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SURINAM_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Surinam)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SURINAM_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Surinam) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SURINAM_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Suriname is a sovereign state on the northeastern Atlantic coast of South America. It is bordered by French Guiana to the east, Guyana to the west and Brazil to the south. At just under 165,000 km2 (64,000 sq mi), it is the smallest country in South America. Suriname has a population of approximately 566,000, most of whom live on the country's north coast, in and around the capital and largest city, Paramaribo. Originally inhabited by a number of indigenous tribes, Suriname was explored and contested by European powers before coming under Dutch rule in the late 17th century. In 1948 the country gained autonomy and in 1954 it became one of the constituent countries of the Kingdom of the Netherlands. On 25 November 1975, the country of Suriname left the Kingdom of the Netherlands to become an independent state, nonetheless maintaining close economic, diplomatic, and cultural ties to its former colonizer. Suriname is considered to be a culturally Caribbean country, and is a member of the Caribbean Community (CARICOM). It is an officially Dutch-speaking country, at the same time, Sranan, an English-based creole language, is the most widely used lingua franca. Suriname is the only territory outside Europe where Dutch is spoken by a majority of the population. The people of Suriname are among the most diverse in the world, spanning a multitude of ethnic, religious, and linguistic groups.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDISH_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Swedish)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDISH_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Swedish) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SWEDISH_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Germanic peoples have inhabited Sweden since prehistoric times, emerging into history as the Geats/Götar and Swedes/Svear and constituting the sea peoples known as the Norsemen. Sweden emerged as an independent and unified country during the Middle Ages. In the 17th century, it expanded its territories to form the Swedish Empire, which became one of the great powers of Europe until the early 18th century. Swedish territories outside the Scandinavian Peninsula were gradually lost during the 18th and 19th centuries, beginning with the annexation of present-day Finland by Russia in 1809. The last war in which Sweden was directly involved was in 1814, when Norway was militarily forced into personal union. Since then, Sweden has been at peace, maintaining an official policy of neutrality in foreign affairs. The union with Norway was peacefully dissolved in 1905, leading to Sweden's current borders. Though it was formally neutral through both world wars, Sweden engaged in humanitarian efforts, such as taking in refugees from German-occupied Europe. After the end of the Cold War, Sweden joined the European Union on 1 January 1995, but declined NATO membership.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAGALOG_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tagalog)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAGALOG_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tagalog) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAGALOG_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Tagalog people are a major ethnic group in the Philippines. They form a majority in Manila, Marinduque and southern Luzon, and a plurality in Central Luzon and the islands of Mindoro, Palawan, and Romblon. The Tagalog are part of the Austronesian migration from Taiwan into the Philippines at around 4000 BCE. The earliest written record of the Tagalog is a 9th-century document known as the Laguna Copperplate Inscription which is about a remission of debt on behalf of the ruler of Tagalog Tondo. Contact with the rest of Southeast Asia led to the creation Baybayin later used in the book Doctrina Cristiana which is written by the 16th century Spanish colonizers. The Tagalog played an active role during the Philippine Revolution and many of its leaders were either from Manila or surrounding provinces. The Katipunan once intended to name the Philippines as "Katagalugan" or the Tagalog Republic.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAIRONA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tairona)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAIRONA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tairona) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAIRONA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Tairona was a group of chiefdoms in the region of Sierra Nevada de Santa Marta in present-day Cesar, Magdalena and La Guajira Departments of Colombia, South America, which goes back at least to the 1st century CE and had significant demographic growth around the 11th century.The Tairona people formed one of the two principal linguistic groups of the Chibcha family, the other being the Muisca. Genetic and archaeological evidence shows a relatively dense occupation of the region by at least 200 BCE. Pollen data compiled by Luisa Fernanda Herrera in the 1980 shows considerable deforestation and the use of cultigens such as yuca and maiz since possibly 1200 BCE. However, occupation of the Colombian Caribbean coast by sedentary or semi-sedentary populations have been documented to have occurred by c. 4000 BCE. Ethnohistorical data shows that initial contact with the Spanish was tolerated by the Tairona but by the 1600 CE confrontations built and a small part of the Tairona population moved to the higher stretches of the Sierra Nevada de Santa Marta. This movement allowed them to evade the worst of the Spanish colonial system during the 17th and 18th centuries. The indigenous Kogui, Wiwa, Arhuacos (Ijka, Ifca) and Cancuamo people who live in the area today are believed to be direct descendants of the Tairona.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAJIKS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tajiks)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAJIKS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tajiks) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAJIKS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Tajiks are an Iranian people, speaking a variety of Persian, concentrated in the Oxus Basin, the Farana valley (Tajikistan and parts of Uzbekistan) and on both banks of the upper Oxus, i.e., the Pamir Mountains (Mountain Badaksan, in Tajikistan) and northeastern Afghanistan (Badaksan). Historically the Tajiks were agriculturalists. According to Richard Nelson Frye, a leading historian of Iranian and Central Asian history, the Persian migration to Central Asia may be considered the beginning of the modern Tajik nation, and ethnic Persians, along with some elements of East-Iranian Bactrians and Sogdians, as the main ancestors of modern Tajiks. In later works, Frye expands on the complexity of the historical origins of the Tajiks. In a 1996 publication, Frye explains that many "factors must be taken into account in explaining the evolution of the peoples whose remnants are the Tajiks in Central Asia" and that "the peoples of Central Asia, whether Iranian or Turkic speaking, have one culture, one religion, one set of social values and traditions with only language separating them."</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TANG_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tang)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TANG_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tang) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TANG_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Tang dynasty, with its capital at Chang'an (present-day Xi'an), which at the time was the most populous city in the world, is generally regarded as a high point in Chinese civilization, and a golden age of cosmopolitan culture. Its territory, acquired through the military campaigns of its early rulers, rivaled that of the Han dynasty. In two censuses of the 7th and 8th centuries, the Tang records estimated the population by number of registered households at about 50 million people. Yet, even when the central government was breaking down and unable to compile an accurate census of the population in the 9th century, it is estimated that the population had grown by then to about 80 million people.[b] With its large population base, the dynasty was able to raise professional and conscripted armies of hundreds of thousands of troops to contend with nomadic powers in dominating Inner Asia and the lucrative trade routes along the Silk Road. Various kingdoms and states paid tribute to the Tang court, while the Tang also conquered or subdued several regions which it indirectly controlled through a protectorate system. Besides political hegemony, the Tang also exerted a powerful cultural influence over neighboring states such as those in Korea, Japan, and Vietnam.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TANZANIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tanzanian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TANZANIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tanzanian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TANZANIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Tanzania is a country in East Africa within the African Great Lakes region. It is bordered by Kenya and Uganda to the north; Rwanda, Burundi, and the Democratic Republic of the Congo to the west; Zambia, Malawi, and Mozambique to the south; and the Indian Ocean to the east. Kilimanjaro, Africa's highest mountain, is in northeastern Tanzania. Tanzania is one of the poorest countries in the world. Tanzania's population of 51.82 million (2014) is diverse, composed of several ethnic, linguistic, and religious groups. Tanzania is a presidential constitutional republic, and since 1996, its official capital has been Dodoma, where the President's Office, the National Assembly, and some government ministries are located. Dar es Salaam, the former capital, retains most government offices and is the country's largest city, principal port, and leading commercial centre.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TASMANIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tasmanian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TASMANIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tasmanian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TASMANIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Evidence indicates the presence of Aborigines in Tasmania about 40,000 years ago. Rising sea levels cut Tasmania off from mainland Australia about 10,000 years ago and by the time of European contact, the Aboriginal people in Tasmania had nine major nations, or ethnic groups. At the time of the British occupation and colonisation in 1803 the indigenous population was estimated at between 3000 and 10,000. Historian Lyndall Ryan's analysis of population studies led her to conclude that there were about 7000 spread throughout the island's nine nations; Nicholas Clements, citing research by N.J.B Plomley and Rhys Jones, settled on a figure of 3000 to 4000. They engaged in fire-stick farming, hunted game including kangaroo and wallabies, caught seals, mutton-birds, shellfish and fish and lived as nine separate "nations" on the island, which they knew as "Trouwunna".</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TATARS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tatars)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TATARS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tatars) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TATARS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Tatars are Turkic people living in Asia and Europe who were one of the five major tribal confederations (khanlig) in the Mongolian plateau in the 12th century AD. The name "Tatar" first appears in written form on the Kul Tigin monument as Old Turkic. Today Tatars named people who speak the Turkic speaking language families. After the establishment of the Mongol Empire under Genghis Khan in 1206, the Empire subjugated the Tatars. Under the leadership of Genghis Khan's grandson Batu Khan (c. 1207-1255), the Mongols moved westwards, driving with them many of the Mongol Turkic peoples toward the plains of Russia. The "Tatar" clan still exists among the Mongols and Hazaras. Russians and Europeans used the name Tatar to denote Mongols as well as Turkic peoples under Mongol rule (especially in the Golden Horde). Later, it applied to any Turkic- or Mongolic-speaking people encountered by Russians. Eventually however, the name became associated with the Turkic Muslims of Ukraine and Russia, namely, the descendants of Muslim Volga Bulgars, Kipchaks, and Cumans, and Turkicized Mongols or Turko-Mongols (Nogais), as well as other Turkic-speaking peoples (Siberian Tatars, Qasim Tatars, Mishar Tatars) in the territory of the former Russian Empire (and as such generally includes all Northwestern Turkic-speaking peoples).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_THRACIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Thracian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_THRACIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Thracian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_THRACIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Thracians were a group of Indo-European tribes inhabiting a large area in Southeastern Europe. They spoke the Thracian language - a scarcely attested branch of the Indo-European language family. The study of Thracians and Thracian culture is known as Thracology. In the first decade of the sixth century BC, the Persians invaded Thrace and made it part of their satrapy Skudra. Thracians were forced to join the invasions of European Scythia and Greece. According Herodotus, the Bithynian Thracians also had to contribute a large contingent to Xerxes' invasion of Greece in 480 BC. Subjugation of Macedonia was part of Persian military operations initiated by Darius the Great (521-486) in 513 - after immense preparations - a huge Achaemenid army invaded the Balkans and tried to defeat the European Scythians roaming to the north of the Danube River. Darius' army subjugated several Thracian peoples at the same time, and virtually all other regions that touch the European part of the Black Sea, such as parts currently of Bulgaria, Romania, Ukraine, and Russia, before it returned to Asia Minor. Darius left in Europe one of his commanders named Megabazus whose task was to accomplish conquests in the Balkans. The Persian troops subjugated gold-rich Thrace, the coastal Greek cities, as well as defeating and conquering the powerful Paeonians. Finally, Megabazus sent envoys to Amyntas, King of Macedon demanding acceptation of Persian domination, which the Macedonian accepted. At this time, many if not most Thracians fell under Persian rule.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_THREE_KINGDOMS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Three Kingdoms)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_THREE_KINGDOMS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Three Kingdoms) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_THREE_KINGDOMS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Three Kingdoms (AD 220-280) was the tripartite division of China between the states of Wei, Shu, and Wu, following the Han dynasty and preceding the Jin dynasty. The term "Three Kingdoms" itself is something of a mistranslation, since each state was eventually headed not by a king, but by an emperor who claimed legitimate succession from the Han dynasty. Nevertheless, the term "Three Kingdoms" has become standard among sinologists. To further distinguish the three states from other historical Chinese states of similar names, historians have added a relevant character: Wei is also known as Cao Wei, Shu is also known as Shu Han, and Wu is also known as Dong (or Eastern) Wu. In a strict academic sense, the period of the Three Kingdoms refers to the period between the foundation of the state of Wei in 220 AD and the conquest of the state of Wu by the Jin dynasty in 280. The earlier, "unofficial" part of the period, from 184 to 220, was marked by chaotic infighting between warlords in various parts of China. The middle part of the period, from 220 and 263, was marked by a more militarily stable arrangement between three rival states of Wei, Shu, and Wu. The later part of the era was marked by the conquest of Shu by Wei (263), the overthrow of Wei by the Jin dynasty (265), and the conquest of Wu by the Jin (280).</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TIWI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tiwi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TIWI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tiwi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TIWI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Tiwi people are one of the many Indigenous groups of Australia. Nearly 2,500 Tiwi live in the Bathurst and Melville Islands, which make up the Tiwi Islands. Tiwi art and language are markedly distinct from those of nearby Arnhem Land. Compared with Arnhem Land art, Tiwi art often appears to be abstract and geometric. With its strong patterns and use of colour, Tiwi art is considered very attractive and highly collectible.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOBA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Toba)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOBA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Toba) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOBA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Toba or Qom are an ethnic group in Argentina, Bolivia and Paraguay. They are part of a larger group of indigenous inhabitants of the Gran Chaco region, called the Guaycurues. As of 2005, there are 47,951 Toba in Argentina, living in the provinces of Chaco, Formosa and Santa Fe. The Toba name themselves Qom-lik, meaning simply "people". The name toba is of Guaraní origin and means "big forehead", which is also the name given to them by the first Spanish settlers (frentones). This is because the Toba cut their hair short in the front of the head as a sign of mourning.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOTONAC_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Totonac)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOTONAC_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Totonac) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOTONAC_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Totonac people resided in the eastern coastal and mountainous regions of Mexico at the time of the Spanish arrival in 1519. Today they reside in the states of Veracruz, Puebla, and Hidalgo. They are one of the possible builders of the Pre-Columbian city of El Tajín, and further maintained quarters in Teotihuacan (a city which they claim to have built). Until the mid-19th century they were the world's main producers of vanilla.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TRANSOXANIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Transoxanian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TRANSOXANIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Transoxanian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TRANSOXANIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Transoxiana (also spelled Transoxania), is the ancient name used for the portion of Central Asia corresponding approximately with modern-day Uzbekistan, Tajikistan, southern Kyrgyzstan and southwest Kazakhstan. Geographically, it is the region between the Amu Darya (Ancient Greek: Oxos) and Syr Darya rivers. The area had been known to the Romans as Transoxania (Land beyond the Oxus), to the Arabs as Mawarannahr (Land Beyond the River), and to the Iranians as Turan, a term used in the Persian national epic Shahnameh. Transoxiana's major cities and cultural centres are Samarkand and Bukhara. Both are in the southern portion of Transoxiana, (though still to the north of the Amu Darya itself, on the river Zeravshan), and the majority of the region was dry but fertile plains. Both cities remained centres of Persian culture and civilisation after the Islamic conquest of Iran, and played a crucial role in the revival of Persian culture with establishment of the Samanid dynasty.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TUCANO_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tucano)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TUCANO_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tucano) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TUCANO_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Tucano people (sometimes spelt Tukano) are a group of indigenous South Americans living in the northwestern Amazon, along the Vaupes River and the surrounding area. They are present in both Colombia and Brazil, although most live on the Colombian side of the border. They are usually described as being made up of many separate tribes, although the appellation is somewhat problematic due to the complex social and linguistic structure of the region.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TUNGUS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tungus)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TUNGUS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tungus) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TUNGUS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Tungusic peoples are the peoples who speak Tungusic languages. They inhabit Eastern Siberia and are recognized as distinct from Mongols and Turkic peoples. The first European description of a Tungusic people was by the Dutch traveller Isaac Massa in 1612. The word originated in Tunguska, a region of eastern Siberia bounded on the west by the Tunguska rivers and on the east by the Pacific Ocean. The largest group of Tungusic peoples are the Manchu people, who number around 10 million. They are originally from Manchuria, which is now Northeast China, but following their conquest of China in the 17th century, they have been almost totally assimilated into the main Han Chinese population of China. This process accelerated especially during the 20th century. The Xibe people are a Manchu subgroup.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TUNISIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Tunisian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TUNISIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Tunisian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TUNISIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>In ancient times, Tunisia was primarily inhabited by Berbers. Phoenician immigration began in the 12th century BC; these immigrants founded Carthage. A rival to Greece that almost destroyed Rome in the Second Punic War, Carthage was eventually defeated by the Romans in the Battle of Carthage of 149 BC. Romans brought Christianity and architecture to Tunisia, including the El Djem amphitheater. Tunisia was conquered by Arabs in the first century of Islam, followed by the Ottomans between 1534 and 1574. The Ottomans held sway for over three hundred years. The French conquest of Tunisia occurred in 1881. Tunisia gained independence with Habib Bourguiba and declared the Tunisian Republic in 1957. In 2011, the Tunisian Revolution resulted in the overthrow of President Zine El Abidine Ben Ali, followed by parliamentary elections. The country voted for parliament again on 26 October 2014, and for President on 23 November 2014.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TURKISH_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Turkish)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TURKISH_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Turkish) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TURKISH_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Turkey is a parliamentary republic in Eurasia, largely located in Western Asia, with the smaller portion of Eastern Thrace in Southeast Europe. Turkey is bordered by eight countries: Syria and Iraq to the south; Iran, Armenia, and the Azerbaijani exclave of Nakhchivan to the east; Georgia to the northeast; Bulgaria to the northwest; and Greece to the west. The Black Sea is to the north, the Mediterranean Sea to the south, and the Aegean Sea to the west. The Bosphorus, the Sea of Marmara, and the Dardanelles (which together form the Turkish Straits) demarcate the boundary between Thrace and Anatolia; they also separate Europe and Asia. Turkey's location at the crossroads of Europe and Asia makes it a country of significant geostrategic importance. Starting from the late 13th century, the Ottomans united Anatolia and created an empire encompassing much of Southeastern Europe, Western Asia and North Africa, becoming a major power in Eurasia and Africa during the early modern period. The empire reached the peak of its power between the 15th and 17th centuries, especially during the 1520-66 reign of Suleiman the Magnificent. After the second Ottoman siege of Vienna in 1683 and the end of the Great Turkish War in 1699, the Ottoman Empire entered a long period of decline. The Tanzimat reforms of the 19th century, which aimed to modernize the Ottoman state, proved to be inadequate in most fields, and failed to stop the dissolution of the empire. The Ottoman Empire entered World War I (1914-18) on the side of the Central Powers and was ultimately defeated. During the war, major atrocities were committed by the Ottoman government against its Armenian, Assyrian and Pontic Greek citizens. Following the war, the huge conglomeration of territories and peoples that formerly comprised the Ottoman Empire was divided into several new states. The Turkish War of Independence (1919-22), initiated by Mustafa Kemal Atatürk and his colleagues in Anatolia, resulted in the establishment of the modern Republic of Turkey in 1923, with Atatürk as its first president.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UKRAINIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Ukrainian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UKRAINIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Ukrainian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UKRAINIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The territory of modern Ukraine has been inhabited since 32,000 BC. During the Middle Ages, the area was a key centre of East Slavic culture, with the powerful state of Kievan Rus' forming the basis of Ukrainian identity. Following its fragmentation in the 13th century, the territory was contested, ruled and divided by a variety of powers, including Lithuania, Poland, the Ottoman Empire, Austria-Hungary, and Russia. A Cossack republic emerged and prospered during the 17th and 18th centuries, but its territory was eventually split between Poland and the Russian Empire, and later submerged fully into Russia. Two brief periods of independence occurred during the 20th century, once near the end of World War I and another during World War II, but both occasions would ultimately see Ukraine's territories conquered and consolidated into a Soviet republic, a situation that persisted until 1991, when Ukraine gained its independence from the Soviet Union in the aftermath of its dissolution at the end of the Cold War.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_URUGUAYAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Uruguayan)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_URUGUAYAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Uruguayan) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_URUGUAYAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Uruguay was inhabited by the Charrúa people for approximately 4000 years before the Portuguese invaded. Portugal established Colonia del Sacramento, one of the oldest European settlements in the country, in 1680. Montevideo was founded as a military stronghold by the Spanish in the early 18th century, signifying the competing claims over the region. Uruguay won its independence between 1811 and 1828, following a four-way struggle between Spain, Portugal, Argentina and Brazil. It remained subject to foreign influence and intervention throughout the 19th century, with the military playing a recurring role in domestic politics until the late 20th century. Modern Uruguay is a democratic constitutional republic, with a president who serves as both head of state and head of government.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UZBEKS_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Uzbeks)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UZBEKS_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Uzbeks) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UZBEKS_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Uzbeks (Ozbek, pl. Ozbeklar) are the largest Turkic ethnic group in Central Asia. They comprise the majority population of Uzbekistan but are also found as a minority group in Afghanistan, Tajikistan, Kyrgyzstan, Kazakhstan, Turkmenistan, Russia and China. Uzbek diaspora communities also exist in Turkey, Saudi Arabia, and Pakistan. Before, 5th century, what is today's Uzbekistan was part of Sogdia, mainly inhabited by Sogdians, an Indo-Iranian people. It was part of the Achaemenid Empire and later part of Sasanian Empire. From 5th to 6th century, what is today's Uzbekistan was part of the Hephthalite Empire. From 6th to 8th century, what is today's Uzbekistan was under the rule of Göktürk Khanate. Turkic and Chinese migration into central Asia occurred during the Chinese Tang Dynasty, and Chinese armies commanded by Turkic generals stationed in large parts of central Asia. But Chinese influence ended with the An Lushan rebellion. From the 9th century on, Transoxania was under the rule of Turkic Kara-Khanid Khanate, their arrival in Transoxania signalled a definitive shift from Iranian to Turkic predominance in Central Asia. Kara-Khanid ruler Sultan Satuq Bughra Khan was the first Turkic ruler to convert Islam, most people of Central Asia soon followed. In the 12th century, Transoxania was conquered by Qara Khitai (Western Liao), a sinicized Khitan dynasty, they brought to Central Asia the Chinese system of government. In the 13th century, Kara-Khanid Khanate was destroyed by the Turkic Khwarazmian dynasty, a vassal of the Qara Khitai.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VALDIVIA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Valdivia)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VALDIVIA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Valdivia) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VALDIVIA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Valdivia Culture is one of the oldest settled cultures recorded in the Americas. It emerged from the earlier Las Vegas culture and thrived on the Santa Elena peninsula near the modern-day town of Valdivia, Ecuador between 3500 BC and 1800 BC. The Valdivia culture was discovered in 1956 by the Ecuadorian archeologist Emilio Estrada. The Valdivia lived in a community that built its houses in a circle or oval around a central plaza and were sedentary people that lived off farming and fishing, though occasionally they went hunting for deer. From the remains that have been found, it has been determined that Valdivians cultivated maize, kidney beans, squash, cassava, chili peppers and cotton plants, the latter of which was used to make clothing.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VANATU_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Vanatu)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VANATU_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Vanatu) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VANATU_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Vanuatu is a Pacific island nation located in the South Pacific Ocean. The archipelago, which is of volcanic origin, is some 1,750 kilometres (1,090 mi) east of northern Australia, 500 kilometres (310 mi) northeast of New Caledonia, east of New Guinea, southeast of the Solomon Islands, and west of Fiji. Vanuatu was first inhabited by Melanesian people. The first Europeans to visit the islands were a Spanish expedition led by Portuguese navigator Fernandes de Queirós, who arrived on the largest island in 1606. He then claimed the archipelago for Spain, as part of the colonial Spanish East Indies, and named it Austrialia del Espiritu Santo.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VANDAL_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Vandal)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VANDAL_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Vandal) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VANDAL_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Vandals were an East Germanic tribe, or group of tribes, who were first heard of in southern Poland, but later moved around Europe establishing kingdoms in Spain and later North Africa in the 5th century. The Vandals are believed to have migrated from southern Scandinavia to the area between the lower Oder and Vistula rivers during the 2nd century BC and to have settled in Silesia from around 120 BC. They are associated with the Przeworsk culture and were possibly the same people as the Lugii. Expanding into Dacia during the Marcomannic Wars and to Pannonia during the Crisis of the Third Century, the Vandals were confined to Pannonia by the Goths around 330 AD, where they received permission to settle by Constantine the Great. Around 400 the Vandals were pushed westwards again, this time by the Huns, crossing the Rhine into Gaul along with other tribes in 406. In 409, the Vandals crossed the Pyrenees into the Iberian Peninsula, where their main groups, the Hasdingi and the Silingi, settled in Gallaecia (northwest) and Baetica (south central) respectively.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAUDI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Saudi)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAUDI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Saudi) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAUDI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The area of modern-day Saudi Arabia formerly consisted of four distinct regions: Hejaz, Najd, and parts of Eastern Arabia (Al-Ahsa) and Southern Arabia ('Asir). The Kingdom of Saudi Arabia was founded in 1932 by Ibn Saud. He united the four regions into a single state through a series of conquests beginning in 1902 with the capture of Riyadh, the ancestral home of his family, the House of Saud. The country has since been an absolute monarchy, effectively a hereditary dictatorship governed along Islamic lines. The ultra-conservative Wahhabism religious movement within Sunni Islam has been called "the predominant feature of Saudi culture", with its global spreading largely financed by the oil and gas trade. Saudi Arabia is sometimes called "the Land of the Two Holy Mosques" in reference to Al-Masjid al-Haram (in Mecca), and Al-Masjid an-Nabawi (in Medina), the two holiest places in Islam. The Kingdom has a total population of 28.7 million, of which 20 million are Saudi nationals and 8 million are foreigners.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALLACHIAN_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Wallachian)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALLACHIAN_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Wallachian) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALLACHIAN_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Wallachia was founded as a principality in the early 14th century by Basarab I, after a rebellion against Charles I of Hungary, although the first mention of the territory of Wallachia west of the river Olt dates to a charter given to the voivode Seneslau in 1246 by Béla IV of Hungary. In 1417, Wallachia accepted the suzerainty of the Ottoman Empire; this lasted until the 19th century, albeit with brief periods of Russian occupation between 1768 and 1854. In 1859, Wallachia united with Moldavia to form the United Principalities, which adopted the name Romania in 1866 and officially became the Kingdom of Romania in 1881. Later, in 1918, Transylvania was ceded by the Treaty of Trianon from Hungary to the Kingdom of Romania, forming the modern Romanian state.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WARAY_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Waray)</English>
		<German>
			<Text>Kultur Waray:Kultur Waray:Kultur Waray:Kultur Waray</Text>
			<Gender>Female</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WARAY_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Waray) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WARAY_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Waray people are a subgroup of the Visayan people whose primary language is the Waray-Waray language, an Austronesian language native to the islands of Samar, Leyte and Biliran, which together comprise the Eastern Visayan region of the Philippines. Waray people inhabit the whole island of Samar and there they are called Samareños while on the island of Leyte they are called Leyteños. On Leyte island, Waray people occupy only the northern part of the island as it is divided by a mountain range in the middle of the island. Hence the language division between the Waray-Waray speaking people in the northern part and the Cebuano speaking people in the southern part. On the island of Biliran, Waray-Waray speaking people live in the eastern part of the island facing the island of Samar. They are commonly referred to using the Waray-Waray term Biliranon. On the island of Ticao, which belongs to the province of Masbate in the Bicol region, Waray-Waray speaking people live in most parts of the island. They are commonly referred to as Ticaonon. However, the Ticaonon have their affinity with the Bicolano speaking people of Masbate island as it is their home province. The Bicol and Waray-Waray languages are more similar in vocabulary to each other than to the Cebuano language.</English>
		<German>Bei den [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Waray[COLOR_REVERT] handelt es sich um eine Untergruppe aus dem Volk der Visaya, die auf den philippinischen Inseln Samar, Leyte und Biliran heimisch ist. Die Waray sind Nachfahren der austronesischsprachigen Einwanderer, die in der Eisenzeit auf die Philippinen kamen. Sie waren die Herrscher der Meere und betätigten sich zeitweise auch als Piraten und griffen Küstendörfer an. Ihre Gefangenen wurden in eine Art Knechtschaft gezwungen und mussten in der Landwirtschaft arbeiten oder Kriegsdienst leisten. Damit ähnelt die Geschichte der Waray sehr der der Wikinger in Nordeuropa.[NEWLINE]Die Waray waren die ersten Filipinos, die 1521 von den Europäern unter Ferdinand Magellan entdeckt wurden. Paradoxerweise konvertierten sie zwar als eine der ersten philippinischen Ethnien zum Christentum, behielten aber trotzdem parallel noch am längsten ihre traditionellen heidnischen Praktiken bei.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WARI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Wari)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WARI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Wari) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WARI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Wari (Spanish: Huari) were a Middle Horizon civilization that flourished in the south-central Andes and coastal area of modern-day Peru, from about AD 500 to 1000. (The Wari culture is not to be confused with the modern ethnic group and language known as Wari', with which it has no known link.) Wari, as the former capital city was called, is located 11 km (6.8 mi) north-east of the modern city of Ayacucho, Peru. This city was the center of a civilization that covered much of the highlands and coast of modern Peru. The best-preserved remnants, beside the Wari Ruins, are the recently discovered Northern Wari ruins near the city of Chiclayo, and Cerro Baul in Moquegua. Also well-known are the Wari ruins of Pikillaqta ("Flea Town"), a short distance south-east of Cuzco en route to Lake Titicaca.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WAYUU_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Wayuu)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WAYUU_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Wayuu) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WAYUU_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Wayuu (also Wayu, Wayúu, Guajiro, Wahiro) is an American Indian ethnic group of the Guajira Peninsula in northern Colombia and northwest Venezuela. The Wayuu language is part of the Maipuran (Arawak) language family. Even though the Wayuu were never subjugated by the Spanish, the two groups were in a more or less permanent state of war. There had been rebellions in 1701 (when they destroyed a Capuchin mission), 1727 (when more than 2,000 natives attacked the Spanish), 1741, 1757, 1761 and 1768. In 1718 Governor Soto de Herrera called them "barbarians, horse thieves, worthy of death, without God, without law and without a king." Of all the Indigenous peoples in the territory of Colombia, they were unique in having learned the use of firearms and horses. In 1769 the Spanish took 22 Wayuus captive in order to put them to work building the fortifications of Cartagena. The reaction of the Indians was unexpected. On May 2, 1769, at El Rincón, near Río de la Hacha, they set their village afire, burning the church and two Spaniards who had taken refuge in it. They also captured the priest. The Spanish immediately dispatched an expedition from El Rincón to capture the Indians. At the head of this force was José Antonio de Sierra, a mestizo who had also headed the party that had taken the 22 Guajiro captives. The Guajiros recognized him and forced his party to take refuge in the house of the curate, which they then set afire. Sierra and eight of his men were killed.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_XIA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Xia)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_XIA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Xia) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_XIA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Xia dynasty is the first dynasty in traditional Chinese history. It is described in ancient historical chronicles such as the Bamboo Annals, the Classic of History and the Records of the Grand Historian. According to tradition, the dynasty was established by the legendary Yu the Great after Shun, the last of the Five Emperors, gave his throne to him. The Xia was later succeeded by the Shang dynasty (1600-1046 BC). According to the traditional chronology based upon calculations by Liu Xin, the Xia ruled between 2205 and 1766 BC; according to the chronology based upon the Bamboo Annals, it ruled between 1989 and 1558 BC. The Xia-Shang-Zhou Chronology Project concluded that the Xia existed between 2070 and 1600 BC. The tradition of tracing Chinese political history from heroic early emperors to the Xia to succeeding dynasties comes from the idea of the Mandate of Heaven, in which only one legitimate dynasty can exist at any given time, and was promoted by the Confucian school in the Eastern Zhou period, later becoming the basic position of imperial historiography and ideology. Although the Xia is an important element in early Chinese history, reliable information on the history of China before 13th century BC can only come from archaeological evidence since China's first established written system on a durable medium, the oracle bone script, did not exist until then; however, no mention of the Xia, or the supposed conquest of the Xia by the Shang, is found in any oracle bones found to date. The first documentary reference to the Xia dates from more than a thousand years later. Thus, concrete existence for the Xia is unproven, despite efforts by Chinese archaeologists to link the Xia with Bronze Age Erlitou archaeological sites. The Xia dynasty is considered by many modern historians to be legendary.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_XIANBEI_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Xianbei)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_XIANBEI_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Xianbei) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_XIANBEI_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Xianbei were proto-Mongols residing in what became today's eastern Mongolia, Inner Mongolia, and Northeast China. Chinese historical texts unequivocally state that the Xianbei were descendants of the Donghu, which used to be believed to represent the "Eastern Hu" based on the Chinese record. The Xianbei were a northern or northeastern Asian population according to modern Chinese and Russian anthropologists. </English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_YAGUA_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Yagua)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_YAGUA_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Yagua) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_YAGUA_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Yagua people are an indigenous people in Colombia and northeastern Peru, numbering approximately 6,000. Currently, they live near the Amazon, Napo, Putumayo and Yavari rivers and their tributaries. As of 2005, some Yagua have migrated northward to Colombia, near the town of Leticia. The third earliest documented European contact with the Yagua was probably made by the Spanish explorer Francisco de Orellana in January 1542. While exploring in the area of modern day Pebas, Orellana encountered a village called Aparia, and captured two chiefs named Aparia and Dirimara, as well as some others. These names could conceivably have come from the Yagua words (j)apiirya 'red macaw clan' and rimyura 'shaman' respectively. The former could very well be a village name as well as a name applied to an individual; today clan names are still used by many Yaguas as family names. The word for shaman might also be used to refer to an individual, especially one singled out as a 'chief'. Regular European contact began in 1686 with the establishment of a Jesuit mission at San Joaquin de los Omagua, on an island in the Amazon river probably near what is now the mouth of the Ampiyacu River. Though this mission was established to serve the Cambeba people, there was undoubtedly contact with the Yaguas as well. From the 17th century to the last half of the 19th century, contact with the Yaguas was mainly through the Jesuit and Franciscan missionaries. In the early 18th century, Portuguese raiding parties attacked the Spanish missions throughout the Amazon region causing much geographic dispersion of the tribes that were in contact with the Spanish, and inflicting severe casualties.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_YOLNGU_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Yolngu)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_YOLNGU_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Yolngu) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_YOLNGU_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Yolngu are an Indigenous Australian people inhabiting north-eastern Arnhem Land in the Northern Territory of Australia. Yolngu means "person" in the Yolu languages. The term Murngin was formerly used by some anthropologists for the Yolngu. Yolu sustained good trade relations with Macassan fisherman for several hundred years. The Macassans respected the land as Yolu land; they only ever camped on the beach, and generally avoided contact with Yolu women. They made yearly visits to harvest trepang and pearls, paying Yolu in kind with goods such as knives, metal, canoes, tobacco and pipes.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZANZIBAR_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Zanzibar)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZANZIBAR_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Zanzibar) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZANZIBAR_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Sultanate of Zanzibar comprised the territories over which the Sultan of Zanzibar was the sovereign. Those territories varied over time. At one point they included all of what is now Kenya as well as the Zanzibar Archipelago of the Swahili Coast. Later they included only a ten mile wide coastal strip of Kenya and Zanzibar. Under an agreement concluded on 8 October 1963 the Sultan relinquished sovereignty over his remaining territory in Kenya. On 12 January 1964 Sultan Jamshid bin Abdullah was deposed and lost sovereignty over the last of his dominions, Zanzibar. In 1698, Zanzibar became part of the overseas holdings of Oman after Saif bin Sultan, the Imam of Oman, defeated the Portuguese in Mombasa, in what is now Kenya. In 1832, or 1840 (the date varies among sources), Omani ruler Said bin Sultan moved his court from Muscat to Stone Town on the island of Unguja. He established a ruling Arab elite and encouraged the development of clove plantations, using the island's slave labour. Zanzibar's commerce fell increasingly into the hands of traders from the Indian subcontinent, whom Said encouraged to settle on the island. After his death in 1856, two of his sons, Majid bin Said and Thuwaini bin Said, struggled over the succession, so Zanzibar and Oman were divided into two separate realms. Thuwaini became the Sultan of Muscat and Oman while Majid became the first Sultan of Zanzibar, but obliged to pay an annual tribute to the Omani court in Muscat. During his 14-year reign as Sultan, Majid consolidated his power around the local slave trade. His successor, Barghash bin Said, helped abolish the slave trade in Zanzibar and largely developed the country's infrastructure. The third Sultan, Khalifa bin Said, also furthered the country's progress toward abolishing slavery.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZENU_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Zenu)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZENU_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Zenu) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZENU_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Zene is an Amerindian tribe in Colombia, whose ancestral territory comprises the valleys of the Sinu and San Jorge rivers as well as the coast of the Caribbean around the Gulf of Morrosquillo. These lands lie within the departments of Cordoba and Sucre. The Zenú culture existed from about 200 BCE to about 1600 CE, constructing major water works and producing gold ornaments. The gold that was often buried with their dead lured the Spanish conquerors, who looted much of the gold. With the arrival of the Spaniards, the tribe all but died out. The 16th-century Spanish chroniclers wrote about the Zenú who were still living there, but recorded little or nothing about the history of the Zenu.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIMBABWE_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Zimbabwe)</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIMBABWE_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Zimbabwe) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<German>Kulturen ermöglichen den Zugriff auf kulturspezifische Gebäude und Einheiten.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIMBABWE_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Great Zimbabwe served as a royal palace for the Zimbabwean monarch and would have been used as the seat of political power. One of its most prominent features were the walls, some of which were over five metres high and which were constructed without mortar. Eventually the city was abandoned and fell into ruin. The earliest known written mention of the ruins was in 1531 by Vicente Pegado, captain of the Portuguese garrison of Sofala, who recorded it as Symbaoe. The first European visit may have been made by the Portuguese traveler António Fernandes in 1513-1515, who crossed twice and reported in detail the region of present-day Zimbabwe (including the Shona kingdoms) and also fortified centers in stone without mortar. However, passing en route a few miles north and about 35 miles south of the site, he did not make a reference to the Great Zimbabwe riddle.</English>
	</TEXT>
</Civ4GameText>