<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Civ4GameText xmlns="http://www.firaxis.com" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.firaxis.com ../../../Xml/Schema/Civ4Gametext.xsd">
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_REICHSTAG</Tag>
		<English>Reichstag</English>
		<French>Le Reichstag</French>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_REICHSTAG_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Reichstag[COLOR_REVERT] grants a [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Golden Age[COLOR_REVERT] to the player when he obtains a new vassal.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_REICHSTAG_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Reichstag building (Reichstag means in English: Diet of the Realm) is a historical edifice in Berlin, Germany, constructed to house the Reichstag, parliament of the German Empire. It was opened in 1894 and housed the Reichstag until 1933, when it was severely damaged in a fire. After the Second World War the Reichstag building fell into disuse as the parliament of the German Democratic Republic met in the Palace of the Republic in East Berlin and the parliament of the Federal Republic of Germany met in the Bundeshaus in Bonn. The building was made safe against the elements and partially refurbished in the 1960s, but no attempt at full restoration was made until after the reunification of Germany on October 3, 1990, when it underwent reconstruction led by internationally renowned architect Norman Foster. After its completion in 1999, it became the meeting place of the modern German parliament, the Bundestag.</English>
		<Polish>Gmach parlamentu Rzeszy w Berlinie - od 1999 siedziba Bundestagu w Berlinie. Od 1994 jest miejscem obrad Zgromadzenia Narodowego (niem. Bundesversammlung), które odbywa sie co piec lat w celu wyboru prezydenta Niemiec (niem. Bundespräsident). Gmach znajduje sie w dzielnicy Tiergarten. Neorenesansowy budynek zostal zbudowany w latach 1884-1894 wedlug projektu Paula Wallota. Do 1918 obradowal w nim parlament II Rzeszy Niemieckiej. W latach 1919-1933 odbywaly sie tu posiedzenia parlamentu Republiki Weimarskiej. Gmach doznal powaznych uszkodzen wskutek pozaru w 1933 oraz w wyniku dzialan wojennych. Zostal odbudowany w zmodernizowanej formie w latach 60. XX wieku przez Paula Baumgartena i przebudowany po zjednoczeniu Niemiec w latach 1991-1999 wedlug projektu Normana Fostera.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_REICHSTAG_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Starts a Golden Age When Another Civilization Becomes Your Vassal</English>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Kiedy inna cywilizacja zostaje Twoim wasalem w Twoim Imperium oglaszana jest Zlota Era</Polish>
	</TEXT>
</Civ4GameText>