<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Civ4GameText xmlns="http://www.firaxis.com" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.firaxis.com ../../Xml/Schema/Civ4Gametext.xsd">
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIODOME</Tag>
		<English>Montreal Biodome</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Le Biodome de Montreal</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIODOME_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Animals are born every few turns to help defend their beloved homeland. Animals get tougher with advances in era.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIODOME_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Montreal Biodome is a facility located in Montreal that allows visitors to walk through replicas of four ecosystems found in the Americas. The Montreal Biodome is one of four facilities operated by the Montreal Nature Museum, which include the Montreal Insectarium, Montreal Botanical Garden, and Montreal Planetarium. It is an accredited member of both the Association of Zoos and Aquariums and the Canadian Association of Zoos and Aquariums.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]The facility allows visitors to walk through replicas of four ecosystems found in the Americas:[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]The Tropical Forest is a replica of the South American rainforest.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]The Laurentian Forest is a replica of the North American wilderness.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]The Saint Lawrence Marine Eco-system is an estuary habitat modelled on the Gulf of Saint Lawrence.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]A polar area that is divided into Arctic and Antarctic.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]All the exhibits are housed inside the former velodrome that was used for the cycling and judo events of the 1976 Summer Olympics, with each of the four environments taking up a portion of the stadium. A variety of animals live in each simulated habitat, ranging from the macaws in the Tropical Forest, to the lynx in the Laurentian Forest, to the penguins in the Antarctic and the different kinds of fish that inhabit the waters of the Saint Lawrence River.</English>
		<Polish>The Montreal Biodome to osrodek zoologiczny, który pozawala zwiedzac cztery biodomy ameryki pólnocnej. Zajmuje sie takze ochrona i rozmnazaniem zagrozonych gatunków zwierzat.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIODOME_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Spawns Random Animal Every 5 Turns</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Fait apparaître un animal au hasard tous les 5 tours</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Co 5 tur "rodzi" losowe zwierze.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_NEW_ANIMAL</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]A baby [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] has been born in the [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Biodome[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]! Ooh it looks cute![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<French>[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]Un bébé [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] est né dans le [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Biodome[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]! Oh, comme il est mignon![COLOR_REVERT]</French>
		<Polish>[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]Maly [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] urodzil sie w [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Biodomie[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]! O, jaki slodziak![COLOR_REVERT]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CYRUS_CYLINDER</Tag>
		<English>Cyrus Cylinder</English>
		<French>Le Cylindre de Cyrus</French>
		<Polish>Cylinder Cyrusa</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CYRUS_CYLINDER_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Cyrus cylinder, also known as the Cyrus the Great cylinder, is a document issued by the Persian ruler Cyrus the Great in the form of a clay cylinder inscribed in Akkadian cuneiform script.  The cylinder was created following the Persian conquest of Babylon in 539 BC, when Cyrus overthrew the Babylonian king Nabonidus and replaced him as ruler, ending the Neo-Babylonian Empire. The text of the cylinder denounces Nabonidus as impious and portrays the victorious Cyrus as pleasing to the chief Babylonian god Marduk. It goes on to describe how Cyrus had improved the lives of the citizens of Babylonia, repatriated displaced peoples and restored temples and cult sanctuaries.</English>
		<Polish>Cylinder Cyrusa (zwany tez Cylindrem Cyrusa Wielkiego) - gliniany cylinder, na którym król perski Cyrus II Wielki nakazal wyryc pismem klinowym napisy stanowiace jego deklaracje polityczna po zajeciu Babilonu.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CYRUS_CYLINDER_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>The [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Cyrus Cylinder[COLOR_REVERT] generates great generals based on your empire's power.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CYRUS_CYLINDER_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Generates Great General Points Based on Game Score[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Vassals Increase the Rate</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Génère des points de General Illustre, basé sur le score actuel[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Les Vassaux font augmenter le taux</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Generuje punkty Wielkiego Generala na podstawie punktacji.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Wasale zwiekszaja przyrosty tych punktów.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LOTUS_TEMPLE</Tag>
		<English>Lotus Temple</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Le Temple du Lotus</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Polish>Swiatynia Lotosu</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LOTUS_TEMPLE_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Bahai House of Worship in New Delhi, India, popularly known as the Lotus Temple due to its flowerlike shape, is a Bahai House of Worship and also a prominent attraction in Delhi. It was completed in 1986 and serves as the Mother Temple of the Indian subcontinent. It has won numerous architectural awards and been featured in hundreds of newspaper and magazine articles.</English>
		<Polish>Swiatynia Lotosu w Delhi (ang. Baha'í House of Worship lub Lotus Temple) - najwieksza swiatynia bahaistyczna w Indiach. Zlokalizowana jest w poludniowej czesci sródmiescia Delhi. Uwaza sie, ze architektura swiatyni w wielu elementach nawiazuje do Tadz Mahal. Polozona w rozleglych ogrodach swiatynia wysokosci okolo 40 metrów, której wyglad zainspirowany jest kwiatem lotosu. Glówne filary tworza dziewieciokat foremny. Czesc górna sklada sie z 27 "platków".</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LOTUS_TEMPLE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Lotus Temple[COLOR_REVERT] gives you a second chance to make friends with leaders with serious conflicts.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LOTUS_TEMPLE_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Changes Leaders with Furious and Annoyed Attitude to Cautious Attitude</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Améliore l'attitude des Leaders adverses, de Furieux ou Inquiet à Prudent</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Zmienia Liderów z Nastawieniem Wscieklym i Zirytowanym na Ostrozne.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAZCA_LINES</Tag>
		<English>Nazca Lines</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Les Lignes de Nazca</Text>
			<Gender>Female</Gender>
			<Plural>1</Plural>
		</French>
		<Polish>Rysunki Nazca</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAZCA_LINES_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Nazca Lines are a series of ancient geoglyphs located in the Nazca Desert in southern Peru. They were designated a UNESCO World Heritage Site in 1994. The high, arid plateau stretches more than 80 kilometres between the towns of Nazca and Palpa on the Pampas de Jumana about 400 km south of Lima. Although some local geoglyphs resemble Paracas motifs, scholars believe the Nazca Lines were created by the Nazca culture between 400 and 650 AD. The hundreds of individual figures range in complexity from simple lines to stylized hummingbirds, spiders, monkeys, fish, sharks, orcas, llamas, and lizards.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]Contrary to the popular belief that the lines and figures can only be seen with the aid of flight, they are visible from atop the surrounding foothills. They were first discovered by the Peruvian archaeologist Toribio Mejia Xesspe, who spotted them when hiking through the foothills in 1927. The Nazca "drew" several hundred simple but huge curvilinear animal and human figures by this technique. In total, the earthwork project is huge and complex: the area encompassing the lines is nearly 500 square kilometres, and the largest figures can span nearly 270 metres. The extremely dry, windless, and constant climate of the Nazca region has preserved the lines well. The Nazca desert is one of the driest on Earth and maintains a temperature around 25 ¡ãC all year round. The lack of wind has helped keep the lines uncovered and visible to the present day.</English>
		<Polish>Rysunki z Nazca - system linii, które ogladane z góry przypominaja ksztaltem zwierzeta, rosliny lub figury geometryczne, bedacy dzielem kultury Nazca. Znajduja sie w poludniowo-zachodniej czesci Peru, niedaleko miasta Nazca, na obszarze ponad 50 km dlugosci i 14 km szerokosci. Linie znajduja sie na czterech plaskowyzach: Palpa, Ingenio, Nazca i Socos, polozonych pomiedzy 419 a 465 kilometrem autostrady panamerykanskiej. Zostaly stworzone przez Indian Nazca miedzy rokiem 300 p.n.e. a 900 n.e.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAZCA_LINES_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Nazca Lines[COLOR_REVERT] provide totally unpredictable benefits out of the following each era advance.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+2[ICON_HAPPY][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+2[ICON_HEALTHY][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+4[ICON_FOOD][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+4[ICON_PRODUCTION][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+4[ICON_GOLD][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+4[ICON_RESEARCH][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+4[ICON_CULTURE][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+4[ICON_ESPIONAGE]</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAZCA_LINES_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Random Benefits with Era Advances</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Des bonus aléatoirs lors du passage des ères</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Losowe dodatki z kazda nowa Era</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_NAZCA_LINES</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Nazca Lines[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] have increased![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<French>Les [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Lignes de Nazca[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] se sont développées![COLOR_REVERT]</French>
		<Polish>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Rysunki z Nazca[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] powiekszyly sie![COLOR_REVERT]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CATACOMBS</Tag>
		<English>Catacombs of Kom el Shoqafa</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Les Catacombes de Kom el Shoqafa</Text>
			<Gender>Female</Gender>
			<Plural>1</Plural>
		</French>
		<Polish>Katakumby z Kom el Shoqafa</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CATACOMBS_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Catacombs of Kom el Shoqafa (meaning 'Mound of shards' or 'Potsherds') is a historical archaeological site located in Alexandria, Egypt and is considered one of the Seven Wonders of the Middle Ages. The necropolis consists of a series of Alexandrian tombs, statues and archaeological objects of the Pharaonic funeral cult with Hellenistic and early Imperial Roman influences.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]Due to the time period, many of the features of the Catacombs of Kom el Shoqafa merge Roman, Greek and Egyptian cultural points; some statues are Egyptian in style, yet bear Roman clothes and hair style whilst other features share a similar style. A circular staircase, which was often used to transport deceased bodies down the middle of it, leads down into the tombs that were tunneled into the bedrock during the age of the Antonine emperors (2nd century AD). The facility was then used as a burial chamber from the 2nd century to the 4th century, before being rediscovered in 1900 when a donkey accidentally fell into the access shaft. To date, three sarcophagi have been found, along with other human and animal remains which were added later. It is believed that the catacombs were only intended for a single family, but it is unclear why the site was expanded in order to house numerous other individuals. The Catacombs of Kom el Shoqafa is, according to some lists, also one of the seven medieval wonders of the world. One of the more gruesome features of the catacombs is the so called Hall of Caracalla. According to tradition, this is a mass burial chamber for the humans and animals massacred by order of the Emperor Caracalla.</English>
		<Polish>Katakumby Kaum asz-Szukafa - odkryte zostaly w Egipcie w Aleksandrii w 1900. Sredniowieczni mysliciele i filozofowie wybrali je za cud swiata sredniowiecznego.[potrzebne zródlo] Do naszych czasów pozostaly one w idealnym stanie.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CATACOMBS_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Catacombs of Kom el Shoqafa[COLOR_REVERT] has a chance of killing the enemy whenever a unit died defending in a city. Chance increases for badly damaged enemy units.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CATACOMBS_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Chance for Enemy to Die with Slain Unit in All Cities</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Lors d'une attaque de vos villes, probabilité pour l'attaquant de mourir en même temsp que le défenseur</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Szansa na zniszczenie wrogiej jednostki za kazda zabita Twoja jednostke.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_MASS_BURIAL</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] was buried together with [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s2[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] in [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Catacombs of Kom el Shoqafa[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<French>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] a été enterré avec [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s2[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] dans les [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Catacombes de Kom el Shoqafa[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</French>
		<Polish>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] zostal pochowany razem z [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s2[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] w [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Katakumbach z Kom el Shoqafa[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FA_MEN_SI</Tag>
		<English>Famen Temple</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Le Temple de Famen</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Polish>Swiatynia Famen</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_FA_MEN_SI_INSPIRED</Tag>
		<English>Famen Inspired</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FA_MEN_SI_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Famen Temple is located in Famen town, Fufeng County, 120 kilometers west of Xi'an City, Shaanxi province. It was widely regarded as the "ancestor of pagoda temples in Guanzhong area".[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]One theory, supported by unearthed eaves-tiles and carved bricks of Han Dynasty, is that the temple was built during the Northern Zhou Dynasty, by Emperor Huan and also by Emperor Ling of the Eastern Han Dynasty. The literature record indicates that during Northern Wei Dynasty, Famen Temple already existed on a quite large scale. However, Buddhism was greatly suppressed in Emperor Wu's years of Northern Zhou Dynasty, and Famen Temple was almost completely destroyed. After establishment of Sui Dynasty, Buddhism was venerated, and Famen Temple was rebuilt, although it couldn't be recovered to its heyday in Northern Wei Dynasty. Its name was changed to Cheng Shi Dao Chang and soon it merged with nearby Baochang Temple and became a temple-owned farm.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]Famen Temple entered its halcyon days after formation of the Tang Dynasty. In AD 618, it was named Famen Temple, and monks were recruited next year. Later the temple took in homeless people from chaos caused by the war at the end of Sui Dynasty, and was unfortunately burnt. It was rebuilt later by the effort of monks. In AD 631, a man named Zhang Liang was appointed to demolish Wangyun Palace to build the pagoda. It was rebuilt in AD 660, and appeared to be a four-storied pavilion-like pagoda. It was named later by Tang Zhongzong "True Relic Pagoda". Tang Zhongzong actively advocated Buddhism, and along with Empress Wei buried their hairs under the pagoda (unearthed in autumn 1978). In AD 710, the temple was renamed "Grand Empire Carefree King Temple", and the pagoda "Grand True Relic Pagoda". In Yizong's years, it held the last activity of Buddha relic acquisition in Tang Dynasty. At that time, Famen Temple was rebuilt, and its underground palace has never been altered since then. The emperors of Tang Dynasty acquired Buddha relic 7 times here, and every time donated generously, which facilitated the expansion of the temple and pagoda. After being built and renovated multiple times, Famen Temple evolved into a scale of 24 courtyards.</English>
		<Polish>Swiatynia Famen to buddyjska swiatynia z czasów dynastii Han. Jest zlokalizowana 120 kilometrów od Xi'an w prowincji Shaanxi.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FA_MEN_SI_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>The [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Famen Temple[COLOR_REVERT] allows missionaries to travel faster and spread religion without failure.</English>
		<Polish>The [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Swiatynia Famen[COLOR_REVERT] pozwala przemieszczac sie Twoim misjonarzom szybciej i sprawniej rozprzestrzeniac wierzenia.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FA_MEN_SI_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Free Morale Promotion for New Missionaries Built[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]100%% Success Rate of Spreading Religion for Missionaries</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Promotion Morale gratuite pour les nouveaux missionnaires recrutés[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]100%% de succès pour la propagation des la religion</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Werbowani nowi misjonarze posiadaja nowa Promocje: Morale[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]100%% Szansy na rozpowszechnienie religii przez misjonarzy</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EMPIRE_STATE_BUILDING</Tag>
		<English>Empire State Building</English>
		<French>
			<Text>L'Empire State Building</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EMPIRE_STATE_BUILDING_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Empire State Building is a 102-story landmark skyscraper and American cultural icon in New York City at the intersection of Fifth Avenue and West 34th Street. It has a roof height of 1,250 feet and with its antenna spire included, it stands a total of 1,454 ft high. Its name is derived from the nickname for New York, the Empire State. It stood as the world's tallest building for 40 years, from its completion in 1931 until construction of the World Trade Center's North Tower was completed in 1972. Following the destruction of the World Trade Center in 2001, the Empire State Building reclaimed the position of tallest building in New York. Once the new One World Trade Center is completed, it will once again be demoted to second tallest building in New York.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]The Empire State Building is designed in the distinctive Art Deco style, and has been named by the American Society of Civil Engineers as one of the Seven Wonders of the Modern World. The building and its street floor interior are designated landmarks of the New York City Landmarks Preservation Commission, and confirmed by the New York City Board of Estimate. It was designated as a National Historic Landmark in 1986. In 2007, it was ranked number one on the List of America's Favorite Architecture according to the AIA. The Empire State Building is currently the third tallest skyscraper in the United States (after the Willis Tower and Trump International Hotel and Tower, both in Chicago), and the 15th tallest in the world. It is also the fourth-tallest freestanding structure in the Americas. The Empire State Building is currently undergoing a $550 million renovation, with $120 million spent in an effort to transform the building into a more energy efficient and eco-friendly structure. Receiving a gold Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design rating in September 2011, the Empire State Building is the tallest LEED certified building in the United States.</English>
		<Polish>The Empire State Building - wiezowiec w Nowym Jorku w Stanach Zjednoczonych. Jeden z najbardziej rozpoznawalnych symboli nie tylko miasta, ale takze calego kraju. Oficjalne otwarcie poprowadzil prezydent Herbert Hoover, który 1 maja 1931 w Waszyngtonie nacisnal przycisk zapalajacy swiatla budynku. Od chwili wybudowania do 1973 ESB byl najwyzszym budynkiem w Nowym Jorku. Tytul najwyzszej budowli odzyskal 11 wrzesnia 2001 po zamachach terrorystycznych na wieze World Trade Center, które byly do tej pory na najwyzszych pozycjach. W calym kraju jest obecnie na 3. miejscu po Willis Tower i Trump International Hotel and Tower w Chicago. Jego oficjalna wysokosc wynosi 381 metrów. Jednak jesli liczyc równiez antene znajdujaca sie na dachu wysokosc ta wzrasta az do 443,2 metrów. Ma 103 pietra, w tym jedno podziemne. Zostal zaprojektowany w stylu art déco przez Shreve, Lamb and Harmon Associates. American Society of Civil Engineers (ASCE) zaliczylo go do 7 cudów wspólczesnego swiata. Nalezy do World Federation of Great Towers. Jego nazwa pochodzi od przydomku stanu Nowy Jork, który brzmi wlasnie Empire State.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EMPIRE_STATE_BUILDING_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Empire State Building[COLOR_REVERT] provides 3 random bonus resources to boost your economy.</English>
		<French>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]L'Empire State Building[COLOR_REVERT] procure 3 ressources bonus au hasard, pour favoriser votre économie.</French>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EMPIRE_STATE_BUILDING_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Provides 3 Random Bonus Resources</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Procure 3 ressource Bonus aléatoirement</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Dostarcza 3 losowych surowców</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_EMPIRE_BONUS</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Empire State Building [COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]provides our empire with [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<Polish>[COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Empire State Building [COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]dostarcza naszemu imperium [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERGAMON</Tag>
		<English>Pergamon Altar</English>
		<French>
			<Text>L'Autel de Pergamon</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Polish>Oltarz Pergamonski</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERGAMON_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Pergamon Altar is a monumental construction built during the reign of King Eumenes II in the first half of the 2nd century BC on one of the terraces of the acropolis of the ancient city of Pergamon in Asia Minor.The structure is 35.64 meters wide and 33.4 meters deep; the front stairway alone is almost 20 meters wide. The base is decorated with a frieze in high relief showing the battle between the Giants and the Olympian gods known as the Gigantomachy. There is a second, smaller and less well preserved high relief frieze on the inner court walls which surround the actual fire altar on the upper level of the structure at the top of the stairs. It depicts, in a series of consecutive scenes, events from the life of Telephus, legendary founder of the city of Pergamon and son of the hero Heracles and Auge, a daughter of the Tegean king Aleus.</English>
		<Polish>Wielki Oltarz Zeusa - wolno stojacy (niezwiazany ze swiatynia) oltarz poswiecony Zeusowi i Atenie Zwycieskiej (gr. Nikeforos). Zbudowany zostal, wedlug projektów Menekratesa z Rodos, w latach (180-160 p.n.e.) w Pergamonie przez Eumenesa II dla upamietnienia zwyciestwa nad Galatami.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERGAMON_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Pergamon Altar[COLOR_REVERT] increases the rate of generating [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Great Generals[COLOR_REVERT] while decreasing the rate for rivals.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERGAMON_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Steals 2 Great General Points for Each Unit Killed</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Vole 2 pts Général Illuste pour chaque unité tuée</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Kradnie 2 punkty Wielkiego Generala za kazda zabita jednostke</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAIPEI_101</Tag>
		<English>Taipei 101</English>
		<French>
			<Text>La tour 'Taipei 101'</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAIPEI_101_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Taipei 101, formerly known as the Taipei World Financial Center, is a landmark skyscraper located in Xinyi District, Taipei, Taiwan. The building ranked officially as the world's tallest from 2004 until the opening of the Burj Khalifa in Dubai in 2010. In July 2011, the building was awarded LEED Platinum certification, the highest award in the Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design rating system and became the tallest and largest green building in the world. The tower has served as an icon of modern Taiwan ever since its opening, and received the 2004 Emporis Skyscraper Award. Fireworks launched from Taipei 101 feature prominently in international New Year's Eve broadcasts and the structure appears frequently in travel literature and international media.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]Taipei 101 comprises 101 floors above ground and 5 floors underground. The building was architecturally created as a symbol of the evolution of technology and Asian tradition. Its postmodernist approach to style incorporates traditional design elements and gives them modern treatments. The tower is designed to withstand typhoons and earthquakes. A multi-level shopping mall adjoining the tower houses hundreds of fashionable stores, restaurants and clubs.</English>
		<Polish>Taipei 101 - liczacy 509,2 m wiezowiec znajdujacy sie w Tajpej na Tajwanie, w dzielnicy Xinyi. Budynek, zaprojektowany w biurze C.Y.Lee and Partners i wzniesiony w przewazajacej czesci przez przedsiebiorstwa KTRT Joint Venture oraz Samsung Engineering and Construction. Do 4 stycznia 2010 (uroczyste otwarcie Burdz Chalifa w Dubaju, Zjednoczone Emiraty Arabskie) dzierzyl przyznawany oficjalnie przez Council on Tall Buildings and Urban Habitat tytul najwyzszego ukonczonego budynku swiata. Wiezowiec posiada 101 kondygnacji nadziemnych oraz 5 podziemnych. Postmodernistyczna architektura budowli laczy w sobie elementy tradycyjne i nowoczesne, nawiazujac zarówno do azjatyckiego kregu kulturowego, jak i trendów ogólnoswiatowej architektury. Taipei 101 wyposazony jest w systemy zabezpieczen zdolne oprzec sie trzesieniom ziemi i huraganom, czesto nawiedzajacym te czesc swiata. Wielopietrowe centrum handlowe przylegajace do wiezowca miesci setki markowych sklepów, restauracji oraz klubów. Pokaz fajerwerków wystrzeliwanych z budowli stal sie stalym elementem relacji telewizyjnych z obchodów Nowego Roku, wiezowiec na dobre wniknal tez do kultury masowej - pojawia sie czesto w filmach, programach telewizyjnych, drukowanych publikacjach, grach komputerowych i przy wielu innych okazjach.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAIPEI_101_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Taipei 101[COLOR_REVERT] increases relationship with other leaders. Merchants are attracted to it.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAIPEI_101_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]+3 Relationship with All Leaders</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]+3 de relation avec tous les Leaders</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]+3 do relacji z wszystkimi przywódcami</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TSUKIJI</Tag>
		<English>Tsukiji Fish Market</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Le Marché aux poissons de Tsukiji</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Polish>Targ Rybny Tsukiji</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TSUKIJI_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Tokyo Metropolitan Central Wholesale Market commonly known as the Tsukiji Market, is the biggest wholesale fish and seafood market in the world and also one of the largest wholesale food markets of any kind. The market is located in Tsukiji in central Tokyo, and is a major attraction for foreign visitors.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]The market handles more than 400 different types of seafood from cheap seaweed to the most expensive caviar, and from tiny sardines to 300 kg tuna and controversial whale species. Overall, more than 700,000 metric tons of seafood are handled every year at the three seafood markets in Tokyo, with a total value in excess of 600 billion yen (approximately 5.5 billion US dollars). The number of registered employees as of 25 January 2010 varies from 60,000 to 65,000, including wholesalers, accountants, auctioneers, company officials, and distributors.</English>
		<French>Montreal Biodome</French>
		<German>Montreal Biodome</German>
		<Italian>Montreal Biodome</Italian>
		<Spanish>Montreal Biodome</Spanish>
		<Polish>Targ rybny Tsukiji - nazwa oficjalna: Centralny Tokijski Hurtowy Targ Metropolitalny. Najwiekszy na swiecie hurtowy targ rybny. Takze jeden z najwiekszych hurtowych targów zywnosciowych w ogóle. Sprzedaje sie na nim wszelkie rodzaje ryb - od sardynek po trzystukilogramowe tunczyki - oraz inne owoce morza. Targ zostal zalozony w 1923, choc tradycja targów rybnych w Tokio siega epoki Edo, kiedy to pierwszy zostal zalozony przez Ieyasu Tokugawe. Ogólnie, na trzech tokijskich targach rybnych sprzedaje sie rocznie ponad 700 tys. ton ryb i owoców morza, a obroty wynosza okolo 600 mld jenów (okolo 5,5 mld dolarów). Sam targ Tsukiji zbywa okolo 2 tys. ton dziennie, a liczba wszystkich zarejestrowanych pracowników waha sie miedzy 60 a 65 tysiacami.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TSUKIJI_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Tsukiji Fish Market[COLOR_REVERT] increases the yield provided by fishing boats and grants a slight chance of finding new sources of [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]fish, clam[COLOR_REVERT] and [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]crab[COLOR_REVERT] resources when built.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TSUKIJI_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Places New Sources of Marine Resources around City[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Fishing Boats: +1[ICON_FOOD], +1[ICON_COMMERCE]</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Place de nouvelles ressources maritimes autour de la ville[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Bateaux-atelier: +1[ICON_FOOD], +1[ICON_COMMERCE]</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Umieszcza wokól miasta nowe lawice ryb wokól miasta[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Lodzie Rybackie: +1[ICON_FOOD], +1[ICON_COMMERCE]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_TSUKIJI_BONUS</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Tsukiji Fish Market [COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]found a new source of [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<French>Le [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Marché aux poissons de Tsukiji [COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] donne accès ç une nouvelle source de [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</French>
		<Polish>[COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Targ rybny Tsukiji [COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] odkryl nowe zródlo [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIZKOV</Tag>
		<English>Zizkov Television Tower</English>
		<French>La Tour de Télévision de Zizkov</French>
		<Polish>Wieza Telewizyjna Zizkov</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIZKOV_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Zizkov Television Tower is a unique transmitter tower built in Prague between 1985 and 1992. It stands high above the city's traditional skyline from its position on top of a hill in the district of Zizkov, from which it takes its name. The tower is an example of high-tech architecture.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]Like many examples of communist-era architecture in Central and Eastern Europe, the TV tower used to be generally resented by the local inhabitants. It also received a spate of nicknames, mostly alluding to its rocket-like shape, e.g. "Baikonur" after Soviet cosmodrome, "Pershing" after the US IRBM, etc. Although official criticism during the time of its construction was impossible, unofficially the tower was lambasted for its 'megalomania', its 'jarring' effect on the Prague skyline, and for destroying part of a centuries-old Jewish cemetery situated near the tower's foundations. However, the official line remains that the cemetery was moved some time before the tower was conceived. Recently, the tower's reputation among Czechs has improved. Voted #2 on the World's Ugliest Buildings list.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]Rumours have also circulated that the tower was planned to be used to jam incoming western radio and television transmissions and that it had a potential use as a communications facility for Warsaw Pact forces in the event of an attack on (or attack by) NATO.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]Today, the tower management strives to attract Czech visitors by focusing on the tower's technological innovations.</English>
		<Polish>Wieza telewizyjna Zizkov - wieza zelbetowa o wysokosci 216 m, zlokalizowana w praskiej dzielnicy Zizkov. Zostala zbudowana w latach 1985-1992. Zaprojektowali ja Vaclav Aulicky, Jirí Kozak i Alex Bem, a sama konstrukcja chroniona jest patentem. Z obiektu emitowanych jest szesc stacji radiowych oraz trzy multipleksy naziemnej telewizji cyfrowej. Na wysokosci 65 metrów znajduje sie restauracja i kawiarnia, natomiast na wysokosci 93 metrów zlokalizowano punkt widokowy, skladajacy sie z trzech kabin. Przy dobrej pogodzie widocznosc siega nawet 100 km. Wieza nalezy do Swiatowej Federacji Wielkich Wiez (World Federation of Great Towers).</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIZKOV_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Zizkov Television Tower[COLOR_REVERT] disrupts trade and conceals the world map of rivals. Additionally, it increases espionage in all cities and reveals the world map.</English>
		<French>La [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Tour de Télévision de Zizkov[COLOR_REVERT] disrupts trade and conceals the world map of rivals. Additionally, it increases espionage in all cities and reveals the world map.</French>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIZKOV_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Reveals World Map[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Conceals World Map of Rivals[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]10% Conceals World Map of Rivals Every Turn[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Rivals with Satellite Technology are Immune</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Révèle complètement la carte[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Dissimule la carte aux rivaux[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]10% de probabilité de dissimuler la carte chaque tour[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Les Rivaux possédant la Technologie des Satellites sont immunisés</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Odkrywa Mape Swiata[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Ukrywa Mape Swiata dla rywali.[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]10% Mapy Swiata jest odkrywane rywalom co ture[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Rywale z odkryta technoligia Satelity sa odporni na ukrycie mapy.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_GLOBAL_JAM</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Zizkov Television Tower[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] has jammed the radio signals all over the world![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<French>La[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Tour de Télévision de Zizkov[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] a brouillé tous les signaux radio![COLOR_REVERT]</French>
		<Polish>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Wieza Telewizyjna Zizkov[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] zaklócila sygnaly radiowe na calym swiecie![COLOR_REVERT]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_ZIZKOV1</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Zizkov Television Tower[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] has jammed the radio signals of [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<French>La [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Tour de Télévision de Zizkov[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] a brouillé les signaux radio de [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</French>
		<Polish>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Wieza Telewizyjna Zizkov[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] zaklócila sygnaly radiowe [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_ZIZKOV2</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Zizkov Television Tower has jammed our radio signals![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<French>La [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Tour de Télévision de Zizkov a brouillé nos signaux radio![COLOR_REVERT]</French>
		<Polish>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Wieza Telewizyjna Zizkov zaklócila nasze sygnaly radiowe![COLOR_REVERT]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_PROJECT_NPT</Tag>
		<English>Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty</English>
		<French>Le Traité de Non-Prolifération nucléaire</French>
		<Polish>Uklad o nierozprzestrzenianiu broni jadrowej</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_PROJECT_NPT_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>n/a</English>
		<Polish>,</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_PROJECT_NPT_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]All Players -1 Relationship with Nuke Owner for each Nuke Exploded[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Furious Rivals Declare War Immediately with Nuke Owner when Nuke Exploded[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires The Manhattan Project[COLOR_REVERT][NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]The Treaty on the Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons, commonly known as the Non-Proliferation Treaty or NPT, is a landmark international treaty whose objective is to prevent the spread of nuclear weapons and weapons technology, to promote cooperation in the peaceful uses of nuclear energy and to further the goal of achieving nuclear disarmament and general and complete disarmament. Opened for signature in 1968, the Treaty entered into force in 1970. On 11 May 1995, the Treaty was extended indefinitely. A total of 190 parties have joined the Treaty, including the five nuclear-weapon States: the United States, Russia, the United Kingdom, France, and China (also the five permanent members of the United Nations Security Council). More countries have ratified the NPT than any other arms limitation and disarmament agreement, a testament to the Treaty's significance. Four non-parties to the treaty are known or believed to possess nuclear weapons: India, Pakistan and North Korea have openly tested and declared that they possess nuclear weapons, while Israel has had a policy of opacity regarding its own nuclear weapons program. North Korea acceded to the treaty in 1985, but never came into compliance, and announced its withdrawal in 2003.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]The NPT is often seen to be based on a central bargain: ¡°the NPT non-nuclear-weapon states agree never to acquire nuclear weapons and the NPT nuclear-weapon states in exchange agree to share the benefits of peaceful nuclear technology and to pursue nuclear disarmament aimed at the ultimate elimination of their nuclear arsenals¡±. The treaty is reviewed every five years in meetings called Review Conferences of the Parties to the Treaty of Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons. Even though the treaty was originally conceived with a limited duration of 25 years, the signing parties decided, by consensus, to extend the treaty indefinitely and without conditions during the Review Conference in New York City on May 11, 1995.</English>
		<Polish>Uklad o nierozprzestrzenianiu broni jadrowej (ang. Treaty on the Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons) - umowa miedzynarodowa zabraniajaca panstwom posiadajacym technologie budowy broni jadrowej sprzedazy jej do krajów, które tej technologii nie posiadaja i jednoczesnie zobowiazanie panstw, które jej nie posiadaja do zaprzestania prób jej rozwoju. Jest takze, w Artykule VI, obowiazek rozbrojenia jadrowego. Uklad ten zostal przedlozony do ratyfikacji 1 lipca 1968. Do konca 2003 roku ratyfikowalo go 189 panstw - wiecej niz jakikolwiek inny traktat.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_PROJECT_IVY_MIKE</Tag>
		<English>Ivy Mike</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_PROJECT_IVY_MIKE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>n/a</English>
		<Polish>.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_PROJECT_IVY_MIKE_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]Damage Boost for Nukes[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+1 Radius of Fallout Created[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires The Manhattan Project[COLOR_REVERT][NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]Ivy Mike was the codename given to the first United States test of a thermonuclear weapon in which a major part of the explosive yield came from nuclear fusion. It was detonated on November 1, 1952 by the United States on Enewetak, an atoll in the Pacific Ocean, as part of Operation Ivy. The device was the first full test of the Teller-Ulam design, a staged fusion bomb, and was the first successful test of a hydrogen bomb.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]The test was carried out at 07:15 A.M local time on November 1, 1952. It produced a yield estimated in the range of 10.4¨C12 Megatons. However, 77% of the final yield came from fast fission of the uranium tamper, which meant that the device produced large amounts of fallout.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][TAB]The blast created a crater 6,240 feet (1.9 km) in diameter and 164 feet (50 m) deep where Elugelab had once been; the blast and water waves from the explosion (some waves up to twenty feet high) stripped the test islands clean of vegetation, as observed by a helicopter survey within 60 minutes after the test, by which time the mushroom cloud and steam were blown away. Radioactive coral debris fell upon ships positioned 30 miles (48 km) from the blast, and the immediate area around the atoll was heavily contaminated for some time. Produced by intensely concentrated neutron flux about the detonation site were two new elements, einsteinium and fermium.</English>
		<Polish>Ivy Mike - nazwa kodowa (kryptonim) nadana pierwszej na swiecie, próbnej eksplozji termojadrowej przeprowadzonej 1 listopada 1952 roku na atolu Eniwetok nalezacym do Stanów Zjednoczonych. Byla to pierwsza eksplozja przeprowadzona w ramach Operacji Ivy. Moc wybuchu wynosila 10 megaton.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CYRUS_TOMB</Tag>
		<English>Tomb of Cyrus</English>
		<French>La Tombe de Cyrus</French>
		<Polish>Grobowiec Cyrusa</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CYRUS_TOMB_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The Tomb of Cyrus is the burial place of the ancient Cyrus the Great of Persia. The tomb is located in Iran, at the Pasargadae World Heritage Site. Cyrus the Great was a Persian Shahenshah (or Emperor), who founded the Persian Empire under the Achaemenid dynasty. It is also said to be the oldest base-isolated structure in the world, and so is resilient to sismic hazards. This empire thence expanded under his rule, as Cyrus eventually conquered the majority of Southwest Asia as well as much of Central Asia, from Egypt and the Hellespont to the Indus River in the east, to create the most expansive nation the world had seen up until that era.</English>
		<Polish>Cyrus II Wielki, zwany takze Starszym (ok. 590-529 p.n.e.) - król Persji z dynastii Achemenidów, syn króla Anszanu Kambyzesa I i medyjskiej ksiezniczki Mandane. Zjednoczyl w ramach swojego imperium wiele ówczesnych panstw. Znany nie tylko z wielkich osiagniec wojennych, lecz takze z tolerancji i sprawiedliwosci. W ciagu niespelna dwudziestu pieciu lat panowania Cyrus podbil wiekszosc krajów Bliskiego Wschodu z wyjatkiem Egiptu i plemion Wyzyny Iranskiej.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CYRUS_TOMB_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Tomb of Cyrus[COLOR_REVERT] prevents the death of [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Great Generals[COLOR_REVERT]. However, they need 8 turns to recover from their injuries.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CYRUS_TOMB_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]Great Generals can Cheat Death</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Les Généraux illustres peuvent simuler leur mort</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]Wielki General moze oszukac smierc.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_GG_REVIVE</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] is faking death and has escaped to the [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Tomb of Cyrus[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<French>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] a simulé sa mort et s'est échappé vers la [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Tombe de Cyrus[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</French>
		<Polish>[COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]%s1[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT] oszukal smierc i zbiegl do [COLOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]Grobowca Cyrusa[COLOR_SELECTED_TEXT]![COLOR_REVERT]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEMBLEY</Tag>
		<English>Wembley Stadium</English>
		<French>Le Stade de Wembley</French>
		<Polish>Stadion Wembley</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEMBLEY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Wembley Stadium[COLOR_REVERT] increases income with excess happiness in your empire.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEMBLEY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Wembley Stadium is a football stadium located in Wembley Park, in the Borough of Brent, London, England. It opened in 2007 and was built on the site of the previous 1923 Wembley Stadium. The earlier Wembley stadium, originally called the Empire Stadium, was often referred to as "The Twin Towers" and was one of the world's most famous football stadiums until its demolition in 2003.</English>
		<Polish>Stadion Wembley - stadion sportowy znajdujacy sie w Londynie, w dzielnicy Wembley. Jest narodowym stadionem Anglii i powstal w miejsce Starego Wembley, który stal w tym samym miejscu od 1923 do 2003 roku. Nowy Wembley otwarto w 2007, a pierwszy mecz na nim odbyl sie 24 marca 2007 (reprezentacje Anglii i Wloch). Jego pojemnosc to 90 tysiecy miejsc, co czyni go drugim najwiekszym stadionem w Europie (zaraz za Camp Nou w Barcelonie). Jest jednym z najnowoczesniejszych obiektów tego typu na swiecie, a jego wlascicielem jest The Football Association.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEMBLEY_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_YELLOW]HELP: [COLOR_REVERT]+25[ICON_GOLD] for every Excess[ICON_HAPPY]</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]+25[ICON_GOLD] pour chaque [ICON_HAPPY] en excès</French>
		<Polish>[ICON_BULLET]+25[ICON_GOLD] za kazdy nadmiar [ICON_HAPPY]</Polish>
	</TEXT>
</Civ4GameText>