<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSPY v2004 rel. 2 U (http://www.xmlspy.com) by XMLSPY 2004 Professional Ed. Release 2, Installed Multi + SMP for 3 users (Firaxis Games) -->
<!-- Sid Meier's Civilization 4 -->
<!-- Copyright Firaxis Games 2005 -->
<!-- -->
<!-- Game Text - New -->
<Civ4GameText xmlns="http://www.firaxis.com" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.firaxis.com ../../../Xml/Schema/Civ4Gametext.xsd">
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_CULTURE_STEAMPUNK</Tag>
		<English>Steampunk</English>
		<French>Steam-punk</French>
		<Spanish>
			<Text>Steampunk</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_CULTURE_STEAMPUNK_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>[BOLD]Steampunk[\BOLD], is a sub-genre of science fiction, fantasy, alternate history, and speculative fiction that came into prominence during the 1980s and early 1990s. Steampunk involves a setting where steam power is still widely used (usually Victorian era Britain or "Wild West"-era United States) that incorporates elements of either science fiction or fantasy. Works of steampunk often feature anachronistic technology, or futuristic innovations as Victorians might have envisioned them, based on a Victorian perspective on fashion, culture, architectural style, art, etc. This technology includes such fictional machines as those found in the works of H. G. Wells and Jules Verne, or the contemporary authors Philip Pullman, Scott Westerfeld and China Mieville.Other examples of steampunk contain alternative history-style presentations of such technology as lighter-than-air airships, analog computers, or such digital mechanical computers as Charles Babbage and Ada Lovelace's Analytical engine.</English>
		<Polish>Steampunk - nurt stylistyczny w kulturze (literatura, film, komiks, moda), odmiana fantastyki naukowej, boczna gałąź cyberpunku. W przeciwieństwie do cyberpunku, technika otaczająca bohaterów nie jest oparta naelektronice lecz na mechanice (np. odpowiednikiem komputera jest maszyna różnicowa). Charakterystyczne dla steampunku zainteresowanie rozwojem techniki często prowadzi do kreowania wynalazków nieznanych w naszej historii, dlatego nurt ten bywa zaliczany do tzw. historii alternatywnych. Akcja utworów steampunkowych przeważnie rozgrywa się w epoce wiktoriańskiej - erze rewolucji technicznej, wieku pary (stąd nazwa gatunku:steam, ang. - para). Steampunk nawiązuje do twórczości ojców fantastyki: Juliusza Verne'a, Herberta George'a Wellsa czy Marka Twaina.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_CULTURE_STEAMPUNK_QUOTE</Tag>
		<English>"There is nothing in machinery, there is nothing in embankments and railways and iron bridges and engineering devices to oblige them to be ugly. Ugliness is the measure of imperfection." - H. G. Wells</English>
		<French>"Il n'y a rien dans les machines, il n'y a rien dans les remblais et les chemins de fer et des ponts de fer et des dispositifs d'ingénierie pour les obliger à être laid. La laideur est la mesure de l'imperfection." - H. G. Wells</French>
		<Polish>"Nie ma nic w maszynach, w nasypach, w torowiskach i żelaznych mostach co obliguje je do bycia brzydkimi. Brzydota jest miarą niedoskonałości." - H. G. Wells</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_CULTURE_STEAMPUNK_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>TBD</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAMPUNK_EMBASSY</Tag>
		<English>Culture (Steampunk)</English>
		<Italian>Cultura (Steampunk)</Italian>
		<Polish>Kultura (Steampunk)</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAMPUNK_EMBASSY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Culture (Steampunk) to gain access to unique buildings and units.</English>
		<French>Construire la Culture (Steampunk) permet d'accéder à des bâtiments et unités uniques.</French>
		<Italian>Costruisci Cultura (Steampunk) per ottenere l'accesso a unità ed edifici unici.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAMPUNK_EMBASSY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Steampunk was influenced by, and often adopts the style of, the 19th century scientific romances of Jules Verne, H.G. Wells, and Mary Shelley.</English>
		<Italian>Steampunk è stata influenzata, spesso adottandone lo stile, dai romanzi scientifici del 19° secolo di Jules Verne, H.G. Wells e Mary Shelley.</Italian>
		<Polish>Steampunk - nurt stylistyczny w kulturze (literatura, film, komiks, moda), odmiana fantastyki naukowej, boczna gałąź cyberpunku. W przeciwieństwie do cyberpunku, technika otaczająca bohaterów nie jest oparta na elektronice lecz na mechanice (np. odpowiednikiem komputera jest maszyna różnicowa). Charakterystyczne dla steampunku zainteresowanie rozwojem techniki często prowadzi do kreowania wynalazków nieznanych w naszej historii, dlatego nurt ten bywa zaliczany do tzw. historii alternatywnych. Akcja utworów steampunkowych przeważnie rozgrywa się w epoce wiktoriańskiej - erze rewolucji technicznej, wieku pary (stąd nazwa gatunku: steam, ang. - para). Steampunk nawiązuje do twórczości ojców fantastyki: Juliusza Verne'a, Herberta George'a Wellsa czy Marka Twaina.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUNICIP_COMP</Tag>
		<English>Municipal Computing Engine</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Centre de Calcul Municipal</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Italian>Centro informatico municipale</Italian>
		<Polish>Miejska Maszyna Obliczeniowa</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUNICIP_COMP_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build a Muncipal Computing Engine to increase your city's science.</English>
		<French>Construisez un [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Centre de Calcul Municipal[COLOR_REVERT] pour améliorer la science de votre ville.</French>
		<Italian>Costruisci un Centro informatico municipale per incrementare la ricerca della tua città.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUNICIP_COMP_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>When the Analytical Engine proved it's worth, cities began commissioning engines of their own to be housed in specially built structures with dedicated steam engines to power them. Operating on a time-share basis, These massively imposing structures are a boon to a city's scientists and engineers though citizens complain about the enormous quantity of soot generated by the buildings as the engine housed inside them clacks away day and night.</English>
		<Italian>Quando il calcolo analitico dimostrò la propria importanza, le città iniziarono a commissionare i propri calcolatori, destinati a strutture costruite appositamente, con motori a vapore dedicati apposta per fornire loro energia. Queste strutture imponenti sono una manna per gli scienziati e gli ingegneri della città, anche se gli abitanti si lamentano dell'enorme quantità di fumo generato dagli edifici mentre il calcolatore all'interno risuona giorno e notte.</Italian>
		<Polish>Maszyna licząca - urządzenie mechaniczne, elektryczne lub elektroniczne wspomagające proces obliczeń. Pojęcie "elektroniczna maszyna licząca" było używane w języku polskim, w drugiej połowie XX wieku, na określenie komputera.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TR_WORKSHOP</Tag>
		<English>Traction Engine Workshop</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Atelier de Moteurs à vapeur</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Italian>Bottega di trattori a vapore</Italian>
		<Polish>Warsztat Lokombil</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TR_WORKSHOP_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build a Traction Engine Workshop to build Steampunk units.</English>
		<French>Construisez un [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Atelier de Moteurs à vapeur[COLOR_REVERT] vous permettra de fabriquer les unités [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Steampunk[COLOR_REVERT].</French>
		<Italian>Costruisci una Bottega di trattori a vapore per costruire unità Steampunk.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TR_WORKSHOP_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>A traction engine is a self-propelled steam engine used to move heavy loads on roads, plough ground or to provide power at a chosen location. The name derives from the Latin tractus, meaning drawn, since the prime function of any traction engine is to draw a load behind it. They are sometimes called road locomotives to distinguish them from (railway) steam locomotives that is, steam engines that run on rails.</English>
		<Italian>Un Trattore a vapore viene usato per spostare carichi pesanti sulle strade, arare campi o fornire elettricità in un certo posto. Il nome deriva dal latino tractus, dato che la funzione primaria di ogni trattore è trainare dietro di sè qualcosa. Spesso vengono chiamati locomotive da strada, per distinguerli da quelle su rotaia.</Italian>
		<Polish>Lokomobila (z łac. locus mobilis) - początkowo był to przewoźny zespół napędowy, zawierający: kocioł parowy, maszynę parową i urządzenie transmisyjne (np. koło pasowe), konstrukcyjnie zbliżony do małego parowozu, ale bez własnego napędu. W miarę rozwoju konstrukcji dodawano przymiotniki uściślające, ale zawsze był to zespół napędowy stanowiący zwartą całość w przeciwieństwie do siłowni z wydzielonym kotłem i silnikiem. Przeważnie silnik parowy był mocowany na kotle, rzadziej do jego boku.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PANOPTICON_PRISON</Tag>
		<English>Panopticon Prison</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Prison Panopticone</Text>
			<Gender>Female</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Italian>Prigione Panopticon</Italian>
		<Polish>Panoptikon</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PANOPTICON_PRISON_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build a Panopticon Prison to increase your city's law.</English>
		<French>Construire une [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Prison Panopticone[COLOR_REVERT] pour vous permettre d'améliorer l'ordre de votre ville et d'en réduire la criminalité.</French>
		<Italian>Costruisci una Prigione Panoptiocon per incrementare la legalità nella tua città.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PANOPTICON_PRISON_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The panopticon was proposed in the late 18th century as a more efficient way of keeping an eye on prisoners and malcontents. A central inspection house which prisoners could not see inside held guards to keep an eye on the prison cells which lined the perimeter and were all visible at all times from the inspection house.</English>
		<Italian>Il panopticon fu proposto nel tardo 18° secolo come una via più efficiente per tenere d'occhio i prigionieri e il malcontento. Una torre di osservazione centrale, all'interno della quale i prigionieri non riescono a vedere, ospita le guardie che tengono d'occhio le celle, che cositutiscono il perimetro e sono tutte visibili in ogni momento dalla torre d'osservazione.</Italian>
		<Polish>Panoptikon (Panopticon; gr. pan = wszystko; optikos = widzieć) - nazwa więzienia, wymyślonego i zaprojektowanego przez angielskiego filozofa utylitarystę, Jeremy'ego Benthama. Niezwykłość Panoptikonu miała polegać na tym, że jego konstrukcja umożliwiałaby więziennym strażnikom obserwowanie więźniów tak, by nie wiedzieli, czy i kiedy są obserwowani.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MADSCIENTIST_CASTLE</Tag>
		<English>Mad Scientist's Castle</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Château de Savant Fou</Text>
			<Gender>Male</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Italian>Castello dello scienziato pazzo</Italian>
		<Polish>Zamek Szalonego Naukowca</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MADSCIENTIST_CASTLE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build a Mad Scientist's Castle to increase your city's science.</English>
		<French>Construisez un [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Château de Savant Fou[COLOR_REVERT] pour améliorer la science de votre ville.</French>
		<Italian>Costruisci un Castello dello scienziato pazzo per incrementare la ricerca della tua città.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MADSCIENTIST_CASTLE_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>The local domicile for the resident mad scientist who controls the surrounding countryside with an iron fist and an army of weird science. Technological progress increases from his experiments and maintenance decreases because he and his capable minions handle some of the local government work. Random experiments on the population tends to upset people though.</English>
		<Italian>La residenza locale dello scienziato pazzo che controlla la campagna circostante, con il pugno di ferro e la sua conoscenza tecnologica. Dai suoi esperimenti derivano un avanzamento tecnologico e una diminuzione del mantenimento, dato che lui e i suoi abili aiutanti controllano il governo locale. Tuttavia, alcuni esperimenti sulla popolazione tendono a innervosire le persone.</Italian>
		<Polish>Szalony naukowiec jest bardzo często przedstawiany jako złoczyńca. Jest to postać, której pogląd na otaczający ją świat jest zniszczony przez maniakalne podejście do nauki i która pracuje nad stworzeniem wynalazku albo odkryciem sposobu na uzyskanie władzy lub pokonanie bohatera. Typowym zakończeniem fabuły jest obrócenie się wynalazku wobec samego naukowca albo poprzez błąd w jego zamyśle lub przez wykorzystanie wynalazku przez bohatera. Przykładami szalonych naukowców są Dr Evil, Dr Frankenstein, Dr Eggman czy Dr Doom.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COAL_DYNAMO</Tag>
		<English>Coal Fired Dynamo</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Dynamo à Charbon</Text>
			<Gender>Female</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Italian>Generatore a carbone</Italian>
		<Polish>Dynamo na węgiel</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COAL_DYNAMO_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build a Coal Fired Dynamo to increase your city's electricity.</English>
		<French>Construisez une [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Dynamo à charbon[COLOR_REVERT] vous permet d'augmenter l'électricité produite dans la ville.</French>
		<Italian>Costruisci un Generatore a carbone per incrementare la produzione elettrica della tua città.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COAL_DYNAMO_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>A primitive Steampunk power plant.</English>
		<Italian>Un primitivo impianto di generazione elettrica.</Italian>
		<Polish>Prymitywna elektownia steampunkowa.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WOOD_DYNAMO</Tag>
		<English>Wood Fired Dynamo</English>
		<French>
			<Text>Dynamo à Bois</Text>
			<Gender>Female</Gender>
			<Plural>0</Plural>
		</French>
		<Italian>Generatore a legna</Italian>
		<Polish>Dynamo na drewno</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WOOD_DYNAMO_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build a Wood Fired Dynamo to increase your city's electricity.</English>
		<French>Construisez une [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Dynamo à bois[COLOR_REVERT] vous permet d'augmenter l'électricité produite dans la ville.</French>
		<Italian>Costruisci un Generatore a legna per incrementare la produzione elettrica della tua città.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WOOD_DYNAMO_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>A primitive Steampunk power plant.</English>
		<Italian>Un primitivo impianto di generazione elettrica.</Italian>
		<Polish>Prymitywna elektownia steampunkowa.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PEAT_DYNAMO</Tag>
		<English>Peat Fired Dynamo</English>
		<French>Dynamo à tourbe</French>
		<Italian>Generatore a torba</Italian>
		<Polish>Dynamo na torf</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PEAT_DYNAMO_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build a Peat Fired Dynamo to increase your city's electricity.</English>
		<French>Construisez une [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]Dynamo à tourbe[COLOR_REVERT] vous permet d'augmenter l'électricité produite dans la ville..</French>
		<Italian>Costruisci un Generatore a torba per incrementare la produzione elettrica della tua città.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PEAT_DYNAMO_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>A primitive Steampunk power plant.</English>
		<Italian>Un primitivo impianto di generazione elettrica.</Italian>
		<Polish>Prymitywna elektownia steampunkowa.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NEMO_ACADEMY</Tag>
		<English>Nemo's Naval Academy</English>
		<French>L'Académie navale de Némo</French>
		<Italian>Accademia navale di Nemo</Italian>
		<Polish>Morska Akademia Nemo</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NEMO_ACADEMY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<English>Build Nemo's Naval Academy to increase your city's naval power.</English>
		<French>Construisez [COLOR_BUILDING_TEXT]l'Académie navale de Némo[COLOR_REVERT] pour améliorer votre puissance navale.</French>
		<Italian>Costruisci un'Accademia navale di Nemo per incrementare la forza navale della tua città.</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NEMO_ACADEMY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Captain Nemo, also known as Prince Dakkar, is a fictional character featured in Jules Verne's novels Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea (1870) and The Mysterious Island (1874).</English>
		<Italian>Il Capitano Nemo, noto anche come Principe Dakkar, è un personaggio di fantasia presente nei romanzi di Jules Verne: Ventimila leghe sotto i mari (1870) e L'isola misteriosa (1874).</Italian>
		<Polish>Kapitan Nemo (nemo łac. nikt) - postać literacka z powieści Juliusza Verne'a Dwadzieścia tysięcy mil podmorskiej żeglugi oraz Tajemnicza wyspa. Projektant, budowniczy i dowódca okrętu podwodnego Nautilus. Był wysoki, miał niebieskie oczy i bladą cerę. W powieści 20 000 mil podmorskiej żeglugi trudno określić jego wiek, ale to dojrzały mężczyzna. Był człowiekiem spokojnym i łagodnym, jednak kiedy popadł w gniew, potrafił być porywczy. Pewny siebie i dumny, zachowywał dystans dla swoich gości. Jego załogę stanowili ludzie z różnych krajów, dobrzy, odważni i szlachetni, a także lojalni wobec siebie i swego kapitana.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BONUS_STEAMPUNK</Tag>
		<English>Steampunk</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BONUS_STEAMPUNK_PEDIA</Tag>
		<English>Steampunk was influenced by, and often adopts the style of, the 19th century scientific romances of Jules Verne, H.G. Wells, and Mary Shelley.</English>
		<Polish>Steampunk - nurt stylistyczny w kulturze (literatura, film, komiks, moda), odmiana fantastyki naukowej, boczna gałąź cyberpunku. W przeciwieństwie do cyberpunku, technika otaczająca bohaterów nie jest oparta na elektronice lecz na mechanice (np. odpowiednikiem komputera jest maszyna różnicowa). Charakterystyczne dla steampunku zainteresowanie rozwojem techniki często prowadzi do kreowania wynalazków nieznanych w naszej historii, dlatego nurt ten bywa zaliczany do tzw. historii alternatywnych. Akcja utworów steampunkowych przeważnie rozgrywa się w epoce wiktoriańskiej - erze rewolucji technicznej, wieku pary (stąd nazwa gatunku: steam, ang. - para). Steampunk nawiązuje do twórczości ojców fantastyki: Juliusza Verne'a, Herberta George'a Wellsa czy Marka Twaina.</Polish>
	</TEXT>
</Civ4GameText>